<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<diff xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../xmllib/diff.xsd">
  <add sel="/language">
  <page id="19530001" title="Clusters" descr="Names\Descriptions" voice="yes">			
	<t id="1">Planet 9</t>
	<t id="2">Following reports of unknown vessels and sporadic disappearances in the outer Oort Cloud, the Protectorate reactivated the trans-orbital accelerator leading to the secretive "Planet 9" and established a sentry presence. Generally considered to be the edge of Terran-controlled Sol, Planet 9 is chiefly remarkable for being the sector where Beryll Syndicate operations in Terran space were finally cornered and hunted to extinction, and is officially home to little more than the occasional patrol or intrepid prospector. However, the increase in traffic accompanying the reactivation of the accelerator has led to an uptick in unknown vessel sightings, and rumours abound that the Protectorate is preparing a major military operation to establish a permanent presence and ensure that any survivors of the Beryll purge or whatever else may be lurking out in the dark are destroyed for good.</t>			
	<t id="3">McCallum Relay</t>
	<t id="4">Found on the very outer edges of the Oort Cloud beyond an accelerator pair that was built in an effort to explore the interstellar space, this sector is now home to a previously undetected Xenon Core Matrix. Believed to have originated from replicant-capable Xenon technology carried by Beryll survivors that fled beyond Planet 9, this sector has evidently never been disconnected from what is now known as Branch 9, displaying all the standard Xenon technologies and designs that are recognizable across the Gate Network. While it is unknown how they maintained contact during Sol's isolation from the Gate Network, the most commonly accepted theory postulates that the Beryll survivors possessed a partially-functioning Jump Beacon, which allowed the Xenon to maintain their Branch Connection for a time after disposing of their would-be Beryll captors. How these Xenon have survived so long without a reliable source of energy is a mystery, though this makes it highly vulnerable to inevitable extermination by Terran forces.</t>	
	<t id="5">{20005,7012} {20404,2}(Mars 2)</t>
	<t id="6">Established due to a change in Protectorate doctrine focused on increasing Sol's strategic depth and resilience, the Ares sector encompasses a resource-rich region created by the orbital degradation of Phobos and bolstered through active asteroid capture from the Asteroid Belt conducted by deepspace expeditions ranging well outside the established Asteroid Belt sector. Previously overlooked due to the richness of Asteroid Belt, the increasing pressure on that sector as the first line of defense against hostile incursion has led the Protectorate to seek alternative concentrations of raw resources in the event that access to Outer Sol is lost.</t>	
	<t id="7">{20005,7017} {20404,2}(Mercury 2)</t>
	<t id="8">Another resource extraction sector established following a shift in Protectorate defensive doctrine, this sector is much closer than the Mercury sector to the planet itself and contains a large silicon-rich debris field. This field is the result of a controversial program of capturing potentially hazardous near-Earth asteroids and trans-solar objects and directing them into close proximity with Mercury, where they are broken up by gravitational interaction with Sol and settle into a close orbit to the small planet.\n\nThe long-running program, first initiated to protect Earth from potential impactors, has drawn heavy and continuous criticism for the dangers that the debris field and transiting captured bodies pose to the crucial energy cell production facilities of the Mercury sector. Nonetheless, the Protectorate's insistence on maintaining the program has over time built up a massive quantity of raw material both in the regional space and fallen to the planet's surface, which now provides an important strategic reserve in the otherwise resource-poor Inner Sol region.</t>		
	<t id="9">Althes</t>
	<t id="10">One of the several Terran Lost Colonies, Althes once formed the gateway between Sol and her other colonies. Connected to Sol via a Terran-constructed gate in the Neptune sector, Althes provided further access to the other lost colonies of Megnir, Segaris, and eventually Aldrin. When the gates shut down, Althes remained connected to neighboring Megnir through one gate, while another realigned with a Xenon Core Matrix, plunging the two colonies into a bitter war for survival with the equally isolated Xenon Matrix. The reconnection of the gates brought little relief, as the isolated Matrix synchronized with the rest of Branch-9 and evolved far past its previous capabilities, forcing the beleaguered colonists to withdraw to Megnir or face complete destruction.</t>		
	<t id="11">Megnir</t>
	<t id="12">Another colony once thought to have been lost, the initial rediscovery of Megnir, followed by Segaris and Aldrin, were momentous occasions subsequently cut short by the Gate Shutdown. Remaining connected to neighbouring Althes, Megnir found itself fighting desperately against the Xenon advance alongside her sister colony during the Isolation. Though the brunt of the fighting was borne by Althes, Megnir supplied much of the men and materiel, with the two nominally independent colonies understanding that this was a do or die moment for all involved. It was thanks to Megnir's shipyard - initially built by the Sol government, heavily used during the Isolation, and decommissioned following induction into the Pioneers Initiative due to the immense amount of acculumated wear and tear - that the colonies were able to avoid total destruction after the loss of Althes.\n\nContact with the colony was restored when a Gate reopened and connected the two-colonies-turned-one to the third colony of Segaris, now under the flag of the Segaris Pioneers. Though Megnir was initially slated for absorption into the Protectorate itself, the Pioneers successfully made the case that the Colonies had stood together before, and deserved the right to stand together again. The continued defense of Megnir is now undertaken by the combined Pioneer forces with occasional assistance by the Terran Intervention Corps, and it is the hope of many among the system's inhabitants to someday reclaim Althes and rediscover Aldrin, making the colonies whole again.</t>		
	<t id="13">{20005,8001} {20005,8003}{20404,4}{20404,8}(Matrix #48)</t>
	<t id="14">Once connected to a major Xenon sector only identified as "Core 023", the Xenon of this sector were the scourge of the Lost Colonies during the Gate Shutdown. When the gate connections began to fail, the Xenon moved extensive assets into Matrix #48, apparently foreseeing the need for the Matrix to stand alone. \n\nRemaining connected to Althes and Megnir while isolated, the local Xenon fought a deadly and protracted conflict against the neighbouring Terran Colonies, making slow but steady progress against the desperate defenders. The reopening of the gates allowed Matrix 48 to resynchronize with the Branch-9 network, catapulting its technological evolution overnight and enabling it to completely force the Terran defenders out of Althes. Though stopped at the Megnir-Althes Gate by the spirited defense of the colonists and later pushed further back by the combined forces of the Pioneers and Terran Intervention Corps, Matrix #48 remains a persistent lurking threat and source of continuing concern for the Segaris Pioneers.</t>	
	<t id="15">{20005,8001} {20005,8003}{20404,7}{20404,9}{20403,1}(Matrix #79A)</t>
	<t id="16">Even more of an enigma than Matrix #79B, this sector is scattered with an even greater number of unknown factors than its counterpart. A probing expedition undertaken by the Alliance of the Word confirmed initial suspicions that even the local region itself is a total mystery, with astrometric studies confirming that the sector had never been encountered within the Network before. Studies of the unknown structures within Matrix #79A have revealed that they pre-date the ones found in Matrix #79B, but gave no insights to their origin or purpose.</t>
	<t id="17">{20005,1041}(Power Circle)</t>
	<t id="18">Sometime before the last Xenon conflict, the planet "Shipfall" was blown apart by a mysterious disaster of awesome magnitude. The event annihilated nearly all traces of what had previously been a thriving Argon industrial colony, with rescue and relief efforts heavily stymied by continuing aftershocks.\n\nEfforts to recolonize the sector were interrupted by the Gate Shutdown cutting off the fledgling colony from critical outside supplies, and the sector was found once again empty when the gates reopened. Devoid of inhabitants, the scattered wreckage and debris in the sector stand a silent vigil for the untold lives lost.</t>						
	<t id="19">{20005,1041} {20402,5}(Power Circle V)</t>
	<t id="20">As initial entry point to the region, Power Circle V was once home to numerous spaceborne installations of the original Power Circle colony, and served as a forward base and staging area for recolonization efforts. Now reconnected once again, the intrepid colonists of the Antigone Republic have eagerly set to the task of reclaiming and recolonizing the system.</t>			
	<t id="21">{20005,1041} {20402,1}(Power Circle I)</t>
	<t id="22">Before re-colonization efforts were brought to an abrupt end by the Shutdown, the Argon Federation went to great lengths to try and secure the success of the new colony. Immense effort was taken to relocate the Gate which once connected to Three Worlds, and a local superhighway was built to ease the transport of supplies arriving in Power Circle V. Unfortunately it seems these efforts have gone largely to waste, as the colony has completely died out and the relocated Gate now connects to the enigmatic Xenon core sectors of Matrix #79A and #79B.</t>			
	<t id="23">Teladi Gain</t>
	<t id="24">The favoured retreat of Boron philosophers and visionaries, this sector came under Teladi management who swiftly reshaped it into a pleasure destination. The Bliss Place produced narcotic spaceweed - largely illegal outside of Teladi space - which drew in dreamers, artists, and neo-philosophers of all races. \n\nDuring the Shutdown the sector's priorities dramatically shifted and the various recreation facilities were quickly abandoned or turned to the necessary work of simple survival. Now reconnected, the Teladi have once again set about restoring the sector to its pre-Shutdown condition.</t>			
	<t id="25">Herron's Nebula</t>
	<t id="26">A mineral rich system made famous throughout Commonwealth space by its residents' vast consumption of Space Fuel and the semi-legal bootlegging which procured it, Herron's Nebula was once an important Argon core sector that supplied vast quantities of raw mineral goods for Federation industry.\n\nFollowing the Reconnection, Federation scouts were initially ecstatic to discover that the system still lay within the Argon sphere of influence, but this excitement was swiftly squashed as both the mining installations and distillery stations were found long-abandoned, with little evidence to be found regarding the fate of the sector's population.</t>			
	<t id="27">Three Worlds</t>
	<t id="28">Once on the border of Argon and Boron space the populated planets of this system were popular vacation destinations for the Argon high society seeking safe, cosmopolitan surroundings where the very best of Argon cuisine was available. When the Gates began to shutdown the sector saw a mass exodus of this society leaving behind only the less fortunate and workers; however, due to the excessive amount of food production in the sector they not only survived but are one of the few populations to grow and thrive.\n\nNow reconnected to the wider network the Argon Federation formally annexed the sector following a widely supported referendum.</t>
	<t id="29">{20005,8001} {20005,8003}{20404,7}{20404,1}{20404,4}(Matrix #714)</t>
	<t id="30">Despite being another newly discovered system, Matrix #714 shows clear signs of long term Xenon occupation with them even constructing structures on the planet's surface. While the purpose of these structures is unknown, the Xenon typically built them after establishing orbital ship production facilities.\n\nThere are still others within the Alliance of the Word who suggest that this order is reversed and instead that the structures come first and are then followed by orbital infrastructure. Regardless, Matrix #714 dominates this region of the Network, producing a steady stream of warships to fuel the fires of Thark's Cascade.</t>		
	<t id="31">Dark Waters</t>
	<t id="32">This system was rumoured to have a hidden gate leading to a top secret Boron military facility. Heavily policed, any potential threats were swiftly detained or destroyed despite the sector itself containing little more than trading outposts and minor mercantile facilities.\n\nAs the Shutdown progressed, the sector was completely evacuated to the neighboring Boron sectors.</t>		
	<t id="33">Mists of Elysium</t>
	<t id="34">The planet Elysium is described as a peaceful paradise world filled with lush plant life. Prior to the Shutdown a thick mist was known to fill the lowlands for half the planet's day, though this did not worry the Boron inhabitants sequestered in their deep-sea homes.\n\nUpon the sector's rediscovery, it was found that the mist phenomenon now extended to cover the seas as well, and that there were no Boron to be found anywhere on the planet.</t>			
	<t id="35">Depths of Silence</t>
	<t id="36">The heavily guarded secret of Dark Waters, Depths of Silence was formerly home to a massive scientific black site established by Royal Boron Military Defence to pioneer new technologies that could give the Boron people any advantage over their enemies. \n\nOnce filled with sprawling, high-tech complexes that investigated everything from creating advanced ion-hybrid weaponry to increasing the nutrient density of BoFu, the sector is now completely overrun by a Kha'ak infestation of unknown origin. What became of the heavy security force and the research they protected remains unknown.</t>			
	<t id="37">Light Water</t>
	<t id="38">Following the discovery of the North gate in Shore of Infinity, this sector was colonized by the Boron, who were well-suited to the unusual conditions of the water world which constitutes the system's only inhabitable planet. \n\nOnce home to a flourishing orbital food and energy industry that supplied other nearby sectors, the Gate Shutdown left the Boron residents in the odd position of having too much production of basic necessities. Lacking in heavy industry or significant technological manufacturing capacity needed to maintain the orbital facilities, the local Boron chose to abandon the spaceborne installations, salvaging as much material as they could before scuttling the stations and retreating deep into the planet's vast oceans.</t>			
	<t id="39">Shining Currents</t>
	<t id="40">Founded as a food production center to aid the continual growth of the Boron Queendom, the name comes from the reflection of the mercury ocean on the primary planet's moon. \n\nAs the gate Shutdown progressed, the Boron evacuated from Dark Waters took refuge in this sector, but neither they nor the original Boron presence seem to have survived.</t>				
	<t id="41">Shore of Infinity</t>
	<t id="42">In the pre-Shutdown network, Shore of Infinity served as a shining example of the warming in Paranid-Boron relations, with both species coexisting and cooperating through minor trade and technology exchanges.\n\nThis sector is home to one of the few Boron colonies that survived the Shutdown, albeit barely. However, the Paranid inhabitants are long gone to an uncertain fate - according to meticulous records kept by the local Boron archivist, these Paranid became increasingly unstable and erratic without the guiding influence of the Paranid religious leadership, culminating in a sudden and likely ill-destined mass exodus.</t>		
	<t id="43">Reservoir of Tranquility</t>
	<t id="44">Located near the giant star of Lehril, this system was once the crux of strategic power for the regional Boron presence. Bordering Split space and being a crossroads to the other nearby Boron colonies, control over the system was critical to maintain the flow of trade through the region and the Boron maintained a constant military fleet presence despite the lack of any permanent installations.\n\nUpon rediscovering the system, Alliance of the Word explorers found a few scattered Split wrecks and nothing else. Though carefully studied and salvaged for information, the wrecks held little to offer other than the radiation-faded markings of Split Family Rhy.</t>			
	<t id="45">Duke's Domain</t>
	<t id="46">A highly agriculturally developed system, Duke's Domain once provided huge amounts of the Soja Beans that form the basis of the Paranid diet. The highly ionised water of the system's planet contains rare organic minerals which greatly improved the flavour of beans nurtured with it, putting the agrarian output of the sector in high demand across all strata of Paranid society. \n\nDuke's Domain suffered particularly heavy losses in the previous Xenon conflict and experienced a near-total breakdown as the Shutdown progressed, with the local population struggling to cope both with their disconnection from Paranid leadership and the lack of heavy industry in the system, which made maintaining orbital installations an impossible task.</t>
	<t id="47">{20005,3038}(Perpetual Sin)</t>
	<t id="48">For a long time an insignificant system seeing only occasional Kha'ak skirmishes, it grew to being proof that those considered to be beyond redemption can be brought back onto the path. On the third day, of the third month, after having fallen into disgrace and being banished here, a Paranid scout managed to discover the location of a jumpgate leading to a then-unknown system. \n\nRegaining the respect of the Pontifex Maximus Paranidia, this scout was sent to explore the system but was never seen again. \n\nThe discovery of this active gate, in close proximity to the Second Duchy, was seen as further evidence that the Paranid Empire was destined for greatness and gave the sector itself some prestige.</t>
	<t id="49">{20005,3038} {20402,1}(Perpetual Sin I)</t>
	<t id="50">Once the original location of the Southern gate leading to Duke's Citadel prior to being relocated by the Paranid. Perpetual Sin I was established to further study the gate of legend and prior to the shutdown Paranid scientists discovered yet another gate floating lifeless and in a decaying orbit at the very extreme edge of the solar system. While there are no indications of their success the trapped Paranid appear to have been making attempts to reactivate these gates.</t>
	<t id="51">{20005,3038} {20402,3}(Perpetual Sin III)</t>
	<t id="52">A refuge for the Paranid who wish to seek the same redemption as the fabled scout of old, Perpetual Sin III has been designated as the site of their ultimate potential salvation and is the only acceptable place for these banished Paranid to gather within the Holy Order without risk of being executed. \n\nAs has became tradition, on the third day, of the third month, of this third system; disgraced Paranid assemble to find either renewed purpose and redemption or further disgrace and damnation. Those who return to the holy path are given this singular chance and should they fail in their duties again will be executed on sight.</t>	
	<t id="53">Fierce Clarity</t>
	<t id="54">A newly discovered system, Fierce Clarity has been designated by the reclusive Pontifex of the Holy Order as a new holy site of the three-dimensionality on the cusp of prophetic wonder. \n\nWhile the ultimate goals of the mysterious Pontifex are unknown, observers have hypothesized that the sector is being heavily developed to support the frontline combat against the Godrealm in neighboring Pontifex's Claim. Other, less substantiated rumours abound that the Holy Order discovered something of immense value in the sector and are trying to hide the truth.</t>						
	<t id="55">Pontifex' Seclusion</t>
	<t id="56">The last sector to be occupied in the New Duchy Sectors, this sector was famed for its lack of hospitality and is said to be a destination of retreat for the Pontifex, should he need to leave the main sectors and be isolated for any reason. Once located deep within the Second Duchy at the end of a treacherous path teeming with pirate activity, the gate realignment has resulted in the sector being absorbed by the Holy Order of the Pontifex.</t>			
	<t id="57">Unholy Descent</t>
	<t id="58">This sector lies in low orbit of the hostile planet Xhar'Bar, where the Xaarist priests accused early Paranid colonists of apostasy. \n\nEvidence suggests that hostile conditions on the planet claimed the lives of these colonists after being cut off from the network, thus depriving both the Holy Order of the Pontifex and the Godrealm of the Paranid of the chance to address these claims of heresy with action.</t>			
	<t id="59">Cathedral of Xaar</t>
	<t id="60">A system which had just been discovered and claimed by the Paranid prior to the beginning of the Collapse, Cathedral of Xaar was previously slated to become a far flung temple in service to the holy three-dimensionality. These ideas were dashed when the sector was once again thrown into the dark and those Paranid within driven to madness by the isolation. Now once again connected to the network, the Godrealm has wasted no time in revisiting these plans and have re-consecrated the sector as a holy site once again.</t>			
	<t id="61">Clarity's End</t>
	<t id="62">In the old network, this sector fell into dispute immediately upon discovery, as long-range scout patrols from Cardinal's Domain ventured entered this area at the same time as the arrival of a mining expedition from Aladna Hill. The resulting tensions did little but reopen old wounds, leading to a cooling of Paranid-Argon relations. \n\nHaving now been reconnected to the Network via Cardinal's Domain, deep behind Godrealm territories and far from Argon space, the Cardinal himself has issued orders to explore and exploit the sector's resources with the aim of aiding efforts to establish the Second Duchy.</t>			
	<t id="63">{20005,8001} {20005,8003}{20404,5}{20404,9}{20404,6}(Matrix #596)</t>
	<t id="64">The existence of this sector was thought to be little more than a legend. That was until a lone Boron pilot, crazed with fear and exhaustion, was picked up in the nearby sector, Menelaus' Paradise. He died shortly after rescue while babbling desperately about an eternal cosmic horror buried deep within the skin of a "dark planet". Because of this the Argon would send numerous spy probes to investigate yet no discovery was ever made public.\n\nFollowing Realignment, Matrix #596 is a part of what the Alliance refers to as a "Xenon supercluster", an area of the Networked dominated by the intensely strong signals emanating from within and the seemingly frenzied Xenon to protect it. Of much concern however, is that the once alien-like world has evolved into a writhing sea of flames and molten rock on a scale which even surpassed the worlds ravaged by the Xenon superweapon.</t>	
	<t id="65">Perdition's End</t>
	<t id="66">Perdition's flames brought fear to the hearts of both Argon and Paranid, and fury and rage from both sides have quenched the firestorm that burned through this sector. \n\nWith the Realignment placing the sector firmly in the Godrealm's sphere of influence, it seems that even flames of conquest may be flickering out for this sector.</t>		
	<t id="67">{20202,901} {20001,201} {20401,4}(Kha'ak Sector Delta)</t>
	<t id="68">When an unknown gate in Windfall III activated it brought with it a reckoning for the Syndicate; a Kha'ak invasion.</t>		
	<t id="69">{20005,7043}(Titania)</t>	
	<t id="70">Situated in close proximity to Uranus's largest moon, Titania, this sector was the primary base for the AGI Task Force prior to their merger into the wider Terran Protectorate. Now operating under the banner of the Intervention Corps, Titania has once again been built to deal with every operation or contingency which the Corps may have to commit to as part of their operational scope. \n\nDespite the organization's new name, Titania retains many of the old ATF landmark stations like the Military Flight School and the Central Intelligence Service which acts as an isolated branch of the Terran Secret Service despite the restructuring that was demanded after the Torus Aeternal was destroyed. \n\nDue Titania's close proximity to the Neptune gate it is believe that much of the protection and security of Outer Sol is organized here and following the recent rumors of Yaki involvement with the Pioneers, many have openly advocated for the return of ATF proper.</t>
	<t id="71">{20005,3020}(Xaar's Belt)</t>
	<t id="72">Following the reconnection of both Clarity's End and Perdition's End, Godrealm of the Paranid sent scouts to delve deeper into the new unknown and found this previously unidentified sector, believing it to be a sign from the holy three-dimensionality and immediately dispatched ships to establish three sets of superhighways.</t>			
	<t id="73">{20005,3020} {20402,1}(Xaar's Belt I)</t>
	<t id="74">Situated between the planet's two moons, Xaar's Belt I is rich in methane and acts as the anchor in the superhighway connections as the scouts identified the, at the time, inactive gate which now connects to the Xenon ravaged Desecrated Skies.</t>			
	<t id="75">{20005,3020} {20402,2}(Xaar's Belt II)</t>
	<t id="76">The sector's asteroid belt is the result of the second moon's slow decay caused by the planet's gravity pulling it down, which ultimately will result in the moon's impact of the planet and destruction of any potential planetary colony.</t>			
	<t id="77">{20005,3020} {20402,3}(Xaar's Belt III)</t>	
	<t id="78">When the Paranid scouts first entered the system via the Clarity's End gate they were met with the brilliance of the local sun's blue corona and began surveying the first moon while venturing deeper into the system, probing for any other potential gates before they made unexpected contact with another team of Paranid scouts who arrived via the Perdition's End gate.</t>	
	<t id="79">The Shallows</t>
	<t id="80">Originally deemed to be impossible to settle due to deeply drifting nebulae; The Shallows remained largely unpopulated. With recent solar flares having helped to clear the nebulae, building had continued at a greater pace. Both Boron and Split forces contested the area, eager to regain lost ground. \n\nDuring the Shutdown this sector was one of few known to have not regressed due to the dominating presence of the Strong Arms corporation and is directly connected to the "Enduring Shores" Boron sectors. \n\nThe Shallows stands as the crossroads against the Atreus Corporation and host to numerous skirmishes during the long isolation. Originally the over zealous Strong Arms conducted an invasion of Queen's Retribution while orbital assets were being evacuated and while the assault succeeded in ravaging the remaining Boron military, it was equally destructive on the Split and led to neither side having the advantage over the other.</t>	
	<t id="81">{20005,5044}(Family Than)</t>
	<t id="82">The seat of political power for the Split within the "Warlord's Dominion". Prior to the Shutdown, Patriarch Than was simply the director of the Strong Arms corporation but following this he seized power in the now completely cutoff Split sectors which now included this previously unknown sector. \n\nWhile all real power was still centered within Thyn's Excavation via the Strong Arms Corporation, Patriarch Than was eager to further validate his new title and laid claim to the entire system. However following reconnection to the Network and under the threats of Patriarch Zyarth, Patriarch Than fell in line and, officially, is subservient to Zyarth. In reality the Strong Arms Corporation still has completely authority within the "Warlord's Dominion".</t>			
	<t id="83">{20005,5044} {20402,1}(Family Than I)</t>
	<t id="84">The capital of Family Than and political seat of power within the "Warlord's Dominion", this sector is arguably the second most important Split sector because of the crucial ore mined from the asteroid belt. \n\nOnce reconnected to the Gate Network, Patriarch Zyarth demanded Family Than yield to his authority or risk the same fate as the formally Free Families. While officially subservient, Patriarch Than is still the director of the Strong Arms Corporation and has refused to degrade his status.</t>			
	<t id="85">{20005,5044} {20402,3}(Family Than III)</t>
	<t id="86">Pushed further out from the planet's orbit, Family Than III is the location of a previously inactive gate which has only very recently reconnected to the wider Network via Unholy Descent and by extension, the zealots of the Holy Order of the Pontifex. \n\nThe sole source of ore for the Split within the "Warlord's Dominion", this system is very busy with industrial ships traversing acrossing the sector to keep the ever demanding Strong Arm war machine running.</t>
	<t id="87">Thyn's Abyss</t>
	<t id="88">This deep space system was about as close as the Split got to a civilian operation and once produced food and other organic products while mines on the asteroids spread across the system. Due to the lack of any real military presence the sector was quickly overwhelmed by Xenon forces before they withdrew back to Matrix #472D just before the Great Shutdown.</t>		
	<t id="89">Thyn's Excavation</t>
	<t id="90">The location of the Stong Arms Headquarters, Thyn's Excavation provided funds and resources for the ongoing conflict in the local area against not just the nearby Boron but across the entire old Network and continues to be very well guarded by the aptly named corporation. \n\nFollowing the Great Shutdown, Strong Arms took complete control of the local Split sectors in what became known as the "Warlord's Dominion" ruled by the self appointed Patriarch Than, the director the Strong Arms Corporation.</t>
	<t id="91">{20005,9008}(Blue Horizon)</t>	
	<t id="92">Prior to the Great Shutdown this sector was officially designated US 18-16 and was the location of a disappointing mineral survey conducted by the Boron Royal Research Institute. Despite the poor results efforts continued to probe the sector for anything of value as it was reconnected to the "Enduring Shores" of the Atreus Corporation who deployed their only Superhighway following a review of the previous survey and the discovery that the results were intentionally fabricated for unknown purposes and obscured the fact that the sector was extremely mineral rich. \n\nHome to most of what was the "Enduring Shores" mining operations, Blue Horizon is as critical as ever against the local Split and Xenon threat.</t>			
	<t id="93">{20005,9008} {20402,1}(Blue Horizon I)</t>	
	<t id="94">The original core of the sector, Blue Horizon I is where the erroneous survey was conducted which stated that the sector was devoid of mineral value despite the presence of a significant asteroid field. \n\nAs such, Blue Horizon I is a vital source of ore for the Atreus Corporation's operation in the "Enduring Shores" and is generally well guarded against any potential Split incursion from the "Warlord's Dominion".</t>				
	<t id="95">{20005,9008} {20402,4}(Blue Horizon IV)</t>
	<t id="96">Settled as a result of the Atreus Corporation's construction of the Superhighway, Blue Horizon IV is abundant in both methane and silicon, further proof that the Boron Royal Research Institute's mineral survey was a complete lie. \n\nSituated further in to the Blue Horizon sector, it is less guarded than its companion and is directly connected to Queen's Harbour. However following the recent reconnection to the Network and the previously inactive gate to Great Trench now online and showing concerning signs of Xenon, the Atreus Corporation has begun to divert newly supplied Queendom military assets to better protect this vital system.</t>	
	<t id="97">Great Trench</t>	
	<t id="98">This Boron mining colony was once a busy hub of both industry and as a refit and supply center for Boron ships working in the new colonies. Harsh conditions and pirate raids made the Boron who lived here harder and more cynical than those in the home systems, \n\nOnce isolated, the colony very quickly fell apart as they were unable to produce their own food and quickly burned through any stockpiles they had gathered.</t>
	<t id="99">Queen's Harbour</t>	
	<t id="100">Once specialising in food and power storage technology, Queen's Harbour is the location of the original Atreus Headquarters that was lost when the Gates began to shut down. While the remnants of the corporation reestablished themselves in Ocean of Fantasy before collapsing under the stewardship of the Provinces Adrift, Atreus proper became the driving force in the "Enduring Shores" of Queen's Harbour, Queen's Retribution, and the formally colonized Blue Horizon. \n\nNow that connection has been reestablished these sectors immediately rejoined the Queendom but are still formally run by the Atreus Corporation due to the vast distance between them and Kingdom's End.</t>
	<t id="101">Queen's Retribution</t>
	<t id="102">Formally a Boron core sector specialising in technological and military output, Queen's Retribution was established to strike out against a growing conflict with the Split. During the Great Shutdown the new Boron colonies were completely disconnected from the wider network and instead were locked into a bitter conflict with the equally trapped "Warlord's Dominion" Split. \n\nWhile originally the home of the local Boron Shipyard, Queen's Retribution found itself now on the frontline in the local conflict. As such, all vital infrastructure was moved to the more secure Queen's Harbour and brought completely under the control of the Atreus Corporation.</t>
	<t id="103">{20005,8001} {20005,8003}{20404,4}{20404,7}{20404,2}{20403,4}(Matrix #472D)</t>
	<t id="104">Once a Split mining outpost, one day a distress signal from the colony was intercepted by the Argon security operatives in Black Hole Sun. When they investigated they found the entire system destroyed, its planet a radioactive hell and access to the system was restricted. There has been no official explanation from any government concerning this disaster although rumours suggest a Xenon superweapon was to blame. \n\nPrior to the Shutdown pilots who passed through this system once reported a large ship but those reports ceased and if the ship existed, its presence and location was never known and the Xenon presence in the system has only further increased following The Collapse.</t>
	<t id="105">{20005,6024}(Rusiris' Dream)</t>
	<t id="106">Located on the fringes of charted space, this area has drawn in adventurers and explorers with whispers of hidden treasures, lost Sohnen technology, and unexplained celestial phenomena.</t>			
	<t id="107">{20005,6024} {20402,1}(Rusiris' Dream I)</t>
	<t id="108">When the Alliance of the Word first discovered this sector they immediately notated the fierce, unpredictable, and perilous space anomalies just beyond the edges of the solar system and believing it to be nothing more than a curious deadend, the scouts left. \n\nIt wasn't until some time later that civilian explorers arrived and collectively navigated the perils and established the newly built superhighway.</t>			
	<t id="109">{20005,6024} {20402,2}(Rusiris' Dream II)</t>
	<t id="110">A magnet for daring pilots and intrepid researchers, Rusiris' Dream II has the allure of many mysteries to unravel and the boundless opportunities for discovery, where every journey could lead to untold riches or unforeseen dangers. \n\nFollowing the completion of the superhighway, Alliance of the Word scouts returned to the sector and discovered the active Gate to the South.</t>
	<t id="111">{20005,6025}(Shadows of Giants)</t>
	<t id="112">An enigma to the Alliance of the Word, Shadows of Giants is both completely unknown and had never been charted yet is home to a fully operational, albeit old, superhighway of unknown origin and unknown builder.</t>			
	<t id="113">{20005,6025} {20402,6}(Shadows of Giants VI)</t>
	<t id="114">"Shrouded in the darkness and adrift in the endless void this system bears witness to the Shadows of Giants."</t>			
	<t id="115">{20005,6025} {20402,7}(Shadows of Giants VII)</t>
	<t id="116">"Bathed in the light and tethered to the Great Giant, this system holds the truth of its magnificence."</t>	
	<t id="117">Bala Gi's Joy</t>
	<t id="118">Once deep in unclaimed space, Bala Gi's Joy is home to a cratered moon, used as a scrapyard for the wreckage of the many ship disabled and then stripped by the pirates of the past following ambushing and attack traveling ships. These same pirates were then trapped following the Shutdown and forced to survive on what little was left in the system following the years of stealing everything of value from the corpses of the dead. \n\nThey did not survive long.</t>
	<t id="119">Blue Profit</t>
	<t id="120">Once a busy and lucrative Teladi system with an economy dependent on high-quality electronics. Blue Profit was most famous as the source of the distinctive style of music devised by Teladi factory workers which combined Teladi reed-whistles and Boron toneshells with Argon and Teladi percussion instruments. "Teladi Blues" is still appreciated by many sentient species post-Shutdown. \n\nNow the sector's space remains silent, the economy having completely collapsed and nearly every ship no longer spaceworthy.</t>			
	<t id="121">{20005,8001} {20005,8003}{20404,4}{20404,8}{20404,3}(Matrix #483)</t>
	<t id="122">A vast and cold expanse, heavily fortified and dominated by the local Xenon, Matrix #483 was only recently discovered yet has clearly been inhabited by the Xenon for quite some time. Every aspect of the environment appears to have bene meticulously controlled, its clinical perfection masks a cold and unfeeling order. To venture into this sector is to navigate a world where every action is monitored and every mistake is harshly punished.</t>			
	<t id="123">The Vault</t>
	<t id="124">While the Teladi Company is not known for its military ventures, the population of this sector would have chosen to disagree. The Vault was a system hard to reach by normal means and contained nothing but high tech stations. \n\nHome to the Teladi Company's main research facility and it always tried to improve upon existing technology. While expected to expand and greatly improve the Company's assets, The Vault was lost to the Shutdown and all hopes and aspirations were lost with it when the colonists were unable to sustain their own survival.</t>			
	<t id="125">Recovered Capital</t>
	<t id="126">Once one of nearly a dozen pirate controlled sectors it was renamed to Recovered Capital during the Shutdown as a large Teladi fleet was stranded in sector and forced into a prolonged war against the equally isolated pirates. \n\nInitially things went very poorly for the Teladi before it became obvious that the pirates could not sustain the conflict beyond the opening phases and were ultimately overwhelmed. \n\nFollowing reconnection the Teladi Company has invested in the sector as a potential trade hub up for the far flung Godrealm and Holy Order enclaves.</t>
	<t id="127">{20005,9002}(Wretched Skies)</t>
	<t id="128">Those who entered this region of Wretched Skies did so for two reasons. To kill or be killed. Split Executor squads routinely patrolled, laying in wait for pilots to be lured into the sector before ripping them from their ships.</t>			
	<t id="129">{20005,9002} {20402,12}(Wretched Skies XII)</t>
	<t id="130">Nicknamed "The Meatgrinder", this region of Wretched Skies is what remained of the sector's tortured past and is where disgraced Paranid pilots duel to the death with Split pilots to settle debts, all sanctioned by Patriarch Zyarth and tolerated by the Godrealm.</t>			
	<t id="131">{20005,9002} {20402,15}(Wretched Skies XV)</t>
	<t id="132">A no man's land devoid of any value but strategic positioning and the superhighways established by the Teladi; Wretched Skies VII stands as a crossroad between the Teladi, the Godrealm, and the Holy Order which ensures the Paranid Civil war will rage here as well.</t>			
	<t id="133">Duke's Vision</t>
	<t id="134">The last great Duke once visited this sector and after a few short hours he collapsed and fell into unconsciousness. When he awoke he claimed he had visions of a great battle in this system between the Paranid and a strange alien race, now known to be the Kha'ak. The Great Duke decided to consult the monks at the Great Monastery on Paranid Prime in the valley of the setting star. His visions did not occur again and he was granted permission to set up a new temple in this system where he first had them. He died without ever knowing the true nature of his visions, or the horror that would follow them. \n\nSeemingly aware of the sector's imminent reconnection, the Holy Order of the Pontifex sent a massive fleet to reclaim it, denying the relatively weak Godrealm enclave in Wretched Skies the honor of bearing holy witness to it first.</t>	
	<t id="135">Emperor's Wisdom</t>
	<t id="136">While establishing themselves in nearby Duke's Vision Holy Order of the Pontifex scouts found another gate had been activated leading to a sector thought long lost, Emperor's Wisdom. While many within the Order felt this was a sign of divine blessings even more see it as an ill omen should the faithful of Xaar return.</t>	
	<t id="137">Consecrated Fire</t>
	<t id="138">A dark system located on the distant edge of the famous Garenisk Void, Consecrated Fire has become yet another point of conflict within the Paranid Civil war due to the Northern connection to Litany of Fury and the Southern connections to Duke's Vision and Emperor's Wisdom. \n\nWhere there is war there are usually privateers or pirates, something Consecrated Fire has no shortage of. It is currently unknown how the Scale Plate Pact organization is able to support their operations so far from traditionally friendly space but neither the Holy Order nor Godrealm have the resources to pursue them while entrenched in their bitter conflict.</t>
	<t id="139">Danna's Chance</t>
	<t id="140">This lawless system was the hub of the black market in food and low-tech industrial produce. Many unscrupulous merchants had made a fortune trading the illicit goods while many more were not so fortunate. \n\nDuring The Shutdown it would seem those local pirates banded together and became quite a formidable organization which kept a firm grip on control and managing the resources which were available. Since reconnection they accepted an invitation to join the Scale Plate Pact and have since received significant economic boost to their operations.</t>
	<t id="141">Legend's Home</t>
	<t id="142">Prior to the Great Shutdown this sector simply did not exist on navigation systems with any rumors ruthlessly squashed until OTAS was ready for the sector to be made public. A center for high tech research and development, Legend's Home is the beating heart of OTAS's power. \n\nAs the gates began to flicker, OTAS launched an invasion into the neighbouring sector of Akeela's Beacon after a dispute over financial bureaucracy would see the government's support of OTAS dwindle substantial. However, once the Great Shutdown began and OTAS was thrown into the dark they returned to their roots, albeit with significantly reduced wages, and are now even more technologically advanced than they have ever been.</t>
	<t id="143">Ministry of Finance</t>
	<t id="144">Once the pride of the local Teladi sectors; the high tower of the Ministry of Finance stands high on the planet's surface. The Ministry was setup to oversee the Company's finances when setting up in new sectors, although this wing of the Teladi Company wasn't entirely successful as the previously connected sector of Bad Debt became a "money pit" due to major miscalculation of the Paranid market. \n\nNow several decades later the Ministry has evolved into the financial police and law enforcement agency of the Teladi Company across their entire holdings.</t>
	<t id="145">Akeela's Beacon</t>
	<t id="146">The four great stars which grace this sector were created following the tragic but noble sacrifice of Akeela Hartnell. Her last will was for the Argon Federation to govern the new system and make it a safe haven for all traders. \n\nHowever, this dream was crushed shortly before the Great Shutdown when the OTAS corporation invaded and occupied the system to deprive the remaining Argon colonies of vital sources of energy. Initially this occupation was justified as a necessary step towards securing the well-being of the system's population but post-Shutdown OTAS reinforced their presence in the sector, developing it into a proper first line of defence should anyone, or anything, attempt to attack Legend's Home.</t>
	<t id="147">Aladna Hill</t>
	<t id="148">One of the first systems to be colonised by the Argon after the last Xenon war, Aladna Hill was a supply and support base for the exploration of further systems. Following the OTAS invasion of Akeela's Beacon the Argon Federation began to amass military assets with the goal of reclaiming the system and bring the corporation to justice. \n\nPost-Shutdown these military assets were used to keep law and order both in Aladna Hill and neighbouring Light of Heart. As such, when they reconnected to the Network they were swiftly reintegrate into the Argon Federation.</t>
	<t id="149">Light of Heart</t>
	<t id="150">Once the source of ships and equipment for the Argon settlements and was claimed following the conclusion of the last Xenon war. Following the OTAS invasion of Akeela's Beacon all efforts were made to build military assets for the counterattack. Unfortunately the Great Shutdown began before this planned attack was initiated which left a significant portion of the Argon Navy stranded in both Light of Heart and Aladna Hill. \n\nDuring this period of isolation Light of Heart changed from being a source of military assets and instead became the heart of trade and commerce with the substantial military ships keeping a firm grip on law and order. Once reconnected this pivot proved especially beneficial as Light of Heart became a key trade route in the Network's new orientation.</t>
	<t id="151">Montalaar</t>
	<t id="152">An old mining outpost founded near the red gas giant "Hitt's Eye", Montalaar had been an Argon settlement in the areas of space claimed following the Xenon conflict. \n\nTrading, food, and materials installations had been constructed in service to the private mining outfits looking to exploit new minerals but following the Shutdown these facilities were slowly decommissioned to keep the orbital station host to a small colony from falling apart. Now that the sector is reconnected, survivors have begun to be relocated across the Federation and the reintegrate of the sector has begun.</t>
	<t id="153">Mines of Fortune</t>
	<t id="154">Once the largest Teladi mining operation in history following the Teladi discovering and retrofitting abandoned space stations set into mineral-rich asteroids. The vast richness of the sector would be of no consolation to those left behind following its complete isolation as there was no infrastructure in place to refine the raw ore and silicon into useable products. It appears that the entire sector collapsed, unable to provide power and food to the doomed residents. \n\nCuriously the previously retrofitted mining stations are absent from the sector, their fates unknown.</t>		
	<t id="155">Zyarth's Stand</t>
	<t id="156">Originally little more than a desolate fallback for Family Zyarth once they had been cut off and trapped behind the Xenon, Zyarth's Stand became home to a Split Equipment Dock and the remaining Zyarth forces prior to the Great Shutdown yet even these gates immediately began to flickering following Family Zyarth's total assault against the Xenon. Now reconnected to Zyarth's Dominion, Patriarch Zyarth is eager to reclaim the system and fully integrate it into his new empire.</t>
	<t id="157">Patriarch's Conclusion</t>
	<t id="158">Once one of the Split's most remote core sectors with a moderate output of agricultural products. Military operations here served as the base for the building conflict in nearby sectors due to the ever increasing tensions with the Boron which finally escalated to outright war following the Great Shutdown. \n\nFollowing its reconnection, Zyarth scouts discovered that all orbital assets had been destroyed as the result of some undocumented war. Worse yet there was no evidence of any Boron wreckage or losses in the conflict which was either the result of sheer overwhelming numbers or the failings of these clearly disgraceful Split.</t>
	<t id="159">Elena's Fortune</t>
	<t id="160">After the Kha'ak attack on President's End the decision was made to bolster the defense of the Argon home systems. The Kha'ak's attack had decimated the pirate forces and allowed the sector to be reclaimed and fortified. Once the system's gates deactivated all of the Federation's plans fell apart and the sector quickly fell back into anarchy and disorder.</t>
	<t id="161">Nyana's Hideout</t>
	<t id="162">Named after the Argon heroine and Goner priestess Nyana Gunne, great-grandaughter of the famous Argon leader Nathan Gunne, this system was the location of some of the more colourful events in her life. Prior to the Great Shutdown the sector had fallen on hard times, hardening the people which served them well in the isolation. Following the Gates' reactivating, Nyana's Hideout connected to the still isolated Argon sectors near the newly formed empire of Patriarch Zyarth and became a shelter for refugees fleeing the frequent slaver raids.</t>
	<t id="163">Interworlds</t>
	<t id="164">Originally an agricultural colony built by the Argon to supply food to the rest of the Argon Federation, Interworlds expanded to include more high tech stations and products. Once home to the 4th Argon Expeditionary Force, they were not present in the system during the Great Shutdown. What did remain was unable to maintain the stations and slowly they were decommissioned to maintain the supply of food.</t>	
	<t id="165">Wastelands</t>
	<t id="166">Once named Light of Hope until the Xenon attacked many years ago and it was clear that the patrols wouldn't hold out against further attacks so the colony was prepared for evacuation using whatever transport ships were available. A large force of four Titan class Destroyers and two Colossus Carriers, complete with full fighter wings were dispatched to escort the fleeing transports but were overwhelmed by a Xenon fleet with only the civilian ships and a lone destroyer, the Challenger, escaping.\n\nThree years later a joint Argon-Boron force reclaimed the sector and recolonization began. Unfortunately the Great Shutdown once again thwarted this sector's progress and what had been established has fallen into complete disrepair and the surviving colonists eking out a meager existence.</t>	
	<t id="167">Ghinn's Escape</t>
	<t id="168">Founded to prevent the Boron expanding further into the area it once connected to, this Split colony was once heavily guarded and a large manufacturer of surveillance equipment and defensive weapons allegedly for protection against Boron aggression. Members of both Families Tkr and Njy were often found in this sector given its close proximity to their space and even saw some skirmishes between them following Family Njy's invasion and occupation of Family Tkr's territory as a result of the Dragon Incident. \n\nFollowing the Great Shutdown this colony completely collapsed and was entirely isolated for decades. The surviving Split families are only just now learning of Patriarch Zyarth's aggression while the sector itself has become a hub for the Fallen Families as they have bolster their ranks with the inhabitants of Ghinn's Escape.</t>					
	<t id="169">{20202,901} {20001,201} {20401,1}(Kha'ak Sector Alpha)</t>
	<t id="170">The presence of wreckage and debris clearly indicate this sector was once connected but there are no known records.</t>				
	<t id="171">{20202,901} {20001,201} {20401,2}(Kha'ak Sector Beta)</t>
	<t id="172">This sector  appears to be a source of a major Kha'ak infestation.</t>			
	<t id="173">{20202,901} {20001,201} {20401,3}(Kha'ak Sector Gamma)</t>
	<t id="174">A poorly scouted sector with sporadic reports of Kha'ak pressence.</t>				
	<t id="175">{20202,901} {20001,201}(Kha'ak Sector)</t>
	<t id="176">This region of space is disconnected from the gate network and shows sign of extreme Kha'ak infestation.</t>			
	<t id="177">{20006,301}(Unknown Sector)</t>	
	<t id="178">Error: Location not found within known network.</t>				
	<t id="179">{20202,901} {20005,4002}(Kha'ak Hive)</t>	
	<t id="180">Operation Final Fury Failed.</t>
	<t id="181">Spaceweed Grove</t>
	<t id="182">Pre-Shutdown the Teladi had been expanding their influence into the sector with aspirations to take control from the local pirates but were met with fierce resistance which only led to an even more protracted conflict. Now that the gates have reactivated Teladi scouts have so far only found the debris of both Teladi and pirate forces along with the shattered remains of old stations with unconfirmed reports that the other gate might also be active too.</t>			
	<t id="183">Shadow's End</t>	
	<t id="184">A previously hidden sector locked behind the OTAS Headquarters of Legend's Home, this sector has since come into its own during the Great Shutdown. Despite the close proximity and abundance of mineral resources, this was the last sector to be incorporated into the OTAS Corporation's holdings as it was not a threat to their security and no local facilities were required. \n\nSince being added, OTAS has expanded their exploitation of the rich resources to fuel their ever growing demand and infrastructure developments while also relocating several high-tech facilities.</t>	
	<t id="185">Tebathimanckatt's Legacy</t>	
	<t id="186">A dim, unpopulated sector along the Paranid border region, Tebathimanckatt's Legacy saw only cursory resource surveys when its jumpgate connection opened from Pious Mists IV, with the Godrealm being preoccupied with reconsolidating its holdings as the gate system began to awaken. This attitude changed following the discovery of the breakaway Holy Order and their heretic Pontifex, which coincided with a flurry of rumors that the sector's name was more than symbolic and that hidden somewhere within were artifacts of great power once held by Admiral Tebathimanckatt himself. \n\nThough these artifacts never materialized despite an intense search by private citizens and Godrealm-affiliated forces alike, the discovery of the jumpgate connecting to Perpetual Sin III saw the system's status skyrocket from quiet Godrealm backwater to a critical strategic avenue and second war front. Forming a potential path to strike at their enemy's interior regions, achieving military control over the sector became a high priority for both factions.</t>
	<t id="187">Untainted Eternity</t>		
	<t id="188">Situated above the accretion disc of a black hole - this sector is completely unknown and new to the Gate Network, unspoiled by centuries of conflict. \n\nCuriously, and troubling to many, the time dilation expected from such close proximity to a black hole is not observed here and even more concerning signals are somehow being emitted from within the black hole, which should be impossible.</t>		
	<t id="189">Belt of Aguilar</t>		
	<t id="190">Founded shortly after the first Kha'ak invasions, as a support outpost for the nearby colonies, Belt of Aguilar has had a short but turbulent history. With the rise of the newly relocated Jonferco, this sector initially enjoyed good prospects as it housed the only gate to the newly discovered Albion system; which was a playground for corporations to test new technologies and extract the vast mineral riches. \n\nHowever, following the destruction of the original Jonferco Headquarters and the shutdown of the Albion gate, the sector's future became uncertain. during the Great Shutdown what was left on the Jonferco corporation began to rebuild and return to their roots while efforts have been made in attempting to reactivate the Albion gate.</t>
	<t id="199">secret</t>		
	<t id="200">secret</t>
	<t id="201">Tkr's Deprivation</t>		
	<t id="202">Once owned by the T'kr Family and a hub of activity, this sector was seized by the Njy Family under orders from the Patriarch of all Split and became little more than a mining system following the Dragon Incident. Even before the Great Shutdown the sector had be run into disrepair with even new stations being poorly maintained, pirate activity had increased, and remains of a minefield played by the T'kr were scattered about. \n\nNow reconnected, Family Tkr attempted to reclaim and rebuild the sector before the disastrous loss in Fires of Defeat. To make a bad situation even worse it's been confirmed that the Northern gate is connected to a dangerous Xenon Matrix.</t>
	<t id="203">{20005,8001} {20005,8003}{20404,6}{20404,9}{20404,5}(Matrix #695)</t>	
	<t id="204">Identified as a heavily entrenched Xenon sector prior to the shutdown, #695 was barely explored due to the extreme risk to pilots and the data corruption of remote drones. While it once was believed to be a core sector; #695 was clearly severed from the wider Xenon network prior to its recent reconnection.</t>		
	<t id="205">secret</t>
	<t id="206">secret</t>
	<t id="207">secret</t>
	<t id="208">secret</t>	
	<t id="209">secret</t>
	<t id="210">secret</t>
	<t id="211">secret</t>
	<t id="212">secret</t>	
	<t id="213">secret</t>
	<t id="214">secret</t>
	<t id="215">Cloudbase South West</t>
	<t id="216">A crowded system which produced high quality wares for the Argon Federation, Cloudbase South West was used by the Goner as a base in their search for the origins of sentient life throughout the known universe. Many had spent their lives in study of ancient legends and engaged in deep historical analysis that eventually lead to the existence of Earth being proven to be more than just a myth. \n\nNow that the Goner have left the system began a slow decline as relations with the neighboring Paranid Empire remained heated. Now it serves as an important bastion against the Xenon threat in Tharka's Cascade.</t>	
	<t id="219">Ocracoke's Storm</t>
	<t id="220">This bleak region was once home to the Yaki pirate faction. While dozens of rumours swirled regarding the sector prior to The Shutdown, little else was ever confirmed and only speculations were left.</t>
	<t id="2000">Derelict Jump Beacon</t>				
  </page>	

			<!--OTAS Assets-->  
  <page id="19530002" title="OTAS" descr="OTAS" voice="yes">
	<t id="100">OTAS</t>
	<t id="101">The Optimised Technology, Armaments and Shielding Corporation, commonly known as OTAS, is a omni-corporation specialized in the design and manufacture of advanced spaceships headquartered in Legend's Home. In the pre-Shutdown era, OTAS technologies and ships were highly advanced, often leading the cutting edge of Commonwealth scientific advancement, granting the corporation a prominent position on the political starscape of the old Commonweath of Planets.\n\nJust prior to the Great Collapse, OTAS launched an attack on Akeela's Beacon in an escalatory response to the passing of certain industry regulations by the Argon Federation. Seen as an act of terrorism by the Argon, the resulting Argon military response was cut short by Gate Shutdown. While the exact history of the period is lost to the chaos of the Great Dark, it is clear that the Argon response failed to bring OTAS to heel and the corporation now holds full administrative and military control of the formerly Argon sectors in their local region. \n\nHaving evolved beyond a simple technologies corporation, the massive OTAS commercial enterprise now operates as a fully independent star nation. Featuring locally appointed representatives from each controlled sector sitting on the board of directors and a functional state apparatus that earns generally favourable public sentiment, any scars of the hostile takeover have seemingly faded from memory.</t>
	<t id="102">While very much still human, and thus biologically indistinguishable from Argon citizens, the citizens of the OTAS corporation-state have developed culturally into a distinct pseudo-corporate society during their isolation. Following the reconnection, OTAS citizens have come to be seen by much of the Commonwealth as a mixture of both the Argon and Terrans in ambition, technology, and temperament. Only time will tell if they continue to carve their own path or are ultimately brought back into the fold.</t>	
	<t id="103">OTAS Capital Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="104">OTAS Capital Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="105">Armaments Professional</t>
	<t id="106">Security Specialist</t>
	<t id="107">OTAS General Use Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="108">OTAS General Use Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="109">OTAS Military Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="110">OTAS Military Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="111">OTAS Police Licence</t>
	<t id="112">OTAS Capital Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="113">OTAS Ancillary Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="114">OTAS Advanced Module Licence</t>
	<t id="115">OTAS Basic Module Licence</t>
	<t id="116">OTAS Intermediate Module Licence</t>
	<t id="117">OTAS Trade Offer Subscription</t>
	<t id="118">OTAS</t>
	<t id="119">OTAS Ship Sale Contract</t>	
	<!--TURRETS/WEAPONS-->	
<!--<t id="200"></t>-->			
	<!--TURRETS/WEAPONS DESCRIPTIONS-->
<!--<t id="300"></t>-->			
	<!--STATION MODULES-->
	<t id="400">{19530002,100} Cross Connection Structure 01</t>	
	<t id="401">Cross 01</t>
	<t id="402">{19530002,100} {20104,15801}(OTAS Stimulant Production)</t>				
	<!--SHIELDS-->
	<t id="500">{19530002,100}(OTAS) {20111,5031}(L) {20106,1001}(Shield Generator) {20111,101}(Mk1)</t>
	<t id="501">{19530002,100}(OTAS) {20111,5031}(L) {20106,1001}(Shield Generator) {20111,201}(Mk2)</t>
	<t id="502">{19530002,100}(OTAS) {20111,5021}(M) {20106,1001}(Shield Generator) {20111,101}(Mk1)</t>
	<t id="503">{19530002,100}(OTAS) {20111,5021}(M) {20106,1001}(Shield Generator) {20111,201}(Mk2)</t>
	<t id="504">{19530002,100}(OTAS) {20111,5011}(S) {20106,1001}(Shield Generator) {20111,101}(Mk1)</t>
	<t id="505">{19530002,100}(OTAS) {20111,5011}(S) {20106,1001}(Shield Generator) {20111,201}(Mk2)</t>
	<t id="506">{19530002,100}(OTAS) {20111,5011}(S) {20106,1001}(Shield Generator) {20111,301}(Mk3)</t>
	<t id="507">{19530002,100}(OTAS) {20111,5041}(XL) {20106,1001}(Shield Generator) {20111,101}(Mk1)</t>
	<!--ENGINES-->
	<t id="1">While isolated from the Network during the Shutdown, OTAS continued to improve their engine technology, optimizing along similar distinct functional categories as their counterpart nations. Following the Reconnection, OTAS was quick to adopt the universal module interface in widespread use, and their engines are compatible with ships of all races with the exception of the Boron.</t>							
	<t id="600">(OTAS L All-Round Engine Mk1){19530002,100} {20111,5031} {20107,1001} {20111,101}</t>	
	<t id="6001">{19530002,100}{20107,203}{20107,304}{20107,401}</t>			
	<t id="601">(OTAS L Travel Engine Mk1){19530002,100} {20111,5031} {20107,1401} {20111,101}</t>
	<t id="6011">{19530002,100}{20107,202}{20107,304}{20107,401}</t>						
	<t id="602">(OTAS M All-Round Engine Mk1){19530002,100} {20111,5021} {20107,1001} {20111,101}</t>	
	<t id="603">(OTAS M All-Round Engine Mk2){19530002,100} {20111,5021} {20107,1001} {20111,201}</t>	
	<t id="604">(OTAS M All-Round Engine Mk3){19530002,100} {20111,5021} {20107,1001} {20111,301}</t>
	<t id="6021">{19530002,100}{20107,203}{20107,302}{20107,404}</t>			
	<t id="605">(OTAS M Combat Engine Mk1){19530002,100} {20111,5021} {20107,1201} {20111,101}</t>
	<t id="606">(OTAS M Combat Engine Mk2){19530002,100} {20111,5021} {20107,1201} {20111,201}</t>
	<t id="607">(OTAS M Combat Engine Mk3){19530002,100} {20111,5021} {20107,1201} {20111,301}</t>	
	<t id="6051">{19530002,100}{20107,201}{20107,302}{20107,404}</t>			
	<t id="608">(OTAS M Travel Engine Mk1){19530002,100} {20111,5021} {20107,1401} {20111,101}</t>
	<t id="609">(OTAS M Travel Engine Mk2){19530002,100} {20111,5021} {20107,1401} {20111,201}</t>
	<t id="610">(OTAS M Travel Engine Mk3){19530002,100} {20111,5021} {20107,1401} {20111,301}</t>
	<t id="6081">{19530002,100}{20107,202}{20107,302}{20107,404}</t>			
	<t id="611">(OTAS S All-Round Engine Mk1){19530002,100} {20111,5011} {20107,1001} {20111,101}</t>	
	<t id="612">(OTAS S All-Round Engine Mk2){19530002,100} {20111,5011} {20107,1001} {20111,201}</t>	
	<t id="613">(OTAS S All-Round Engine Mk3){19530002,100} {20111,5011} {20107,1001} {20111,301}</t>
	<t id="6111">{19530002,100}{20107,203}{20107,301}{20107,404}</t>			
	<t id="614">(OTAS S Combat Engine Mk1){19530002,100} {20111,5011} {20107,1201} {20111,101}</t>
	<t id="615">(OTAS S Combat Engine Mk2){19530002,100} {20111,5011} {20107,1201} {20111,201}</t>
	<t id="616">(OTAS S Combat Engine Mk3){19530002,100} {20111,5011} {20107,1201} {20111,301}</t>
	<t id="6141">{19530002,100}{20107,201}{20107,301}{20107,404}</t>			
	<t id="617">(OTAS S Travel Engine Mk1){19530002,100} {20111,5011} {20107,1401} {20111,101}</t>
	<t id="618">(OTAS S Travel Engine Mk2){19530002,100} {20111,5011} {20107,1401} {20111,201}</t>
	<t id="619">(OTAS S Travel Engine Mk3){19530002,100} {20111,5011} {20107,1401} {20111,301}</t>	
	<t id="6171">{19530002,100}{20107,202}{20107,301}{20107,404}</t>			
	<t id="620">(OTAS XL All-Round Engine Mk1){19530002,100} {20111,5041} {20107,1001} {20111,101}</t>	
	<t id="6201">{19530002,100}{20107,203}{20107,305}{20107,401}</t>			
	<t id="621">(OTAS XL Travel Engine Mk1){19530002,100} {20111,5041} {20107,1401} {20111,101}</t>			
	<t id="6211">{19530002,100}{20107,202}{20107,305}{20107,401}</t>	
	<!--SHIPS-->
	<t id="700">Boreas</t>
	<t id="701">Auster</t>
	<t id="702">Aquilo</t>
	<t id="703">Skiron</t>
	<t id="704">Sirokos</t>
	<t id="705">Solano</t>
	<t id="706">Eurus</t>
	<t id="707">Notus</t>
	<t id="708">Venti</t>
	<t id="709">Zephyrus</t>
	<t id="710">Astraeus</t>
	<t id="711">Mistral</t>
	<t id="712">Tempest</t>
	<t id="713">Vesuvius</t>
	<t id="714">Genthus</t>	
	<t id="715">Andaman</t>	
	<t id="716">(Magnetar \(Mineral\) Stalwart){20101,11101} {20111,3101} {20111,1401}</t>	
	<t id="717">(Magnetar \(Gas\) Stalwart){20101,11101} {20111,3201} {20111,1401}</t>
	<t id="718">(Drill \(Mineral\) Stalwart){20101,10801} {20111,3101} {20111,1401}</t>
	<t id="719">(Sunder \(Gas\) Stalwart){20101,10901} {20111,3201} {20111,1401}</t>
	<t id="720">(Mercury Stalwart){20101,10701} {20111,1401}</t>
	<t id="721">(Ides Stalwart){20101,11701} {20111,1401}</t>		
	<t id="722">(Courier \(Mineral\) Stalwart){20101,11601} {20111,3101} {20111,1401}</t>
	<t id="723">(Courier Stalwart){20101,11601} {20111,1401}</t>				
	<t id="724">(Callisto Stalwart){20101,12901} {20111,1401}</t>		
	<!--SHIP DESCRIPTIONS-->
	<t id="800">Once the linchpin of the OTAS fleet, the Boreas continues to serve as the organization's premier destroyer-class warship. Upon Reactivation the Boreas has undergone significant change to compete with existing destroyer class ships. The modern Boreas is now much more heavily armed and shielded than before while still retaining some of the signature speed.</t>
	<t id="801">Completely redesigned following the Shutdown, the modern Auster retains the rank of a heavily shielded and lethal bomber while still retaining the now S-class fighter size.</t>
	<t id="802">A descendent of the ship that first established "M7M" Missile Frigate type designation, the modern Aquilo honors its lineage with an intimidating array of launch tubes capable of launching the signature Anemoi Cruise Missile, providing massively destructive long-range fire support against capital targets and stations during OTAS fleet actions. \n\nDespite the tremendous power of its main armament, proper usage of the Aquilo necessitates a sizable escort force and strong local battlespace control, as the ship's relatively poor mobility and limited defensive armament leave it highly vulnerable to direct attack despite its typically above-average OTAS shielding.</t>
	<t id="803">The Skiron represented a significant step forward in OTAS corvette design. A further improvement on previous designs, the modern Skiron has evolved into a robust gunboat and is typically seen escorting capital class ships or as anchors in patrol fleets.</t>
	<t id="804">Once nearly abandoned following the seizure of Argon space, the Sirokos "M7M" frigate has had a radical redesign into a modern strike corvette with S-class fighter storage and launching capabilities.</t>
	<t id="805">The modern Solano is a highly advanced scout/interceptor hybrid. Its superb top speed and small size make it well-suited for swift reconnaissance in hostile space, and the above-average firepower packed onto the ship makes it a deadly counter to other scouting vessels, though it must rely on its speed to escape from larger threats.</t>			
	<t id="806">The standard fighter type deployed by OTAS, the Eurus is a well-rounded and capable combatant with respectable firepower and excellent high-speed maneuverability. While it has few truly stand-out features aside from the high top speed, the ship enjoys a general advantage over its Commonwealth peers thanks to the advanced nature of OTAS technologies. The Eurus is a common sight in any location with an OTAS presence, serving on the offensive frontline and enforcing police presence in secured sectors.</t>		
	<t id="807">The Notus bomber was developed by OTAS during the isolation of the Great Dark. Initially just an exploratory testbed attempting to emulate the success of the M7M missile frigate- one of the many OTAS innovations of the pre-shutdown Commonwealth- the Notus performed well in simulations and exercises, promising to provide an immense amount of striking power with the ability to carry and deploy a wide variety of heavy ordnance in its modular side pods. When the gates abruptly reopened and OTAS resumed open hostilities against the Argon Federation, the Notus soon proved its worth and became notorious for savage lightning strikes capable of swiftly crippling Argon capital ships. \n\nSeeing an opportunity in their shared enemy, the Zyarth Patriarchy were quick to make diplomatic overtures towards OTAS, with the aim of procuring the Notus' technology for their own use. This effort culminated in the Split Wolf bomber and numerous improvements to the Notus, as well as new weapons that could take full advantage of the Notus-type ordnance hardpoint. The technology rapidly proliferated through the rest of the gate network, with the other Commonwealth powers and even the Terrans soon fielding their own bomber models- developed through espionage, battlefield salvage, or their own engineering efforts.</t>
	<t id="808">Regarded as one of the most feared heavy fighters pre-Shutdown, OTAS diligently worked to keep the Venti at the pinnacle of lethality. The Venti is able to bring a truly devastating array of weapons to bare on anything deemed an enemy of OTAS.</t>
	<t id="809">OTAS completed a total redesign of the Zephyrus just after the reactivation of local gates. Acknowledging they would require a strike carrier capable of projecting OTAS authority, the redesign maintained the core concept of the ship but brought it into the modern era with the new standardized S-class docking bays.</t>
	<t id="810">Once a common sight in pre-Shutdown OTAS fleets, the venerable Astraeus saw continuous design changes and modifications during the Shutdown-era to fit an evolving combat role as OTAS reshaped its fleets. The modern Astraeus is a capable and versatile escort frigate: fast and reasonably shielded, fitting array of offensive and defensive turrets, and even possessing limited launch facilities for a handful of escort fighters. \n\nThough it lacks any forward-firing main armament, the unconventional shape of the hull and ample turret hardpoints allows the Astraeus to maintain superb fields of fire all around itself, and it is often seen operating ahead or within formations of larger capital ships on anti-fighter picket duty.</t>
	<t id="811">The life force of OTAS and long overshadowed, the Mistral is without a doubt the most important ship in the OTAS fleet. Following The Shutdown and takeover of the local Argon sectors large numbers of Mistrals would be seen transporting vast quantities of supplies across the new OTAS Exclusion Zone.</t>
	<t id="812">Developed in total secrecy pre-Shutdown and unleashed during the OTAS hostile seizure of the local Argon sectors, the Tempest is an extremely formidable battleship even by modern standards. The design saw continual updates, improvements, and iterations during the Great Dark to maintain its ability to engage entire fleets with minimal support, and it is one of the few deployment platforms for the OTAS Firestorm Artillery batteries. \n\nRumors abound that the ship makes use of highly illegal and dangerous AGI technology, though this has never been firmly proven despite intense scrutiny from both Commonwealth rivals and the Terran Protectorate.</t>
	<t id="813">Following their reconnection to the Commonwealth, OTAS quickly identified the immediate requirement for a new and modern construction ship in order for them to be able to expand outward and compete with the other powers. \n\nStolen in the same attack as many other Argon industrial ships, the Vesuvius is a near exact copy of the Mammoth; OTAS having seen little need to spend time and credits to further refine a humble construction vessel.</t>
	<t id="814">Another design stolen from the Federation following OTAS's reconnection, the Genthus is a twin to the Nomad but with several unseen upgrades and improvements. Previously, OTAS had no need for long range or large scale fleet resupplying given their total control on their cluster of systems. Born more out of necessity than ambition, the Genthus is expected to fulfill its role admirably.</t>	
	<t id="815">Despite what the Federation has publicly stated,the Andaman's existence is proof that the rumors of OTAS successfully stealing ship designs was true. A heavily modified and arguably improved variant of the Colossus, OTAS quickly tasked their engineers with "resolving" the issues which they believed Federation engineers were incapable of correcting. Now flaunted openly as if to intentionally incite a hostile response, the Andaman has become a powerful addition to the OTAS fleet.</t>
	<!--iSHIELDS-->
<!--<t id="900"></t>-->		
	<!--STATIONS-->
	<t id="1101">OTAS Defence Set</t>		
	<t id="1110">{20102,1051} Trading Station</t>
	<t id="1111">OTAS Trading Station Set</t>	
	<t id="1120">{20102,1061} Equipment Dock</t>
	<t id="1121">OTAS Equipment Dock Set</t>		
	<t id="1130">{20102,1071} Shipyard</t>
	<t id="1131">OTAS Shipyard Set</t>		
	<t id="1140">{20102,1081} Wharf</t>		
  </page>		
		
  <page id="19530003" title="Titles" descr="Titles" voice="no">
	<t id="1">System Analyst</t>	
	<t id="2">Reclamation</t>				
  </page>		
  <page id="19530004" title="Ships" descr="Ships" voice="yes">
	<t id="1">A variant configuration of the ubiquitous P, the Y is a heavy bomber fitted with twin torpedo launch tubes capable of deploying the same devastating anti-capital torpedoes of the smaller LX bomber.</t>
	<t id="2">IG M - Y Internal Generator</t>	
	<t id="3">(old) ----  {20403,25}{20403,24}</t>
	<t id="4">The D is an alternative configuration of the standard P hull. Featuring two additional turrets and reinforced hull plating, the prevailing theory is that the D is intended to bolster Xenon anti-fighter capabilities.</t>
	<t id="5">IG M - D Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="6">{20403,9}{20403,24}</t>
	<t id="7">An even more dangerous configuration of the Xenon I, the IX possesses a host of enhancements- an expanded array of main battery turrets, overcharged internal generator, and heavily reinforced hull structure. Thankfully, the ships are a rare sight outside of deeply occupied Xenon sectors and do not appear to be a standard combat configuration used in offensive actions, possibly due to the vast amount of resources required to produce one. All confirmed encounters with the type follow the same pattern: a fleet conducting offensive operations against the Xenon gains the upper hand, pushing deep into Xenon territory. When victory against the local branch matrix seems to be at hand, the situation shifts with the sudden appearance of an IX that swiftly swings the balance of power. \n\nMuch of what is known about the IX is sourced from encounters by the Terran Intervention Corps, with the Terran government being uncharacteristically open and cooperative in sharing intelligence regarding the type. Military analysts have attached the "Reclamation" title to these vessels, concluding that they are a reactive, last-ditch attempt by the Xenon to secure certain "core" sectors under threat, by dedicating all remaining available resources to their production in hopes of re-establishing the local presence once the sector is cleared of hostiles. As the ships have been observed seemingly appearing from nowhere even after the destruction of local Xenon shipbuilding facilities, it is theorized that they are assembled under asteroid cover or heavy sensor jamming fields, utilizing the same in-situ bootstrapped self-assembly technology that has been observed in the construction of Xenon stations.</t>	
	<t id="8">IG XL - IX Internal Generator</t>	
	<t id="8">{20403,12}{20403,24} (LX)</t>	
  </page>
  <!--<page id="19530005" title="N/A" descr="N/A" voice="no"/>-->
  <page id="19530006" title="Weapons" descr="Weapons" voice="no">
	<t id="1">\033#993d7bff#MH\033X Xenon Plasma Bomb</t>
	<t id="2">The Plasma Bomb is a weapon designed to penetrate the shield of a heavier ship to disable its engines and weaponry, or deal direct hull damage. </t>			
  </page>
  
			<!--Reemergence Assets-->
  <page id="19530007" title="Ships" descr="Ships" voice="yes">
	<!--TURRETS/WEAPONS-->
	<t id="200">\033#95e03b29#BMB\033X\ Light Plasma Bomb</t>  
	<t id="201">\033#95e03b29#LM\033X Extended Range PPC</t>
	<t id="202">Target Ranging and Tracking Designator - 22km</t>	
	<t id="203">Target Ranging and Tracking Designator - 30km</t>
	<t id="204">Kitsune Heavy Missile Launcher</t>	
	
	<!--TURRETS/WEAPONS DESCRIPTIONS-->
	<t id="300">Size: SMALL\n Weapon Class: BOMBER\n\nThe Light Plasma Bomb is a standardized, near-universally compatible weapon intended to be fitted to the heavy ordnance hardpoint found on bomber-type attack craft.\n\nA derivative offshoot of the ubiquitous Plasma Cannon technology, the weapon fires a highly unstable ionized plasma mixture held within a transient containment field. Upon impact the projectile loses containment and produces a high-energy flare, causing significant damage to anything unlucky enough to be caught within the sizable blast radius. Though very destructive, the projectiles have an extremely poor velocity and effective range due to containment bleed-off, making the weapon largely ineffective when deployed against anything other than its intended capital-class targets.</t>	
	<t id="301">Size: LARGE\n\nThis modified version of the standard Argon-built Photon Pulse Cannon was developed specifically for use as the primary armament of the Boron Marlin frigate. \n\nThough it uses the same underlying operating principles as the Argon progenitor, the Boron version of the PPC has been re-engineered to fit Boron power architecture and tactical sensibilities, boasting greater engagement distance at the cost of limited gimbal range and incompatibility with non-Boron ship systems.</t> 
	<t id="302">This piece of equipment is used to assist Viper missile frigate captains in maintaining proper distance from their intended targets. \n\nWhile manually operated rangefinding and targeting devices are a primitive solution dating back to pre-spaceflight era, their adoption has been highly effective in curtailing Split captains' tendency to grow bored in their standoff fire support role and demanding that their ship "close with the enemy, so that they may strike them with their blade", by giving them something to do. The additional benefits of slightly reduced target acquisition times and marginally improved terminal guidance are seen as welcome but ultimately unnecessary side effects. </t>	
	<t id="303">A sophisticated target acquisition and tracking suite utilizing a human-in-the-loop advanced long-range recognition system, initially designed for the Kitsune. \n\nThough the early trial versions of the system were fully automated and demonstrated excellent performance, battlefield experience revealed that in the heat of combat, the inability of the crew to directly influence the ship's armament produced a variety of psychological effects that manifested in poor tactical judgement and significantly impaired combat efficiency. By reintroducing the human factor at several critical points of the target engagement process, these issues were eliminated and overall combat effectiveness saw an notable improvement, even in low-pressure trial scenarios.</t>
	<t id="304">The integrated missile launch system designed for the Kitsune, capable of firing Agile and Shield-bypass cruise missiles to ranges of up to 30km.</t>

	<!--VRO description overrides-->
	<t id="400">Properties: Cruise missile | Guided | Swarm | Target-seeking \nAI Launch Range: 24 km \n\nDeveloped specifically for use with Viper's multi-tube launchers, this light cruise missile can deal with most light and medium targets and still be effective versus larger ships. </t>	
	<t id="401">Properties: Cruise missile | Guided | Target-seeking \nAI Launch Range: 32 km \n\nThis cruise missile, launched exclusively by Kitsune missile frigate, is remarkably fast for it's size and payload.</t>
	<t id="402">Properties: Cruise missile | Guided | Target-seeking \nAI Launch Range: 32 km \n\nA heavy cruise missile exclusive to the Kitsune missile frigate. The Shield-Bypass Cruise Missile is more sluggish and possesses a less destructive payload than the Agile, but the advanced dual-action warhead allows the weapon to inflict heavy damage against a target with active shields.</t>
	
	<!--SHIPS-->
	  <!-- L carriers -->
	<t id="700">Cheetah</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="701">(Chiba E){20101,62901} {20111,5462}</t>	
	<t id="702">Ariadne</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="703">(Griffon){20101,12201}</t>
	<t id="704">(Shrike E){20101,21701} {20111,5462}</t>
	<t id="705">LEAVE EMPTY (boron spot)</t>
	  <!-- S bombers -->
	<t id="710">Wolf</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="711">(Falchion){20101,61901}</t>
	<t id="722">PAR placeholder</t>
	<t id="713">(Buster){20101,10201}</t>
	<t id="714">Hawk</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="715">(Candiru){20101,52801}</t>	  
	  <!-- frigates -->
	<t id="720">(Marlin){20101,51701}</t>
	<t id="721">Caracal</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="722">Serval</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="723">(Cassowary){20101,22801}</t>
	<t id="724">Adder</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	  <!-- TMs -->
	<t id="730">Crocodile</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="731">(Scabbard){20101,63301}</t>
	<t id="732">(Helianthus){20101,120901}</t>
	<t id="733">Orthrus</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="734">Jacana</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="735">(Pleco){20101,51501}</t>
	  <!-- others / misc -->
	<t id="740">BOR BELUGA placeholder</t>
	<t id="741">ALI ARAN placeholder</t>
	<t id="742">(Kagawa){20101,64701}</t>
	<t id="743">(Pata){20101,64201}</t>
	<t id="744">Bulwark</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="745">(Douala){20101,81001}</t>	
	  <!-- M corvettes -->
	<t id="750">(Centaur){20101,12801}</t>
	  <!-- TPs -->
	<t id="760">Express</t>
	  
	<!--SHIP DESCRIPTIONS-->
	  <!-- L carriers -->
	<t id="800">A new development and seldom seen outside of Split space, the Cheetah is a light carrier ostensibly built in a bout of cooperation among the Split Free Families as a more specifically tailored version of the Split Panther. However, observers have noted that the Cheetah's unique capabilities are oddly well-suited to the lightning-fast ambush raids carried out by Fallen Families raiders, and the ship is just as commonly seen wearing Fallen Families colors as it is in Free Families livery, leading to a widely-accepted theory that the ship was in fact built to the specifications of an influential Fallen Families warband. \n\nRegardless of the truth of its origins, the Cheetah itself is an extremely capable raider - boasting an exceptionally high top speed along with an L-class turret hardpoint, a very large fighter capacity, and numerous launch tubes to rapidly surprise and overwhelm a target with fighters. However it is much less capable than its peers when it comes under direct threat, having poor shielding and only a small number of M-class defensive turrets. In addition, the Cheetah is fitted with relatively few landing pads, making it slow to recover its fighter complement. Alongside its limited capacity for self-defense against peer targets, this means that Cheetah captains must remain mindful of not only their attack vectors, but also be constantly planning an exit strategy should the tides of battle turn against them.</t>	
	<t id="801">The Chiba E is the Terran refinement of the Pioneers' original converted design. In a rare display of technological acknowledgement, the Terran Protectorate purchased access to the Chiba's design specifications and soon placed an improved version into service. While the design heritage of the Hokkaido hull remains clearly evident, the Chiba E is built to purpose from the keel up; featuring numerous internal modifications and improvements including expanded fighter-handling facilities and dedicated launch tubes, the ship has greatly improved performance in the light carrier role. \n\nIdentical in function to the original, the Chiba E is commonly seen patrolling Terran space, serving as a a base for local policing efforts or as small task force leaders.</t>	
	<t id="802">Ariadne</t>
	<t id="803">Griffon</t>
	<t id="804">Shrike E placeholder</t>
	<t id="805">LEAVE EMPTY (boron spot)</t>
	  <!-- S bombers -->
	<t id="810">The Split Wolf bomber is one of the largest and deadliest S-class combat ships, surpassing even the powerful Chimera. Developed with the assistance of OTAS engineers under a diplomatic effort to cooperate against their enemy, the Argon Federation, the Wolf makes use of technologies first pioneered for the OTAS Notus bomber, adapted for the generally lower Commonwealth technology base. Though relatively slow and a large target, the Wolf has a powerful arsenal of weapons fitted to a heavily reinforced hull, and in numbers presents a formidable threat to capital-class targets of any size. \n\nWith the Wolf demonstrating an integration of OTAS and Commonwealth engineering, the technology soon spread through the Gate Network, with other powers fielding their own bomber-type vessels.</t>
	<t id="811">The Terran Falchion bomber is perhaps the most heavily specialized ship in the class. While broadly identical in strategic function as the Notus and other Commonwealth counterparts, the Falchion does not use any version of the Notus' technology, and was developed and built completely from scratch by Terran engineers. \n\nUnlike other bombers, the Falchion carries no secondary armament to accompany the ordnance hardpoints, and is largely reliant on fighter escorts to clear the battlespace. In exchange, the ship presents a very small target profile and possesses robust shielding, maximizing its survivability against its capital sized targets. </t>
	<t id="822">PAR placeholder</t>
	<t id="813">Designed, built, and put into service with staggering and uncharacteristic alacrity by the Argon Federation Navy, the Buster is the result of Argon efforts to swiftly close the capabilities gap posed by the OTAS Notus and Split Wolf bombers. \n\nUnlike many of its peers, the Buster as a combat machine is wholly unremarkable: lacking the configurable multi-missile launchers found on the Notus, backing up it's single bomber-class hardpoint with a pair of conventional light weapons mounts and featuring a singular shield projector, the ship trades individual power for expedience in service and an exceptionally low production cost.\n\nThanks to the Argon Navy's numerous external threats and competing priorities, it has thus far maintained that "the ship you have now is better than a ship you might have next year" and the Buster has remained in service with no replacement in sight despite its various shortcomings, much to the annoyance of its pilots. Many common jokes within Argon Buster squadrons pointedly highlight the attractiveness of the ship's low cost of production and operation to the Argon civilian government, laced with macabre punchlines wondering how many Busters must be destroyed before it becomes economically advantageous to develop an improved ship. However, this same affordability has resulted in the Buster finding a surprisingly successful market among small independent mercenary outfits or private security firms, where the ship represents a very cheap opportunity to augment marketable capabilities.</t>
	<t id="814">Hawk</t> 
	<t id="815">BOR placeholder</t>	  
	  <!-- frigates -->
	<t id="820">A cooperative effort between Boron and Argon engineers, the Marlin is a frigate built with lessons learned from encounters with Split and Xenon forces following the reconnection of Boron space to the wider Commonwealth. Having identified a need for heavier anti-capital firepower than that provided by the larger Ray, the Marlin is designed with a unique (among Boron vessels) primary weapon hardpoint capable of mounting the powerful Argon Photon Pulse Cannon. Coupled with its small size and reduced price compared to a full destroyer, a squadron of Marlins can match the firepower of much larger vessels and overwhelm otherwise superior foes while maintaining cost parity.\n\nBased on a heavily redesigned version of their previous Sturgeon hull, the Marlin represents a surprising breakthrough success for the nascent Stellar Shores Shipping company, providing their first foothold in the highly competitive military procurement market and placing them solidly in line with their older, more established corporate peers.</t>
	<t id="821">Caracal</t>
	<t id="822">Serval</t>
	<t id="823">One of the more unusual ships produced by the Teladi Company, the Cassowary frigate is something of an engineering and marketing oddity. Abruptly released to the market with little fanfare shortly after the launch of the Heron E, critical observers have noted the ship's resemblance to a truncated forward dome section of the larger Heron freighter. The Teladi Company has vehemently denied allegations that the Cassowary is simply a repurposed Heron hull section that suffered structural failure during construction, with one Teladi Company spokesperson being quoted as saying that "The front section did not 'fall off' of anything! If anything, the Cassowary IS the front!". The Teladi Company has since distanced itself from the quoted official and has not acknowledged any requests for clarification.\n\nUnusual appearance notwithstanding, the Cassowary is an uncharacteristically well-armed offering in the Teladi catalogue. Boasting no less than three large turret hardpoints and protected by two large shield projectors, the ship is a superlative standout in the frigate class, though it is notably lacking in point-defense armament compared to its peers and suffers from a significant aft blindspot due to the unique hull layout.</t>
	<t id="824">Faced with the ever-increasingly irritating task of policing Free Families colonial space against progressively more creative threats cooked up by Fallen Families warbands, Zyarth forces found themselves in need of a more powerful rapid response and escort vessel than the ubiquitous Cobras and Dragons that ordinarily formed the backbone of colonial police forces. Initial plans to employ the Rattlesnake in this role were met with great enthusiasm from Split captains, but were denied due to the perceived expense of "wasting" a frontline combat vessel on police duty. Unexpectedly, it was Family Kritt which approached the Patriarch with a new design to fulfill the role - the Adder frigate. \n\nMounting a large and conspicuous turret battery primarily consisting of anti-fighter weaponry, the Adder is an impressively optimized design - visually impressive, fast, well-armed, and most importantly, much cheaper to manufacture than the Rattlesnake. Among its peers, the Adder boasts a massive array of medium turrets matched with a characteristically strong Split-built hull and powerful engines, providing Zyarth colonial police with a robust fleet leader when engaging ships such as the Free Families Cheetah. The ship has also become a common sight in Split frontline formations, where its high speed and powerful screening armament provides an excellent complement to the immense raw firepower of the Rattlesnake, allowing Split forces to continue to operate even with heavy enemy fighter presence.</t>
	  <!-- TMs -->
	<t id="830">A class of ship that fell out of favour during the Shutdown-Era, TM-class Military Transports serve dual roles as well-defended couriers of sensitive cargo and as cost-effective solutions for low-intensity patrol and police duties.\n\nThough they were largely unneeded during the isolation of the Gate Shutdown, the class was reintroduced following the Reconnection to alleviate the increased pressure placed on military forces by the rise in inter-faction tensions and Xenon activity, replacing frontline-capable combat units in second-line roles. Traditionally built on a modified civilian transport hull, TM-class vessels sacrifice a large portion of their cargo capacity in exchange for handling and servicing equipment to support a small wing of fighters. Rather than traditional docking pads, TMs are fitted with short range graviton tractor beam arrays to hold docked fighters in place, using a standard service umbilical to transfer crew between vessels rather than maintaining an "open-space" atmospheric envelope. Though this allows TMs to carry a large number of parasite fighters for their size, the lack of internal storage bays means that the externally-docked fighters are vulnerable to damage and the ship can only realistically support as many fighters as it can dock. \n\nThe Split-built Crocodile is one of the smallest ships in the class, though it still manages to land a wing of four heavy fighters and features the aggressive speed common to Split designs.</t>
	<t id="831">TM</t>
	<t id="832">A class of ship that fell out of favour during the Shutdown-Era, TM-class Military Transports serve dual roles as well-defended couriers of sensitive cargo and as cost-effective solutions for low-intensity patrol and police duties.\n\nThough they were largely unneeded during the isolation of the Gate Shutdown, the class was reintroduced following the Reconnection to alleviate the increased pressure placed on military forces by the rise in inter-faction tensions and Xenon activity, replacing frontline-capable combat units in second-line roles. Traditionally built on a modified civilian transport hull, TM-class vessels sacrifice a large portion of their cargo capacity in exchange for handling and servicing equipment to support a small wing of fighters. Rather than traditional docking pads, TMs are fitted with short range graviton tractor beam arrays to hold docked fighters in place, using a standard service umbilical to transfer crew between vessels rather than maintaining an "open-space" atmospheric envelope. Though this allows TMs to carry a large number of parasite fighters for their size, the lack of internal storage bays means that the externally-docked fighters are vulnerable to damage and the ship can only realistically support as many fighters as it can dock. \n\nThe Paranid Helianthus is a fairly minimal modification of the Demeter, simply extending the chassis and replacing many of the outer-hull storage units with an array of micro-tractor emitters. Though lightly armed, like its transporter ancestor the Helianthus boasts improved shielding and excellent mobility.</t>
	<t id="833">A class of ship that fell out of favour during the Shutdown-Era, TM-class Military Transports serve dual roles as well-defended couriers of sensitive cargo and as cost-effective solutions for low-intensity patrol and police duties.\n\nThough they were largely unneeded during the isolation of the Gate Shutdown, the class was reintroduced following the Reconnection to alleviate the increased pressure placed on military forces by the rise in inter-faction tensions and Xenon activity, replacing frontline-capable combat units in second-line roles. Traditionally built on a modified civilian transport hull, TM-class vessels sacrifice a large portion of their cargo capacity in exchange for handling and servicing equipment to support a small wing of fighters. Rather than traditional docking pads, TMs are fitted with short range graviton tractor beam arrays to hold docked fighters in place, using a standard service umbilical to transfer crew between vessels rather than maintaining an "open-space" atmospheric envelope. Though this allows TMs to carry a large number of parasite fighters for their size, the lack of internal storage bays means that the externally-docked fighters are vulnerable to damage and the ship can only realistically support as many fighters as it can dock. \n\nThe Argon Orthrus is in many ways the archetypical example of the class, with average shielding and mobility backed up by a pair of M-class turrets for self defense, supporting a wing of four fighters.</t>
	<t id="834">A class of ship that fell out of favour during the Shutdown-Era, TM-class Military Transports serve dual roles as well-defended couriers of sensitive cargo and as cost-effective solutions for low-intensity patrol and police duties.\n\nThough they were largely unneeded during the isolation of the Gate Shutdown, the class was reintroduced following the Reconnection to alleviate the increased pressure placed on military forces by the rise in inter-faction tensions and Xenon activity, replacing frontline-capable combat units in second-line roles. Traditionally built on a modified civilian transport hull, TM-class vessels sacrifice a large portion of their cargo capacity in exchange for handling and servicing equipment to support a small wing of fighters. Rather than traditional docking pads, TMs are fitted with short range graviton tractor beam arrays to hold docked fighters in place, using a standard service umbilical to transfer crew between vessels rather than maintaining an "open-space" atmospheric envelope. Though this allows TMs to carry a large number of parasite fighters for their size, the lack of internal storage bays means that the externally-docked fighters are vulnerable to damage and the ship can only realistically support as many fighters as it can dock. \n\nThe Teladi Jacana boasts above-average shielding, hull integrity and cargo capacity, though it possesses the typically below-average mobility and poor armament found on civilian Teladi designs.</t>
	<t id="835">A class of ship that fell out of favour during the Shutdown-Era, TM-class Military Transports serve dual roles as well-defended couriers of sensitive cargo and as cost-effective solutions for low-intensity patrol and police duties.\n\nThough they were largely unneeded during the isolation of the Gate Shutdown, the class was reintroduced following the Reconnection to alleviate the increased pressure placed on military forces by the rise in inter-faction tensions and Xenon activity, replacing frontline-capable combat units in second-line roles. Traditionally built on a modified civilian transport hull, TM-class vessels sacrifice a large portion of their cargo capacity in exchange for handling and servicing equipment to support a small wing of fighters. Rather than traditional docking pads, TMs are fitted with short range graviton tractor beam arrays to hold docked fighters in place, using a standard service umbilical to transfer crew between vessels rather than maintaining an "open-space" atmospheric envelope. Though this allows TMs to carry a large number of parasite fighters for their size, the lack of internal storage bays means that the externally-docked fighters are vulnerable to damage and the ship can only realistically support as many fighters as it can dock. \n\nFurther building on the success of the Dolphin transporter, the Pleco is a result of a joint effort between Atreus Shipbuilding Currents and Stellar Shores Shipping to develop a mid-size TM-type vessel. Though using the same grav-harness docking technology as most TMs, the unique hull form and docking arrangement of the Pleco allows it to carry no less than six parasite fighters, giving it a distinct edge in offensive capabilities compared to its peers, despite its poor speed. Coupled with the characteristically sturdy Boron shielding, the Pleco makes for a far more dangerous opponent than its spindly appearance and unassuming name might suggest.</t>
	  <!-- others / misc -->
	<t id="840">BOR BELUGA placeholder</t>
	<t id="841">ARAN placeholder</t>
	<t id="842">One of the largest ships found in Terran space, the Pioneer-built Kagawa is a freighter vessel of truly mammoth proportions. Rivaling the Terran Asgard battleship in sheer size and mass, the Kagawa features one of the largest cargo-handling capacities found anywhere in the Gate Network.\n\nFollowing the reconnection of the Althes and Megnir jumpgates, and the ensuing massive military and humanitarian efforts to secure those sectors against Xenon assault, the engineers of the Pioneer Initiative were tasked with preparing an ultraheavy transport vessel capable of ferrying enormous amounts of humanitarian supplies or necessary war materiel that might be needed if a route was discovered to the final lost colony of Aldrin. The advent of Project Genesis terraforming efforts expedited development of the Kagawa, with the sheer scale of resources demanded by the terraforming process promising a steady demand for such large transports.</t>	
	<t id="843">A ship with a legacy dating to the early years of the Pioneer Initiative, the Pata was born from the Pioneers' need to carefully shepherd all available resources. Derived from the core of the Bolo miner, the Pata is fitted with a larger engine array and a trio of tractor beam projector turrets that allowed the early Pioneers to first clear large debris fields to make navigation safer, and later to recover useful debris and wreckage for salvage and reprocessing. \n\nThough the faction is no longer as desperately strapped for resources, the conservationist spirit has persisted in the form of more organized salvage operations utilizing purpose-built Patas which constitute a small but culturally important segment of the economy, and the ship's highly distinctive silhouette can be spotted throughout Pioneer space and the bordering regions.</t>
	<t id="844">The Pioneer-built Bulwark is a highly specialized ship for a very specific purpose. Designed to provide small-scale logistics and repair support for stranded civilian vessels and damaged satellite networks, the Bulwark is fitted with a scaled-up version of the standard space suit repair beam and features a unique storage bay to carry a number of disassembled and flat-packed repair drones, though the ship cannot deploy them for usage by itself. In concert with an onboard engineering module capable of assembling or disassembling repair drones in-situ for transfer to a larger ship, the ship's small size belies its remarkable drone carrying capacity, allowing a single Bulwark to effectively get stranded or damaged ships back under way.</t>
	<t id="845">Developed and employed by the Riptide Rakers as a stopgap measure to assist large ships which were crippled by the Tide but could be saved, the Douala is a small and simple utility vessel suitable for use the confined space around Tidebreak station. A minimalist design intended to only be deployed over short distances in the hectic periods between Tides, the Douala is sluggish, lightly shielded, and completely unarmed save for a single repair beam. The ship's primary defining feature is a set of bulky storage units capable of housing a small handful of repair drones for transfer to a larger ship, as the Douala lacks the size or facilities to deploy them itself.</t>
	  <!-- M corvettes -->
	<t id="850">As the first highly-anticipated combat-line product launched by the post-shutdown reconsolidated Jonferson Space Dynamics Division, the Mk3 Centaur is a dramatic return to the ship's roots as a fast, aggressive corvette-class striker. Designed in a bid to produce a ship capable of matching or exceeding the capabilities of the venerable Terran Katana, the ship boasts a formidable array of forward weaponry, good all-around turret coverage and fighter-like agility, though this comes at the cost of a light-duty hull structure and somewhat mediocre overall protection. \n\nWith the newly-reformed company holding a tenuous financial position, it was a deliberate decision by Jonferco designers to recall the classic Argon design in a bid for a knockout market entrance. Though the Centaur fell somewhat short of the impossibly lofty expectations set upon it by Jonferco executive leadership, the ship proved a commercial and military success, being well liked by its users and earning a particular popularity with the semi-independent Special Action Task Forces of the Argon and Antigone navies.</t>	
	  <!-- TPs -->
	<t id="860">Express</t>
	
	<!--iSHIELDS-->
	  <!-- L carriers -->
	<t id="900">IG L - Cheetah Internal Generator</t>	
	<t id="901">IG L - Chiba E Internal Generator</t>	
	<t id="902">IG L - Ariadne Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="903">IG L - Griffon Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="904">IG L - LEAVE EMPTY (teladi spot, using existing VRO iShield)</t>
	<t id="905">IG L - LEAVE EMPTY (boron spot)</t>
	  <!-- S bombers -->
	<t id="910">IG S - Wolf Internal Shield Generator</t>
	<t id="911">IG S - Falchion Internal Shield Generator</t>
	<t id="922">IG S - PAR placeholder Internal Shield Generator</t>
	<t id="913">IG S - Buster Internal Shield Generator</t>
	<t id="914">IG S - Hawk Internal Shield Generator</t> 
	<t id="915">IG S - BOR placeholder Internal Shield Generator</t>	  
	  <!-- frigates -->
	<t id="920">IG L - Marlin Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="921">IG L - Caracal Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="922">IG L - Serval Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="923">IG L - Cassowary Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="924">IG L - Adder Internal Generator</t>	
	  <!-- TMs -->
	<t id="930">IG M - TM Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="931">IG M - TM Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="932">IG M - TM Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="933">IG M - TM Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="934">IG M - TM Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="935">IG M - TM Internal Generator</t>
	  <!-- others / misc -->
	<t id="940">IG XL - Beluga Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="941">IG XL - Aran Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="942">IG XL - Kagawa Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="943">IG M - Pata Internal Generator</t>	
	<t id="944">IG S - Bulwark Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="945">IG S - Douala Internal Generator</t>	
	  <!-- M corvettes -->
	<t id="950">IG M - Centaur Internal Shield Generator</t>

	<!--STATIONS-->
    <t id="1000">Haven</t>
    <t id="1001">{20006,102}(No information available)</t>	
    <t id="1002">(Yaki S Haven){20203,2801} {20111,5011} {19530007,1000}</t>
    <t id="1003">(Yaki M Haven){20203,2801} {20111,5021} {19530007,1000}</t>
    <t id="1004">(Yaki L Haven){20203,2801} {20111,5031} {19530007,1000}</t>
    <t id="1005">Den</t>	
    <t id="1006">(Scaleplate S Den){20203,1001} {20111,5011} {19530007,1005}</t>
    <t id="1007">(Scaleplate M Den){20203,1001} {20111,5021} {19530007,1005}</t>
    <t id="1008">(Scaleplate L Den){20203,1001} {20111,5031} {19530007,1005}</t>	
	<t id="1100">{20102,1041} Defence Platform</t>		

	<!--MISC-->
	<t id="1100">{20111,5302} {20101,100401}(Standard Defence Drone)</t>
	<t id="11001">The product of a joint Argon-Teladi venture to produce a new generation of cheap defence drone following the Gate Reconnection, the Universal Standard-Armaments Semi-Autonomous Fighter Drone - more commonly referred to as the Commonwealth Standard defence drone, or simply the Standard - is a massive commercial and military success that can be found both in service and available for sale throughout every corner of settled space. \n\nThough the design has begun to significantly show its age in the modern battlespace and brings very little in the way of individual combat power, decades of design maturation and manufacturing refinements have driven the cost of the Standard down to practically nothing, letting even the most cash-strapped freighter captain freely deploy them in bulk as disposable countermeasures against pirate attack. This has ensured the continued popularity of the Standard despite its perceived obsolescence in frontline military use.</t>	
	<t id="1101">{20202,601} {20101,100401}(Xenon Defence Drone)</t>
	<t id="11011">Little is known about the Xenon defence drone beyond the proven fact that it is tactically superior to any of its counterparts. Beyond being larger, more robust and having better armament, Xenon AGI systems also ensure the drone is smarter and meaner than any other drone system. A swarm of Xenon drones can swiftly bring down an underprepared foe of any size and present a formidable obstacle when contesting battlespace control of Xenon-occupied systems.</t>	
	<t id="1102">Keris Defence Drone(Terran)</t>
	<t id="11021">The modern incarnation of Terran Keris defence drone is a powerful and advanced semiautomonous weapons system. Though somewhat slower than its Commonwealth counterparts, the Keris presents a reduced target profile and possesses superior armament in the form of a standard Terran Pulse Cannon.</t>	
	<t id="1103">Krill Defence Drone(Boron)</t>
	<t id="11031">Designed in a bid to reduce casualty risk to fighter pilots, the Krill defense drone is a very agile drone armed with a single Ion Gatling. \n\nAccording to Boron fleet doctrine, correct usage of the Krill drone in a coordinated fleet action sees it deployed in large numbers alongside manned fighters, using its physical presence to distract enemy fire and the engine-disrupting properties of the Ion Gatling to pull apart enemy formations, thus allowing crewed fighters to deliver decisive tactical strikes in relative safety. </t>	
	<t id="1104">Skink Defence Drone(Split)</t>
	<t id="11041">A highly conventional application of Split combat philosophy, the Split-designed Skink defence drone is extremely fast and mounts a deadly Tau Accelerator as the main weapon system, giving it an unexpected edge in combat when facing larger targets.</t>	
	<t id="1105">Cupid Defence Drone(Paranid)</t>
	<t id="11051">As much a product of cultural dogma as one of military necessity, the Paranid Cupid defence drone was initially designed by the Holy Order to both provide their forces with a combat advantage and to free their captains from the perceived shame of relying on the heretical Standard drone. The Holy Order enjoyed a brief period of drone superiority before the design was acquired by the Godrealm, which swiftly adopted the system and began to field their own copy. \n\nArmed with a scaled-down version of the Paranid Railgun system, the Cupid gives Paranid forces a unique form of offensive support.</t>
	<t id="1106">Sparrow Defence Drone(Teladi)</t>
	<t id="11061">DESCRIPTION KEYWORDS: RUGGED, SURVIVABLE, ONLY ARMED WITH Impulse Ray Emitter, BUT WELL SHIELDED</t>
	<t id="1107">{20111,5302} {20101,100401} mk2(Argon)</t>
	<t id="11071">DESCRIPTION KEYWORDS: the II is Arg's bid to recreate the success but too little too late with factions having developed their own. ARMED WITH PAC, better speed and mobility</t>
  </page>		
</add>
	<!--VANILLA-->	
  <replace sel="/language/page[@id='20004']/t[@id='1080022']/text()[1]">Titan(same as {20004, 1080021}) is the largest of Saturn's(same as {20004, 1080011}) many moons. Contentious proposals to terraform Titan in order to make it habitable for humans, have been put forward several times, but to date the potential benefits have yet to be shown to outweigh the immense cost.\n\nUntil recently this sector was only connected to Saturn and not to any other part of the Sol system and it did not see as much traffic as many other areas. However, following a reconfiguration of the Sol network and the Accelerator being moved to the sector, Titan is now significantly more heavily traversed.</replace>	
	
  <replace sel="/language/page[@id='20221']/t[@id='3061']/text()[1]">Cruiser</replace>
  <replace sel="/language/page[@id='20221']/t[@id='3062']/text()[1]">Heavier than a Destroyer, ships of this class are far better better against capital ships and stations but are extremely vulnerable to smaller ships.</replace>
</diff>  
