<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<diff xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../xmllib/diff.xsd">
  <add sel="/language">
  <page id="19530001" title="Clusters" descr="Names\Descriptions" voice="yes">			
	<t id="1">Planet 9</t>
	<t id="2">Following reports of unknown vessels and sporadic disappearances in the outer Oort Cloud, the Protectorate reactivated the trans-orbital accelerator leading to the secretive "Planet 9" and established a sentry presence. Generally considered to be the edge of Terran-controlled Sol, Planet 9 is chiefly remarkable for being the sector where Beryll Syndicate operations in Terran space were finally cornered and hunted to extinction, and is officially home to little more than the occasional patrol or intrepid prospector. However, the increase in traffic accompanying the reactivation of the accelerator has led to an uptick in unknown vessel sightings, and rumours abound that the Protectorate is preparing a major military operation to establish a permanent presence and ensure that any survivors of the Beryll purge or whatever else may be lurking out in the dark are destroyed for good.</t>			
	<t id="3">McCallum Relay</t>
	<t id="4">Found on the very outer edges of the Oort Cloud beyond an accelerator pair that was built in an effort to explore the interstellar space, this sector is now home to a previously undetected Xenon Core Matrix. Believed to have originated from replicant-capable Xenon technology carried by Beryll survivors that fled beyond Planet 9, this sector has evidently never been disconnected from what is now known as Branch 9, displaying all the standard Xenon technologies and designs that are recognizable across the Gate Network. While it is unknown how they maintained contact during Sol's isolation from the Gate Network, the most commonly accepted theory postulates that the Beryll survivors possessed a partially-functioning Jump Beacon, which allowed the Xenon to maintain their Branch Connection for a time after disposing of their would-be Beryll captors. How these Xenon have survived so long without a reliable source of energy is a mystery, though this makes it highly vulnerable to inevitable extermination by Terran forces.</t>	
	<t id="5">{20101,31801}(Ares)</t>
	<t id="6">Established due to a change in Protectorate doctrine focused on increasing Sol's strategic depth and resilience, the Ares sector encompasses a resource-rich region created by the orbital degradation of Phobos and bolstered through active asteroid capture from the Asteroid Belt conducted by deepspace expeditions ranging well outside the established Asteroid Belt sector. Previously overlooked due to the richness of Asteroid Belt, the increasing pressure on that sector as the first line of defense against hostile incursion has led the Protectorate to seek alternative concentrations of raw resources in the event that access to Outer Sol is lost.</t>	
	<t id="7">{20101,31301}(Hermes)</t>
	<t id="8">Another resource extraction sector established following a shift in Protectorate defensive doctrine, the Hermes sector is much closer than the Mercury sector to the planet itself and contains a large silicon-rich debris field. This field is the result of a controversial program of capturing potentially hazardous near-Earth asteroids and trans-solar objects and directing them into close proximity with Mercury, where they are broken up by gravitational interaction with Sol and settle into a close orbit to the small planet.\n\nThe long-running program, first initiated to protect Earth from potential impactors, has drawn heavy and continuous criticism for the dangers that the debris field and transiting captured bodies pose to the crucial energy cell production facilities of the Mercury sector. Nonetheless, the Protectorate's insistence on maintaining the program has over time built up a massive quantity of raw material both in the regional space and fallen to the planet's surface, which now provides an important strategic reserve in the otherwise resource-poor Inner Sol region.</t>		
	<t id="9">Althes</t>
	<t id="10">One of the several Terran Lost Colonies, Althes once formed the gateway between Sol and her other colonies. Connected to Sol via a Terran-constructed gate in the Neptune sector, Althes provided further access to the other lost colonies of Megnir, Segaris, and eventually Aldrin. When the gates shut down, Althes remained connected to neighboring Megnir through one gate, while another realigned with a Xenon Core Matrix, plunging the two colonies into a bitter war for survival with the equally isolated Xenon Matrix. The reconnection of the gates brought little relief, as the isolated Matrix synchronized with the rest of Branch-9 and evolved far past its previous capabilities, forcing the beleaguered colonists to withdraw to Megnir or face complete destruction.</t>		
	<t id="11">Megnir</t>
	<t id="12">Another colony once thought to have been lost, the initial rediscovery of Megnir, followed by Segaris and Aldrin, were momentous occasions subsequently cut short by the Gate Shutdown. Remaining connected to neighbouring Althes, Megnir found itself fighting desperately against the Xenon advance alongside her sister colony during the Isolation. Though the brunt of the fighting was borne by Althes, Megnir supplied much of the men and materiel, with the two nominally independent colonies understanding that this was a do or die moment for all involved. It was thanks to Megnir's shipyard - initially built by the Sol government, heavily used during the Isolation, and decommissioned following induction into the Pioneers Initiative due to the immense amount of acculumated wear and tear - that the colonies were able to avoid total destruction after the loss of Althes.\n\nContact with the colony was restored when a Gate reopened and connected the two-colonies-turned-one to the third colony of Segaris, now under the flag of the Segaris Pioneers. Though Megnir was initially slated for absorption into the Protectorate itself, the Pioneers successfully made the case that the Colonies had stood together before, and deserved the right to stand together again. The continued defense of Megnir is now undertaken by the combined Pioneer forces with occasional assistance by the Terran Intervention Corps, and it is the hope of many among the system's inhabitants to someday reclaim Althes and rediscover Aldrin, making the colonies whole again.</t>		
	<t id="13">{20005,8001} {20005,8003}{20404,4}{20404,8}(Matrix #48)</t>
	<t id="14">Once connected to a major Xenon sector only identified as "Core 023", the Xenon of this sector were the scourge of the Lost Colonies during the Gate Shutdown. When the gate connections began to fail, the Xenon moved extensive assets into Matrix #48, apparently foreseeing the need for the Matrix to stand alone. \n\nRemaining connected to Althes and Megnir while isolated, the local Xenon fought a deadly and protracted conflict against the neighbouring Terran Colonies, making slow but steady progress against the desperate defenders. The reopening of the gates allowed Matrix 48 to resynchronize with the Branch-9 network, catapulting its technological evolution overnight and enabling it to completely force the Terran defenders out of Althes. Though stopped at the Megnir-Althes Gate by the spirited defense of the colonists and later pushed further back by the combined forces of the Pioneers and Terran Intervention Corps, Matrix #48 remains a persistent lurking threat and source of continuing concern for the Segaris Pioneers.</t>	
	<t id="15">{20005,8001} {20005,8003}{20404,7}{20404,9}{20403,1}(Matrix #79A)</t>
	<t id="16">Even more of an enigma than Matrix #79B, this sector is scattered with an even greater number of unknown factors than its counterpart. A probing expedition undertaken by the Alliance of the Word confirmed initial suspicions that even the local region itself is a total mystery, with astrometric studies confirming that the sector had never been encountered within the Network before. Studies of the unknown structures within Matrix #79A have revealed that they pre-date the ones found in Matrix #79B, but gave no insights to their origin or purpose.</t>
	<t id="17">{20005,1041}(Power Circle)</t>
	<t id="18">Sometime before the last Xenon conflict, the planet "Shipfall" was blown apart by a mysterious disaster of awesome magnitude. The event annihilated nearly all traces of what had previously been a thriving Argon industrial colony, with rescue and relief efforts heavily stymied by continuing aftershocks.\n\nEfforts to recolonize the sector were interrupted by the Gate Shutdown cutting off the fledgling colony from critical outside supplies, and the sector was found once again empty when the gates reopened. Devoid of inhabitants, the scattered wreckage and debris in the sector stand a silent vigil for the untold lives lost.</t>						
	<t id="19">{20005,1041} {20402,1}(Power Circle I)</t>
	<t id="20">As initial entry point to the region, Power Circle I was once home to numerous spaceborne installations of the original Power Circle colony, and served as a forward base and staging area for recolonization efforts. Now reconnected once again, the intrepid colonists of the Antigone Republic have eagerly set to the task of reclaiming and recolonizing the system.</t>			
	<t id="21">{20005,1041} {20402,3}(Power Circle III)</t>
	<t id="22">Before re-colonization efforts were brought to an abrupt end by the Shutdown, the Argon Federation went to great lengths to try and secure the success of the new colony. Immense effort was taken to relocate the Gate which once connected to Three Worlds, and a local superhighway was built to ease the transport of supplies arriving in Power Circle 1. Unfortunately it seems these efforts have gone largely to waste, as the colony has completely died out and the relocated Gate now connects to the enigmatic Xenon core sectors of Matrix #79A and #79B.</t>			
	<t id="23">Teladi Gain</t>
	<t id="24">The favoured retreat of Boron philosophers and visionaries, this sector came under Teladi management who swiftly reshaped it into a pleasure destination. The Bliss Place produced narcotic spaceweed - largely illegal outside of Teladi space - which drew in dreamers, artists, and neo-philosophers of all races. \n\nDuring the Shutdown the sector's priorities dramatically shifted and the various recreation facilities were quickly abandoned or turned to the necessary work of simple survival. Now reconnected, the Teladi have once again set about restoring the sector to its pre-Shutdown condition.</t>			
	<t id="25">Herron's Nebula</t>
	<t id="26">A mineral rich system made famous throughout Commonwealth space by its residents' vast consumption of Space Fuel and the semi-legal bootlegging which procured it, Herron's Nebula was once an important Argon core sector that supplied vast quantities of raw mineral goods for Federation industry.\n\nFollowing the Reconnection, Federation scouts were initially ecstatic to discover that the system still lay within the Argon sphere of influence, but this excitement was swiftly squashed as both the mining installations and distillery stations were found long-abandoned, with little evidence to be found regarding the fate of the sector's population.</t>			
	<t id="27">Tempting Fumes</t>
	<t id="28">A newly discovered sector in previously unknown space in the Argon-Teladi border regions, Tempting Fumes quickly developed a reputation as a pirate haven. Attempts to flush out the pirate presence invariably results in a resurgence of pirate activity in both Tempting Fumes itself and the neighboring sectors, much to the frustration of Federation authorities.\n\nCertain claims of Teladi involvement with the pirates have thus far remained unproven.</t>
	<t id="29">Split Fire</t>
	<t id="30">Split Fire was once a seedy frontier system that hosted much of the illicit black-market trading in the Network, with pirates and smugglers brokering all manner of illegal deals hidden from the eyes of the Commonwealth powers, often using the system's thriving industry of counterfeit Paranid jewelry as anonymous currency. \n\nThough these activities were slowed by rumors of Xenon activity, the black market continued operating in strength until the moment that the system's Gates went dark. Reports from Federation scouts indicate that the sector is now completely overrun with Xenon and that no evidence remains of organic life nor non-Xenon installations.</t>			
	<t id="31">Dark Waters</t>
	<t id="32">This system was rumoured to have a hidden gate leading to a top secret Boron military facility. Heavily policed, any potential threats were swiftly detained or destroyed despite the sector itself containing little more than trading outposts and minor mercantile facilities.\n\nAs the Shutdown progressed, the sector was completely evacuated to the neighboring Boron sectors.</t>		
	<t id="33">Mists of Elysium</t>
	<t id="34">The planet Elysium is described as a peaceful paradise world filled with lush plant life. Prior to the Shutdown a thick mist was known to fill the lowlands for half the planet's day, though this did not worry the Boron inhabitants sequestered in their deep-sea homes.\n\nUpon the sector's rediscovery, it was found that the mist phenomenon now extended to cover the seas as well, and that there were no Boron to be found anywhere on the planet.</t>			
	<t id="35">Depths of Silence</t>
	<t id="36">The heavily guarded secret of Dark Waters, Depths of Silence was formerly home to a massive scientific black site established by Royal Boron Military Defence to pioneer new technologies that could give the Boron people any advantage over their enemies. \n\nOnce filled with sprawling, high-tech complexes that investigated everything from creating advanced ion-hybrid weaponry to increasing the nutrient density of BoFu, the sector is now completely overrun by a Kha'ak infestation of unknown origin. What became of the heavy security force and the research they protected remains unknown.</t>			
	<t id="37">Light Water</t>
	<t id="38">Following the discovery of the North gate in Shore of Infinity, this sector was colonized by the Boron, who were well-suited to the unusual conditions of the water world which constitutes the system's only inhabitable planet. \n\nOnce home to a flourishing orbital food and energy industry that supplied other nearby sectors, the Gate Shutdown left the Boron residents in the odd position of having too much production of basic necessities. Lacking in heavy industry or significant technological manufacturing capacity needed to maintain the orbital facilities, the local Boron chose to abandon the spaceborne installations, salvaging as much material as they could before scuttling the stations and retreating deep into the planet's vast oceans.</t>			
	<t id="39">Shining Currents</t>
	<t id="40">Founded as a food production center to aid the continual growth of the Boron Queendom, the name comes from the reflection of the mercury ocean on the primary planet's moon. \n\nAs the gate Shutdown progressed, the Boron evacuated from Dark Waters took refuge in this sector, but neither they nor the original Boron presence seem to have survived.</t>				
	<t id="41">Shore of Infinity</t>
	<t id="42">In the pre-Shutdown network, Shore of Infinity served as a shining example of the warming in Paranid-Boron relations, with both species coexisting and cooperating through minor trade and technology exchanges.\n\nThis sector is home to one of the few Boron colonies that survived the Shutdown, albeit barely. However, the Paranid inhabitants are long gone to an uncertain fate - according to meticulous records kept by the local Boron archivist, these Paranid became increasingly unstable and erratic without the guiding influence of the Paranid religious leadership, culminating in a sudden and likely ill-destined mass exodus.</t>		
	<t id="43">Reservoir of Tranquility</t>
	<t id="44">Located near the giant star of Lehril, this system was once the crux of strategic power for the regional Boron presence. Bordering Split space and being a crossroads to the other nearby Boron colonies, control over the system was critical to maintain the flow of trade through the region and the Boron maintained a constant military fleet presence despite the lack of any permanent installations.\n\nUpon rediscovering the system, Alliance of the Word explorers found a few scattered Split wrecks and nothing else. Though carefully studied and salvaged for information, the wrecks held little to offer other than the radiation-faded markings of Split Family Rhy.</t>			
	<t id="45">Duke's Domain</t>
	<t id="46">A highly agriculturally developed system, Duke's Domain once provided huge amounts of the Soja Beans that form the basis of the Paranid diet. The highly ionised water of the system's planet contains rare organic minerals which greatly improved the flavour of beans nurtured with it, putting the agrarian output of the sector in high demand across all strata of Paranid society. \n\nDuke's Domain suffered particularly heavy losses in the previous Xenon conflict and experienced a near-total breakdown as the Shutdown progressed, with the local population struggling to cope both with their disconnection from Paranid leadership and the lack of heavy industry in the system, which made maintaining orbital installations an impossible task.</t>
	<t id="47">{20005,3038}(Perpetual Sin)</t>
	<t id="48">For a long time an insignificant system seeing only occasional Kha'ak skirmishes, it grew to being proof that those considered to be beyond redemption can be brought back onto the path. On the third day, of the third month, after having fallen into disgrace and being banished here, a Paranid scout managed to discover the location of a jumpgate leading to a then-unknown system. \n\nRegaining the respect of the Pontifex Maximus Paranidia, this scout was sent to explore the system but was never seen again. \n\nThe discovery of this active gate, in close proximity to the Second Duchy, was seen as further evidence that the Paranid Empire was destined for greatness and gave the sector itself some prestige.</t>			
	<t id="49">{20005,3038} {20402,1}(Perpetual Sin I)</t>
	<t id="50">Once the original location of the Southern gate leading to Duke's Citadel prior to being relocated by the Paranid. Perpetual Sin I was established to further study the gate of legend and prior to the shutdown Paranid scientists discovered yet another gate floating lifeless and in a decaying orbit at the very extreme edge of the solar system. While there are no indications of their success the trapped Paranid appear to have been making attempts to reactivate these gates.</t>
	<t id="51">{20005,3038} {20402,3}(Perpetual Sin III)</t>
	<t id="52">A refuge for the Paranid who wish to seek the same redemption as the fabled scout of old, Perpetual Sin III has been designated as the site of their ultimate potential salvation and is the only acceptable place for these banished Paranid to gather within the Holy Order without risk of being executed. \n\nAs has became tradition, on the third day, of the third month, of this third system; disgraced Paranid assemble to find either renewed purpose and redemption or further disgrace and damnation. Those who return to the holy path are given this singular chance and should they fail in their duties again will be executed on sight.</t>	
	<t id="53">Sanctum Verge</t>
	<t id="54">A newly discovered system, Sanctum Verge has been designated by the reclusive Pontifex of the Holy Order as a new holy site of the three-dimensionality on the cusp of prophetic wonder. \n\nWhile the ultimate goals of the mysterious Pontifex are unknown, observers have hypothesized that the sector is being heavily developed to support the frontline combat against the Godrealm in neighboring Pontifex's Claim. Other, less substantiated rumours abound that the Holy Order discovered something of immense value in the sector and are trying to hide the truth.</t>						
	<t id="55">Pontifex' Seclusion</t>
	<t id="56">The last sector to be occupied in the New Duchy Sectors, this sector was famed for its lack of hospitality and is said to be a destination of retreat for the Pontifex, should he need to leave the main sectors and be isolated for any reason. Once located deep within the Second Duchy at the end of a treacherous path teeming with pirate activity, the gate relignment has resulted in the sector being absorbed by the Holy Order of the Pontifex</t>			
	<t id="57">Unholy Descent</t>
	<t id="58">This sector lies in low orbit of the hostile planet Xhar'Bar, where the Xaarist priests accused early Paranid colonists of apostasy. \n\nEvidence suggests that hostile conditions on the planet claimed the lives of these colonists after being cut off from the network, thus depriving both the Holy Order of the Pontifex and the Godrealm of the Paranid of the chance to address these claims of heresy with action.</t>			
	<t id="59">Cathedral of Xaar</t>
	<t id="60">A system which had just been discovered and claimed by the Paranid prior to the beginning of the Collapse, Cathedral of Xaar was previously slated to become a far flung temple in service to the holy three-dimensionality. These ideas were dashed when the sector was once again thrown into the dark and those Paranid within driven to madness by the isolation. Now once again connected to the network, the Godrealm has wasted no time in revisiting these plans and have re-consecrated the sector as a holy site once again.</t>			
	<t id="61">Clarity's End</t>
	<t id="62">In the old network, this sector fell into dispute immediately upon discovery, as long-range scout patrols from Cardinal's Domain ventured entered this area at the same time as the arrival of a mining expedition from Aladna Hill. The resulting tensions did little but re-open old wounds, leading to a cooling of Paranid-Argon relations. \n\nHaving now been reconnected to the Network via Cardinal's Domain, deep behind Godrealm territories and far from Argon space, the Cardinal himself has issued orders to explore and exploit the sector's resources with the aim of aiding efforts to establish the Second Duchy.</t>			
	<t id="63">Desecrated Skies</t>
	<t id="64">Ravaged by conflict, greed, and now the Xenon; this sector remains in turmoil. Pre-shutdown, the constant roiling conflicts between competing pirate factions made Desecrated Skies extremely dangerous to travel. Paranid efforts to cleanse the sector were frequent and forceful but failed to produce lasting results, with pirate activity soon reappearing almost as soon as the last Paranid ship left through the gate. \n\nJust a few months before the sector was cut off by the Shutdown, the Beryll Syndicate was rumored to have become involved with one of the local pirate groups - likely the source of the Xenon found to be occupying the system upon its rediscovery.</t>	
	<t id="65">Perdition's End</t>
	<t id="66">Perdition's flames brought fear to the hearts of both Argon and Paranid, and fury and rage from both sides have quenched the firestorm that burned through this sector. \n\nWith the Realignment placing the sector firmly in the Godrealm's sphere of influence, it seems that even flames of conquest may be flickering out for this sector.</t>		
	<t id="67">Ket's Reckoning</t>
	<t id="68">When an unknown gate in Windfall III activated, Ket Rova, a nearby Riptide Raker smuggler on the run from Vigor Syndicate enforcers, took a risk and dashed through the newly-active gate in his bid for freedom, becoming the first known individual to lay eyes on the new sector. \n\nThough initially calm and deserted, the peace was abruptly shattered by the appearance of a massive Kha'ak swarm, apparently drawn by the reignition of the gate. When Ket escaped back to Windfall III he brought with him a reckoning for the Syndicate; a Kha'ak invasion.</t>		
	<t id="69">{20005,7043}(Titania)</t>	
	<t id="70">Situated in close proximity to Uranus's largest moon, Titania, this sector was the primary base for the AGI Task Force prior to their merger into the wider Terran Protectorate. Now operating under the banner of the Intervention Corps, Titania has once again been built to deal with every operation or contingency which the Corps may have to commit to as part of their operational scope. \n\nDespite the organization's new name, Titania retains many of the old ATF landmark stations like the Military Flight School and the Central Intelligence Service which acts as an isolated branch of the Terran Secret Service despite the restructuring that was demanded after the Torus Aeternal was destroyed. \n\nDue Titania's close proximity to the Neptune gate it is believe that much of the protection and security of Outer Sol is organized here and following the recent rumors of Yaki involvement with the Pioneers, many have openly advocated for the return of ATF proper.</t>
	<t id="71">{20005,3020}(Xaar's Belt)</t>
	<t id="72">Following the reconnection of both Clarity's End and Perdition's End, Godrealm of the Paranid sent scouts to delve deeper into the new unknown and found this previously unidentified sector, believing it to be a sign from the holy three-dimensionality and immediately dispatched ships to establish three sets of superhighways.</t>			
	<t id="73">{20005,3020} {20402,1}(Xaar's Belt I)</t>
	<t id="74">Situated between the planet's two moons, Xaar's Belt I is rich in methane and acts as the anchor in the superhighway connections as the scouts identified the, at the time, inactive gate which now connects to the Xenon ravaged Desecrated Skies.</t>			
	<t id="75">{20005,3020} {20402,2}(Xaar's Belt II)</t>
	<t id="76">The sector's asteroid belt is the result of the second moon's slow decay caused by the planet's gravity pulling it down, which ultimately will result in the moon's impact of the planet and destruction of any potential planetary colony.</t>			
	<t id="77">{20005,3020} {20402,3}(Xaar's Belt III)</t>	
	<t id="78">When the Paranid scouts first entered the system via the Clarity's End gate they were met with the brilliance of the local sun's blue corona and began surveying the first moon while venturing deeper into the system, probing for any other potential gates before they made unexpected contact with another team of Paranid scouts who arrived via the Perdition's End gate.</t>	
	<t id="79">The Shallows</t>
	<t id="80">Originally deemed to be impossible to settle due to deeply drifting nebulae; The Shallows remained largely unpopulated. With recent solar flares having helped to clear the nebulae, building had continued at a greater pace. Both Boron and Split forces contested the area, eager to regain lost ground. \n\nDuring the Shutdown this sector was one of few known to have not regressed due to the dominating presence of the Strong Arms corporation and is directly connected to the "Enduring Shores" Boron sectors. \n\nThe Shallows stands as the crossroads against the Atreus Corporation and host to numerous skirmishes during the long isolation. Originally the over zealous Strong Arms conducted an invasion of Queen's Retribution while orbital assets were being evacuated and while the assault succeeded in ravaging the remaining Boron miltiary, it was equally destructive on the Split and led to neither side having the advantage over the other.</t>	
	<t id="81">{20005,5044}(Family Than)</t>
	<t id="82">The seat of political power for the Split within the "Warlord's Dominion". Prior to the Shutdown, Patriarch Than was simply the director of the Strong Arms corporation but following this he seized power in the now completely cutoff Split sectors which now included this previously unknown sector. \n\nWhile all real power was still centered within Thyn's Excavation via the Strong Arms Corporation, Patriarch Than was eager to further validate his new title and laid claim to the entire system. However following reconnection to the Network and under the threats of Patriach Zyarth, Patriach Than fell in line and, officially, is subservient to Zyarth. In reality the Strong Arms Corporation still has completely authority within the "Warlord's Dominion".</t>			
	<t id="83">{20005,5044} {20402,1}(Family Than I)</t>
	<t id="84">The capital of Family Than and political seat of power within the "Warlord's Dominion", this sector is arguably the second most important Split sector because of the crucial ore mined from the asteroid belt. \n\nOnce reconnected to the Gate Network, Patriarch Zyarth demanded Family Than yield to his authority or risk the same fate as the formally Free Families. While officially subservient, Patriach Than is still the director of the Strong Arms Corporation and has refused to degrade his status.</t>			
	<t id="85">{20005,5044} {20402,3}(Family Than III)</t>
	<t id="86">Pushed further out from the planet's orbit, Family Than III is the location of a previously inactive gate which has only very recently reconnected to the wider Network via Unholy Descent and by extension, the zealots of the Holy Order of the Pontifex. \n\nThe sole source of ore for the Split within the "Warlord's Dominion", this system is very busy with industrial ships traversing acrossing the sector to keep the ever demanding Strong Arm war machine running.</t>
	<t id="87">Thyn's Abyss</t>
	<t id="88">This deep space system was about as close as the Split got to a civilian operation and once produced food and other organic products while mines on the asteroids spread across the system. Due to the lack of any real military presence the sector was quickly overwhelmed by Xenon forces before they withdrew back to Matrix #472D just before the Great Shutdown.</t>		
	<t id="89">Thyn's Excavation</t>
	<t id="90">The location of the Stong Arms Headquarters, Thyn's Excavation provided funds and resources for the ongoing conflict in the local area against not just the nearby Boron but across the entire old Network and continues to be very well guarded by the aptly named corporation. \n\nFollowing the Great Shutdown, Strong Arms took complete control of the local Split sectors in what became known as the "Warlord's Dominion" ruled by the self appointed Patriarch Than, the director the Strong Arms Corporation.</t>
	<t id="91">{20005,9008}(Blue Horizon)</t>	
	<t id="92">Prior to the Great Shutdown this sector was officially designated US 18-16 and was the location of a disappointing mineral survey conducted by the Boron Royal Research Institute. Despite the poor results efforts continued to probe the sector for anything of value as it was reconnected to the "Enduring Shores" of the Atreus Corporation who deployed their only Superhighway following a review of the previous survey and the discovery that the results were intentionally fabricated for unknown purposes and obscured the fact that the sector was extremely mineral rich. \n\nHome to most of what was the "Enduring Shores" mining operations, Blue Horizon is as critical as ever against the local Split and Xenon threat.</t>			
	<t id="93">{20005,9008} {20402,1}(Blue Horizon I)</t>	
	<t id="94">The original core of the sector, Blue Horizon I is where the erroneous survey was conducted which stated that the sector was devoid of mineral value despite the presense of a significant asteroid field. \n\nAs such, Blue Horizon I is a vital source of ore for the Atreus Corporation's operation in the "Enduring Shores" and is generally well guarded against any potential Split incursion from the "Warlord's Dominion".</t>				
	<t id="95">{20005,9008} {20402,4}(Blue Horizon IV)</t>
	<t id="96">Settled as a result of the Atreus Corporation's construction of the Superhighway, Blue Horizon IV is abundant in both methane and silicon, further proof that the Boron Royal Research Institue's mineral survey was a complete lie. \n\nSituated further in to the Blue Horizon sector, it is less guarded than its companion and is directly connected to Queen's Harbour. However following the recent reconnection to the Network and the previously inactive gate to Great Trench now online and showing concerning signs of Xenon, the Atreus Corporation has begun to divert newly supplied Queendom military assets to better protect this vital system.</t>	
	<t id="97">Great Trench</t>	
	<t id="98">This Boron mining colony was once a busy hub of both industry and as a refit and supply center for Boron ships working in the new colonies. Harsh conditions and pirate raids made the Boron who lived here harder and more cynical than those in the home systems, \n\nOnce isolated, the colony very quickly fell apart as they were unable to produce their own food and quickly burned through any stockpiles they had gathered.</t>
	<t id="99">Queen's Harbour</t>	
	<t id="100">Once specialising in food and power storage technology, Queen's Harbour is the location of the original Atreus Headquarters that was lost when the Gates began to shut down. While the remnants of the corporation reestablished themselves in Ocean of Fantasy before collapsing under the stewartship of the Provinces Adrift, Atreus proper became the driving force in the "Enduring Shores" of Queen's Harbour, Queen's Retribution, and the formally colonized Blue Horizon. \n\nNow that connection has been reestablished these sectors immediately rejoined the Queendom but are still formally run by the Atreus Corporation due to the vast distance between them and Kingdom's End.</t>
	<t id="101">Queen's Retribution</t>
	<t id="102">Formally a Boron core sector specialising in technological and military output, Queen's Retribution was established to strike out against a growing conflict with the Split. During the Great Shutdown the new Boron colonies were completely disconnected from the wider network and instead were locked into a bitter conflict with the equally trapped "Warlord's Dominion" Split. \n\nWhile originally the home of the local Boron Shipyard, Queen's Retribution found itself now on the frontline in the local conflict. As such, all vital infrastructure was moved to the more secure Queen's Harbour and brought completely under the control of the Atreus Corporation.</t>
	<t id="103">{20005,8001} {20005,8003}{20404,4}{20404,7}{20404,2}{20403,4}(Matrix #472D)</t>
	<t id="104">Once a Split mining outpost, one day a distress signal from the colony was intercepted by the Argon security operatives in Black Hole Sun. When they investigated they found the entire system destroyed, its planet a radioactive hell and access to the system was restricted. There has been no official explanation from any government concerning this disaster although rumours suggest a Xenon superweapon was to blame. \n\nPrior to the Shutdown pilots who passed through this system once reported a large ship but those reports ceased and if the ship existed, its presence and location was never known and the Xenon presence in the system has only further increased following The Collapse.</t>
	<t id="105">{20005,9038}(Ocracoke's Storm)</t>
	<t id="106">This bleak region was once home to the Yaki pirate faction. While dozens of rumours swirled regarding the sector prior to The Shutdown, little else was ever confirmed and only speculations were left.</t>				
	<t id="107">{20005,9038} {20402,1}(Ocracoke's Storm I)</t>
	<t id="108">Prior to the deactivation of the Gates the Yaki were responsible for the bold theft of a pair of, at the time, experimental superhighways which were used to expand the sector significantly while moving the Southern gate further South. There were also rumours that the Yaki were responsible for the theft of Accelerators destined for Lucky Planets but no proof was discovered before The Collapse.</t>			
	<t id="109">{20005,9038} {20402,2}(Ocracoke's Storm II)</t>
	<t id="110">The enigmatic Southern sector of Ocracoke's Storm, the local gate was once connected to Senator's Badlands and had been heavily guarded by the Yaki's strongest ships. It now remains as silent as its Northern counterpart, showing no indications of the fate to these Yaki and continuing to conceal their secrets.</t>
	<t id="111">{20005,6025}(Shadows of Giants)</t>
	<t id="112">An enigma to the Alliance of the Word, Shadows of Giants is both completely unknown and had never been charted yet is home to a fully operational, albeit old, superhighway of unknown origin and unknown builder.</t>			
	<t id="113">{20005,6025} {20402,6}(Shadows of Giants VI)</t>
	<t id="114">"Shrouded in the darkness and adrift in the endless void this system bares witness to the Shadows of Giants."</t>			
	<t id="115">{20005,6025} {20402,7}(Shadows of Giants VII)</t>
	<t id="116">"Bathed in the light and tethered to the Great Giant, this system holds the truth of its magnificence."</t>	
	<t id="117">Bala Gi's Joy</t>
	<t id="118">Once deep in unclaimed space, Bala Gi's Joy is home to a cratered moon, used as a scrapyard for the wreckage of the many ship disabled and then stripped by the pirates of the past following ambushing and attack traveling ships. These same pirates were then trapped following the Shutdown and forced to survive on what little was left in the system following the years of stealing everything of value from the corpses of the dead. \n\nThey did not survive long.</t>
	<t id="119">Blue Profit</t>
	<t id="120">Once a busy and lucrative Teladi system with an economy dependent on high-quality electronics. Blue Profit was most famous as the source of the distinctive style of music devised by Teladi factory workers which combined Teladi reed-whistles and Boron toneshells with Argon and Teladi percussion instruments. "Teladi Blues" is still appreciated by many sentient species post-Shutdown. \n\nNow the sector's space remains silent, the economy having completely collapsed and nearly every ship no longer spaceworthy.</t>			
	<t id="121">{20005,8001} {20005,8003}{20404,4}{20404,8}{20404,3}(Matrix #483)</t>
	<t id="122">Matrix #483 Desc</t>			
	<t id="123">The Vault</t>
	<t id="124">While the Teladi Company is not known for its military ventures, the population of this sector would have choosen to disagree. The Vault was a system hard to reach by normal means and contained nothing but high tech stations. \n\nHome to the Teladi Company's main research facility and it always tried to improve upon existing technology. While expected to expand and greatly improve the Company's assets, The Vault was lost to the Shutdown and all hopes and aspirations were lost with it when the colonists were unable to sustain their own survival.</t>			
	<t id="125">Recovered Capital</t>
	<t id="126">Once one of nearly a dozen pirate controlled sectors it was renamed to Recovered Capital during the Shutdown as a large Teladi fleet was stranded in sector and forced into a prolonged war against the equally isolated pirates. \n\nInitially things went very poorly for the Teladi before it became obvious that the pirates could not sustain the conflict beyond the opening phases and were ultimately overwhelmed.</t>
	<t id="127">{20005,9002}(Wretched Skies)</t>
	<t id="128"></t>			
	<t id="129">{20005,9002} {20402,12}(Wretched Skies XII)</t>
	<t id="130"></t>			
	<t id="131">{20005,9002} {20402,15}(Wretched Skies XV)</t>
	<t id="132"></t>			
	<t id="133">Duke's Vision</t>
	<t id="134"></t>	
	<t id="135">Emperor's Wisdom</t>
	<t id="136"></t>	
	<t id="137">Fierce Clarity</t>
	<t id="138"></t>
	<t id="139">Danna's Chance</t>
	<t id="140">This lawless system was the hub of the black market in food and low-tech industrial produce. Many unscrupulous merchants had made a fortune trading the illicit goods while many more were not so fortunate. \n\nDuring The Shutdown it would seem those local pirates banded together and became quite a formidable organization which kept a firm grip on control and managing the resources which were available. Since reconnection they accepted an invitation to join the Scale Plate Pact and have since received significant economic boost to their operations.</t>
	<t id="141">Legend's Home</t>
	<t id="142">Prior to the Great Shutdown this sector simply did not exist on navigation systems with any rumors ruthlessly squashed until OTAS was ready for the sector to be made public. A center for high tech research and development, Legend's Home is the beating heart of OTAS's power. \n\nAs the gates began to flicker, OTAS launched an invasion into the neighbouring sector of Akeela's Beacon after a dispute over financial bureaucracy would see the government's support of OTAS dwindle substantial. However, once the Great Shutdown began and OTAS was thrown into the dark they returned to their roots, albeit with significantly reduced wages, and are now even more technologically advanced than they have ever been.</t>
	<t id="143">Merchant Haven</t>
	<t id="144">Merchant Haven was established to be a major trade port for the new Teladi expansion campaign, however plans failed when surprise attacks by hostile pirate forces stopped their advance into the nearby systems. The sector then served the local Teladi population and traded with the nearby Argon and Split. \n\nFollowing its reconnection, Merchant Haven found itself in a very advantageous position in the Teladi's largest block of sectors.</t>
	<t id="145">Akeela's Beacon</t>
	<t id="146">The four great stars which grace this sector were created following the tragic but noble sacrifice of Akeela Hartnell. Her last will was for the Argon Federation to govern the new system and make it a safe haven for all traders. \n\nHowever, this dream was crushed shortly before the Great Shutdown when the OTAS corporation invaded and occupied the system to deprive the remaining Argon colonies of vital sources of energy. Initially this occupation was justified as a necessary step towards securing the well-being of the system's population but post-Shutdown OTAS reinforced their presence in the sector, developing it into a proper first line of defence should anyone, or anything, attempt to attack Legend's Home.</t>
	<t id="147">Aladna Hill</t>
	<t id="148">One of the first systems to be colonised by the Argon after the last Xenon war, Aladna Hill was a supply and support base for the exploration of further systems. Following the OTAS invasion of Akeela's Beacon the Argon Federation began to amass military assets with the goal of reclaiming the system and bring the corporation to justice. \n\nPost-Shutdown these military assets were used to keep law and order both in Aladna Hill and neighbouring Light of Heart. As such, when they reconnected to the Network they were swiftly reintegrate into the Argon Federation.</t>
	<t id="149">Light of Heart</t>
	<t id="150">Once the source of ships and equipment for the Argon settlements claimed following the conclussion of the last Xenon war. Following the OTAS invasion of Akeela's Beacon all efforts were made to building military assets for the counterattack. Unfortunately the Great Shutdown began before this planned attack was initiated which left a significant portion of the Argon Navy stranded in both Light of Heart and Aladna Hill. \n\nDuring this period of isolation Light of Heart changed from being a source of military assets and instead became the heart of trade and commerce with the substantial military ships keeping a firm grip on law and order. Once reconnected this pivot proved especially benefitial as Light of Heart became a key trade route in the Network's new orientation.</t>
	<t id="151">Montalaar</t>
	<t id="152">An old mining outpost founded near the red gas giant "Hitt's Eye", Montalaar had been an Argon settlement in the areas of space claimed following the Xenon conflict. \n\nTrading, food, and materials installations had been constructed in service to the private mining outfits looking to exploit new minerals but following the Shutdown these facilities were slowly decommissioned to keep the orbital station host to a small colony from falling apart. Now that the sector is reconnected, survivors have begun to be relocated across the Federation and the reintegrate of the sector has begun.</t>
	<t id="153">Mines of Fortune</t>
	<t id="154">Once the largest Teladi mining operation in history following the Teladi discovering and retrofitting abandoned space stations set into mineral-rich asteroids. The vast richness of the sector would be of no consolation to those left behind following its complete isolation as there was no infrastructure in place to refine the raw ore and silicon into useable products. It appears that the entire sector collapsed, unable to provide power and food to the doomed residents. \n\nCuriously the previously retrofitted mining stations are absent from the sector, their fates unknown.</t>		
	<t id="155">Zyarth's Stand</t>
	<t id="156">Originally little more than a desolate fallback for Family Zyarth once they had been cut off and trapped behind the Xenon, Zyarth's Stand became home to a Split Equipment Dock and the remaining Zyarth forces prior to the Great Shutdown yet even these gates immediately began to flickering following Family Zyarth's total assault against the Xenon. Now reconnected to Zyarth's Dominion, Patriarch Zyarth is eager to reclaim the system and fully integrate it into his new empire.</t>
	<t id="157">Patriarch's Conclusion</t>
	<t id="158">Once one of the Split's most remote core sectors with a moderate output of agricultural products. Military operations here served as the base for the building conflict in nearby sectors due to the ever increasing tensions with the Boron which finally escalated to outright war following the Great Shutdown. \n\nFollowing its reconnection, Zyarth scouts discovered that all orbital assets had been destroyed as the result of some undocumented war. Worse yet there was no evidence of any Boron wreckage or losses in the conflict which was either the result of sheer overwhelming numbers or the failings of these clearly disgraceful Split.</t>
	<t id="159">Elena's Fortune</t>
	<t id="160">After the Kha'ak attack on President's End the decision was made to bolster the defense of the Argon home systems. The Kha'ak's attack had decimated the pirate forces and allowed the sector to be reclaimed and fortified. Once the system's gates deactivated all of the Federation's plans fell apart and the sector quickly fell back into anarchy and disorder.</t>
	<t id="161">Nyana's Hideout</t>
	<t id="162">Named after the Argon heroine and Goner priestess Nyana Gunne, great-grandaughter of the famous Argon leader Nathan Gunne, this system was the location of some of the more colourful events in her life. Prior to the Great Shutdown the sector had fallen on hard times, hardening the people which served them well in the isolation. Following the Gates' reactivating, Nyana's Hideout connected to the still isolated Argon sectors near the newly formed empire of Patriarch Zyarth and became a shelter for refugees fleeing the frequent slaver raids.</t>
	<t id="163">Interworlds</t>
	<t id="164">Originally an agricultural colony built by the Argon to supply food to the rest of the Argon Federation, Interworlds expanded to include more high tech stations and products. Once home to the 4th Argon Expeditionary Force, they were not present in the system during the Great Shutdown. What did remain was unable to maintain the stations and slowly they were decommissioned to maintain the supply of food.</t>	
	<t id="165">Wastelands</t>
	<t id="166">Once named Light of Hope until the Xenon attacked many years ago and it was clear that the patrols wouldn't hold out against further attacks so the colony was prepared for evacuation using whatever transport ships were available. A large force of four Titan class Destroyers and two Colossus Carriers, complete with full fighter wings were dispatched to escort the fleeing transports but were overwhelmed by a Xenon fleet with only the civilian ships and a lone destroyer, the Challenger, escaping.\n\nThree years later a joint Argon-Boron force reclaimed the sector and recolonization began. Unfortunately the Great Shutdown once again thwarted this sector's progress and what had been established has fallen into complete disrepair and the surviving colonists eking out a meager existence.</t>	
	<t id="167">Ghinn's Escape</t>
	<t id="168">Founded to prevent the Boron expanding further into the area it once connected to, this Split colony was once heavily guarded and a large manufacturer of surveillance equipment and defensive weapons allegedly for protection against Boron aggression. Members of both Families Tkr and Njy were often found in this sector given its close proximity to their space and even saw some skirmishes between them following Family Njy's invasion and occupation of Family Tkr's territory as a result of the Dragon Incident. \n\nFollowing the Great Shutdown this colony completely collapsed and was entirely isolated for decades. The surviving Split families are only just now learning of Patriarch Zyarth's aggression while the sector itself has become a hub for the Fallen Families as they have bolster their ranks with the inhabitants of Ghinn's Escape.</t>					
	<t id="169">{20202,901} {20001,201} {20401,1}(Kha'ak Sector Alpha)</t>
	<t id="170">The presence of wreckage and debris clearly indicate this sector was once connected but there are no known records.</t>				
	<t id="171">{20202,901} {20001,201} {20401,2}(Kha'ak Sector Beta)</t>
	<t id="172">This sector  appears to be a source of a major Kha'ak infestation.</t>			
	<t id="173">{20202,901} {20001,201} {20401,3}(Kha'ak Sector Gamma)</t>
	<t id="174">A poorly scouted sector with sporadic reports of Kha'ak pressence.</t>				
	<t id="175">{20203,3104} {20202,901} {20001,201}(Unknown Kha'ak Sector)</t>
	<t id="176">This region of space is disconnected from the gate network and shows sign of extreme Kha'ak infestation.</t>			
	<t id="177">{20006,301}(Unknown Sector)</t>	
	<t id="178">Error: Location not found within known network.</t>				
	<t id="179">{20202,901} {20005,4002}(Kha'ak Hive)</t>	
	<t id="180">Operation Final Fury Failed.</t>
	<t id="181">Spaceweed Grove</t>
	<t id="182">Pre-Shutdown the Teladi had been expanding their influence into the sector with aspirations to take control from the local pirates but were met with fierce resistence which only led to an even more protracted conflict. Now that the gates have reactivated Teladi scouts have so far only found the debris of both Teladi and pirate forces along with the shattered remains of old stations with uncomfirmed reports that the other gate is also active.</t>			
	<t id="183">Shadow's End</t>	
	<t id="184">A previously hidden sector locked behind the OTAS Headquarters of Legend's Home, this sector has since come into its own during the Great Shutdown. Despite the close proximity and abundance of mineral resources, this was the last sector to be incorporated into the OTAS Corporation's holdings as it was not a threat to their security and no local facilities were required. \n\nSince being added, OTAS has expanded their exploitation of the rich resources to fuel their ever growing demand and infrastructure developments while also relocating several high-tech facilities.</t>	
	<t id="185">Tebathimanckatt's Legacy</t>	
	<t id="186">A dim, unpopulated sector along the Paranid border region, Tebathimanckatt's Legacy saw only cursory resource surveys when its jumpgate connection opened from Pious Mists IV, with the Godrealm being preoccupied with reconsolidating its holdings as the gate system began to awaken. This attitude changed following the discovery of the breakaway Holy Order and their heretic Pontifex, which coincided with a flurry of rumors that the sector's name was more than symbolic and that hidden somewhere within were artifacts of great power once held by Admiral Tebathimanckatt himself. \n\nThough these artifacts never materialized despite an intense search by private citizens and Godrealm-affiliated forces alike, the discovery of the jumpgate connecting to Perpetual Sin III saw the system's status skyrocket from quiet Godrealm backwater to a critical strategic avenue and second war front. Forming a potential path to strike at their enemy's interior regions, achieving military control over the sector became a high priority for both factions.</t>
	<t id="187">Untainted Eternity</t>		
	<t id="188">Situated above the accretion disc of a black hole - this sector is completely unkown and new to the Gate Network, unspoiled by centuries of conflict. \n\nCuriously, and troubling to many, the time dilation expected from such close proximity to a black hole is not observed here and even more concerning signals are somehow being emitted from within the black hole, which should be impossible.</t>		
	<t id="189">Belt of Aguilar</t>		
	<t id="190">Founded shortly after the first Kha'ak invasions, as a support outpost for the nearby colonies, Belt of Aguilar has had a short but turbulent history. With the rise of the newly relocated Jonferco, this sector initially enjoyed good prospects as it housed the only gate to the newly discovered Albion system; which was a playground for corporations to test new technologies and extract the vast mineral riches. \n\nHowever, following the destruction of the original Jonferco Headquarters and the shutdown of the Albion gate, the sector's future became uncertain. during the Great Shutdown what was left on the Jonferco corporation began to rebuild and retun to their roots while efforts have been made in attempting to reactivate the Albion gate.</t>
	<t id="199">Torus 87</t>		
	<t id="200">Torus 87 Desc</t>	
	<t id="201">Tkr's Deprivation</t>		
	<t id="202">Once owned by the T'kr Family and a hub of activiity, this sector was seized by the Njy Family under orders from the Patriarch of all Split and became little more than a mining system following the Dragon Incident. Even before the Great Shutdown the sector had be run into disrepair with even new stations being poorly maintained, pirate activity had increased, and remains of a minefield played by the T'kr were scattered about. \n\nNow reconnected, Family Tkr attempted to reclaim and rebuild the sector before the disasterous lost in Fires of Defeat. To make a bad situation even worse it's been confirmed that the Northern gate is connected to a dangerous Xenon Matrix.</t>
	<t id="203">{20005,8001} {20005,8003}{20404,6}{20404,9}{20404,5}(Matrix #695)</t>	
	<t id="204">Identified as a heavily entrenched Xenon sector prior to the shutdown, #695 was barely explored due to the extreme risk to pilots and the data corruption of remote drones. While it once was believed to be a core sector; #695 was clearly severed from the wider Xenon network prior to its recent reconnection.</t>		
	<t id="205">{20005,7004}(Aldrin)</t>
	<t id="206">desc</t>
	<t id="207">{20005,7004} {20402,1}(Aldrin I)</t>
	<t id="208">desc</t>	
	<t id="209">{20005,7004} {20402,2}(Aldrin II)</t>
	<t id="210">desc</t>
	<t id="211">{20005,7004} {20402,3}(Aldrin III)</t>
	<t id="212">desc</t>	
	<t id="213">The Bastion</t>
	<t id="214">desc</t>
	<t id="215">Cloudbase South West</t>
	<t id="216">desc</t>		

	<t id="2000">Derelict Jump Beacon</t>	
	<!--TEST SECTOR ENTRIES-->
	<t id="18000">Test Cluster</t>
	<t id="18001">Test Cluster Desc</t>			
	<t id="18002">Test Sector 001</t>
	<t id="18003">Test Sector 001 Desc</t>			
	<t id="18004">Test Sector 002</t>
	<t id="18005">Test Sector 002 Desc</t>			
	<t id="18006">Test Sector 003</t>	
	<t id="18007">Test Sector 003 Desc</t>
  </page>	

			<!--OTAS Assets-->  
  <page id="19530002" title="OTAS" descr="OTAS" voice="yes">	
	<t id="100">OTAS</t>
	<t id="101">The Optimised Technology, Armaments and Shielding Corporation, commonly known as OTAS, is a omnicorporation specialized in the design and manufacture of advanced spaceships heaquartered in Legend's Home. In the pre-Shutdown era, OTAS technologies and ships were highly advanced, often leading the cutting edge of Commonwealth scientific advancement, granting the corporation a prominent position on the political starscape of the old Commonweath of Planets.\n\nJust prior to the Great Collapse, OTAS launched an attack on Akeela's Beacon in an escalatory response to the passing of certain industry regulations by the Argon Federation. Seen as an act of terrorism by the Argon, the resulting Argon military response was cut short by Gate Shutdown. While the exact history of the period is lost to the chaos of the Great Dark, it is clear that the Argon response failed to bring OTAS to heel and the corporation now holds full administrative and military control of the formerly Argon sectors in their local region. \n\nHaving evolved beyond a simple technologies corporation, the massive OTAS commercial enterprise now operates as a fully independent star nation. Featuring locally appointed representatives from each controlled sector sitting on the board of directors and a functional state apparatus that earns generally favourable public sentiment, any scars of the hostile takeover have seemingly faded from memory.</t>
	<t id="102">While very much still human, and thus biologically indistinguishable from Argon citizens, the citizens of the OTAS corporation-state have developed societally and culturally into a distinct people during their isolation. Following the reconnection, OTAS citizens have come to be seen by much of the Commonwealth as a mixture of both the Argon and Terrans in ambition, technology, and temperament. Only time will tell if they continue to carve their own path or are ultimately brought back into the fold.</t>
	<t id="103">OTAS Capital Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="104">OTAS Capital Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="105">Armaments Professional</t>
	<t id="106">Security Specialist</t>
	<t id="107">OTAS General Use Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="108">OTAS General Use Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="109">OTAS Military Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="110">OTAS Military Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="111">OTAS Police Licence</t>
	<t id="112">OTAS Capital Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="113">OTAS Ancillary Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="114">OTAS Advanced Module Licence</t>
	<t id="115">OTAS Basic Module Licence</t>
	<t id="116">OTAS Intermediate Module Licence</t>
	<t id="117">OTAS Trade Offer Subscription</t>
	<t id="118">OTAS</t>
	<t id="119">OTAS Ship Sale Contract</t>	
	<!--TURRETS/WEAPONS-->
	<t id="200">Anemoi Cruise Missile Launcher</t>
	<t id="201">Anemoi Cruise Missile</t>
	<t id="202">Phased Array Laser Cannon</t>		
	<t id="203">Firestorm Artillery</t>
	<t id="204">\033#97e19b23#SH\033X  M/AM Barrage Accelerator</t>		
	<t id="205">\033#95e03b29#LM\033X M/AM Mass Driver</t>	
	<t id="206">\033#95e03b29#BMB\033X\ Multi-Missile Launch Array</t>
	<t id="207">\033#95e03b29#BMB\033X\ Cluster Bomb Launcher</t>
	<t id="208">Rangefinder - 28km</t>	
	<!--TURRETS/WEAPONS DESCRIPTIONS-->
	<t id="300">Designed specifically for the Aquilo, this launcher is the only platform capable of deploying the OTAS Anemoi Cruise Missile.</t>
	<t id="301">Properties: Cruise missile | Guided | Swarm | Target-seeking \nAI Launch Range: 30 km the many unique weapons developed in the isolation of the Shutdown era, the Anemoi Cruise Missile system swiftly gained notoriety among Commonwealth military observers during OTAS's initial wave of strikes against the Argon Federation. \n\nUnlike most comparable Commonwealth missile systems, the Anemoi utilizes an array of advanced passive and active tracking and guidance systems, able to achive effective target locks at ranges of 30km despite the prevalence of signal masking and jamming systems in the modern battlespace. This is paired with a distinctive quad-missile launch salvo that has taken many unprepared targets by surprise and greatly increases the difficulty of achieving effective missile interception.</t>		
	<t id="302">Rather than traditional amplification oscillators and focusing chambers found on standard Commonwealth high-output beam weaponry, the OTAS Phased Array Laser Cannon uses an array of quickly-positionable tuning mirrors to rapidly concentrate and focus energy into a cohesive beam. While the PALC has significantly reduced raw power output and range compared to its peers, the design features much faster turret tracking and a shorter cycle time which lets it rapidly re-engage new targets with near-perfect accuracy, making it a deadly weapon against fighters.</t>	
	<t id="303">\033#95e03b29#XL Turret\033X\ TEMPEST ONLY \nThe Firestorm Artillery is the result of a decades-long OTAS effort to replicate the Terran Point Singularity Projector, infamous for savaging even the high-tech OTAS-supported Argon Navy during the Terran Conflict era. Despite years of research and nigh-unlimited resources poured into the project, OTAS was ultimately forced to conclude that replicating and deploying the Terran technology in a viable manner was impossible due to the unique high-energy power architcture of Terran ships and systems. In the end, an alternative route was chosen- rather than imitate the Point Singularity Projector itself, OTAS would simply aim to replicate the weapon's destructive power.\n\nThus a surprisingly low-tech solution was found: by converting Firestorm torpedo warheads for use in ballistic shells fired from enormous oversized kinetic accelerators, OTAS could field a heavy siege weapon with superb range and devastating destructive potential. However, the design did require several compromises: the sheer size of the turret and munitions handling systems means it is slow to acquire targets and can only be mounted on specially designed hardpoints such as those on Tempest, while the relative sensitivity of the warhead payload enforces a low projectile velocity and further limits its ability to engage small or moving targets.</t>
	<t id="304">Size: SMALL\n Weapon Class: HEAVY\n\nDeveloped from studying salvaged Terran Matter/Antimatter weapons technology, this fighter-class weapon fires a torrent of small M/AM warheads that can devastate targets in short order. However, the small scale of the warheads causes them to suffer faster payload containment destabilization, resulting in a severely limited effective range.</t>	
	<t id="305">Size: LARGE\n Weapon Class: RAILGUN\n\nA devastating capital-class weapon based on a combination of pre-Shutdown Split kinetic weapons technology and salvaged Terran Matter/Antimatter weapons, the M/AM Mass Driver is regarded as one of the great triumphs of Dark-era OTAS research. Firing large-caliber shells carrying the heaviest and stablest matter/antimatter payload ever developed by the Commonwealth, the weapon delivers devastating firepower with lethal accuracy at long range.</t>	
	<t id="306">Size: SMALL\n Weapon Class: BOMBER\n\nA modular, on-the-fly-reconfigurable universal launch system capable of loading and firing nearly any self-propelled missile system available throughout the gate network. \n\nOriginally developed by OTAS for their revolutionary Notus bomber, Terran observers were quick to realize the weapon's potential and the Protectorate soon developed their own version- identical in concept and operation, but created using Terran technology. OTAS' comparatively advanced technological base combined with vigorous counter-espionage efforts has thus far kept their version of the design safe from replication by the less sophisticated rival Commonwealth powers.</t>	
	<t id="307">Size: SMALL\n Weapon Class: BOMBER\n\nThe result of a joint development effort by Split and OTAS scientists to produce a new weapon for the Notus and the newly-introduced Split Wolf, the Cluster Bomb Launcher is a specialized, single-payload variant of the standard Missile Launch Array that fires large volleys of unguided explosive projectiles. Intended to give bombers viable striking power against capital-class targets without being reliant on limited missile ammunition, the weapon is highly effective in it's intended role and is now a common sight among Split bomber forces. However, the wide spread and poor velocity of the projectiles along with a lack of proximity detonation ability renders the system largely ineffective against small craft.</t>
	<t id="308">A sophisticated missile guidance and target tracking system forming a cornerstone of the Anemoi Cruise Missile's multi-faceted targeting package, designed for the Aquilo. \n\nWhile active laser designator systems are an ancient pre-spaceflight technology, simulated combat exercises with the early Aquilo testbeds revealed that the laser designator unit - nominally just a contingency backup system to the more advanced options built into the suite - proved extremely popular with Aquilo crews and the ship performed notably better when the system was enabled than when it was turned off. Additional testing revealed that the cause was twofold: the narrow-band wavelength cycling ability of the laser proved effective at defeating a variety of conventional missile countermeasures, and on several occasions the Aquilo was able to use the visible laser beam to force one opposing ship to take evasive manuevers while using different guidance option to engage a second ship, taking both opponents by surprise.</t>	
	<!--STATION MODULES-->
	<t id="400">{19530002,100} Cross Connection Structure 01</t>	
	<t id="401">Cross 01</t>
	<t id="402">{19530002,100} {20104,15801}(OTAS Stimulant Production)</t>	
	<!--SHIPS-->
	<t id="700">Boreas</t>
	<t id="701">Auster</t>
	<t id="702">Aquilo</t>
	<t id="703">Skiron</t>
	<t id="704">Sirokos</t>
	<t id="705">Solano</t>
	<t id="706">Eurus</t>
	<t id="707">Notus</t>
	<t id="708">Venti</t>
	<t id="709">Zephyrus</t>
	<t id="710">Astraeus</t>
	<t id="711">Mistral</t>
	<t id="712">Tempest</t>
	<t id="713">Vesuvius</t>
	<t id="714">Genthus</t>	
	<t id="715">Andaman</t>		
	<!--SHIP DESCRIPTIONS-->
	<t id="800">Once the linchpin of the OTAS fleet, the Boreas continues to serve as the organization's premier destroyer-class warship. Upon Reactivation the Boreas has undergone significant change to compete with existing destroyer class ships. The modern Boreas is now much more heavily armed and shielded than before while still retaining some of the signature speed.</t>
	<t id="801">Completely redesigned following the Shutdown, the modern Auster retains the rank of a heavily shielded and lethal bomber while still retaining the now S-class fighter size.</t>
	<t id="802">A descendent of the ship that first establised "M7M" Missile Frigate type designation, the modern Aquilo honors its lineage with an intimidating array of launch tubes capable of launching the signature Anemoi Cruise Missile, providing massively destructive long-range fire support against capital targets and stations during OTAS fleet actions. \n\nDespite the tremendous power of its main armament, proper usage of the Aquilo necessitates a sizable escort force and strong local battlespace control, as the ship's relatively poor mobility and limited defensive armament leave it highly vulnerable to direct attack despite its typically above-average OTAS shielding.</t>
	<t id="803">The Skiron represented a significant step forward in OTAS corvette design. A further improvement on previous designs, the modern Skiron has evolved into a robust gunboat and is typically seen escorting capital class ships or as anchors in patrol fleets.</t>
	<t id="804">Once nearly abandoned following the seizure of Argon space, the Sirokos "M7M" frigate has had a radical redesign into a modern strike corvette with S-class fighter storage and launching capabilities.</t>
	<t id="805">The modern Solano is a highly advanced scout/interceptor hybrid. Its superb top speed and small size make it well-suited for swift reconnaisance in hostile space, and the above-average firepower packed onto the ship makes it a deadly counter to other scouting vessels, though it must rely on its speed to escape from larger threats.</t>			
	<t id="806">The standard fighter type deployed by OTAS, the Eurus is a well-rounded and capable combatant with respectable firepower and excellent high-speed manueverability. While it has few truly stand-out features aside from the high top speed, the ship enjoys a general advantage over its Commonwealth peers thanks to the advanced nature of OTAS technologies. The Eurus is a common sight in any location with an OTAS presence, serving on the offensive frontline and enforcing police presence in secured sectors.</t>		
	<t id="807">The Notus bomber was developed by OTAS during the isolation of the Great Dark. Initially just an exploratory testbed attempting to emulate the success of the M7M missile frigate- one of the many OTAS innovations of the pre-shutdown Commonwealth- the Notus performed well in simulations and exercises, promising to provide an immense amount of striking power with the ability to carry and deploy a wide variety of heavy ordnance in its modular side pods. When the gates abruptly reopened and OTAS resumed open hostilities against the Argon Federation, the Notus soon proved its worth and became notorious for savage lightning strikes capable of swiftly crippling Argon capital ships. \n\nSeeing an opportunity in their shared enemy, the Zyarth Patriarchy were quick to make diplomatic overtures towards OTAS, with the aim of procuring the Notus' technology for their own use. This effort culminated in the Split Wolf bomber and numerous improvements to the Notus, as well as new weapons that could take full advantage of the Notus-type ordnance hardpoint. The technology rapidly proliferated through the rest of the gate network, with the other Commonwealth powers and even the Terrans soon fielding their own bomber models- developed through espionage, battlefield salvage, or their own engineering efforts.</t>
	<t id="808">Regarded as one of the most fear heavy fighters pre-Shutdown, OTAS as diligently worked to keep the Venti at the pinnacle of lethality. The Venti is able to bring a truly devastating array of weapons to bare on anything deemed an enemy of OTAS.</t>
	<t id="809">OTAS completed a total redesign of the Zephyrus just after to the reactivation of local gates. Acknowledging they would require a strike carrier capable of projecting OTAS authority, the redesign maintained the core concept of the ship but brought it into the modern era with the new standardized S-class docking bays.</t>
	<t id="810">Once a common sight in pre-Shutdown OTAS fleets, the venerable Astraeus saw continuous design changes and modifications during the Shutdown-era to fit an evolving combat role as OTAS reshaped its fleets. The modern Astraeus is a capable and versatile escort frigate: fast and reasonably shielded, fitting array of offensive and defensive turrets, and even possessing limited launch facilities for a handful of escort fighters. \n\nThough it lacks any forward-firing main armament, the unconventional shape of the hull and ample turret hardpoints allows the Astraeus to maintain surperb fields of fire all around itself, and it is often seen operating ahead or within formations of larger capital ships on anti-fighter picket duty.</t>
	<t id="811">The life force of OTAS and long overshadowed, the Mistral is without a doubt the most important ship in the OTAS fleet. Following The Shutdown and takeover of the local Argon sectors large numbers of Mistrals would be seen transporting vast quantities of supplies across the new OTAS Exclusion Zone.</t>
	<t id="812">Developed in total secrecy pre-Shutdown and unleashed during the OTAS hostile seizure of the local Argon sectors, the Tempest is an extremely formidable battleship even by modern standards. The design saw continual updates, improvements, and iterations during the Great Dark to maintain its ability to engage entire fleets with minimal support, and it is one of the few deployment platforms for the OTAS Firestorm Artillery batteries. \n\nRumors abound that the ship makes use of highly illegal and dangerous AGI technology, though this has never been firmly proven despite intense scrutiny from both Commonwealth rivals and the Terran Protectorate.</t>
	<t id="813">Following their reconnection to the Commonwealth, OTAS quickly identified the immediate requirement for a new and modern construction ship in order for them to be able to expand outward and compete with the other powers. \n\nStolen in the same attack as many other Argon industrial ships, the Vesuvius is a near exact copy of the Mammoth; OTAS having seen little need to spend time and credits to further refine a humble construction vessel.</t>
	<t id="814">Another design stolen from the Federation following OTAS's reconnection, the Genthus is a twin to the Nomad but with several unseen upgrades and improvements. Previously, OTAS had no need for long range or largescale fleet resuppling given their total control on their cluster of systems. Born more out of necessity than ambition, the Genthus is expected to fufill its role admirably.</t>	
	<t id="815">Despite what the Federation has publicly stated,the Andaman's existence is proof that the rumors of OTAS successfully stealing ship designs was true. A heavily modified and arguably improved variant of the Colossus, OTAS quickly tasked their engineers with "resolving" the issues which they believed Federation engineers were incapable of correcting. Now flaunted openly as if to intentionally incite a hostile response, the Andaman has become a powerful addition to the OTAS fleet.</t>
	<!--iSHIELDS-->
	<t id="900">IG XL - Tempest Internal Generator</t>		
	<t id="901">IG L - Aquilo Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="902">IG L - Astraeus Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="903">IG L - Boreas Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="904">IG L - Mistral Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="905">IG L - Zephyrus Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="906">IG M - Sirokos Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="907">IG M - Skiron Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="908">IG S - Auster Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="909">IG S - Eurus Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="910">IG S - Notus Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="911">IG S - Solano Internal Generator</t>		
	<t id="912">IG S - Venti Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="913">IG XL - Vesuvius Internal Generator</t>	
	<t id="914">IG XL - Genthus Internal Generator</t>		
	<t id="915">IG XL - Andaman Internal Generator</t>			
  </page>		
		
  <page id="19530003" title="Titles" descr="Titles" voice="no">
	<t id="1">System Analyst</t>	
	<t id="2">Reclamation</t>				
  </page>		
  <page id="19530004" title="Ships" descr="Ships" voice="yes">
	<t id="1">A variant configuration of the ubiquitous P, the Y is a heavy bomber fitted with twin torpedo launch tubes capable of deploying the same devastating anti-capital torpedoes of the smaller LX bomber.</t>
	<t id="2">IG M - Y Internal Generator</t>	
	<t id="3">(old) ----  {20403,25}{20403,24}</t>
	<t id="4">The D is an alternative configuration of the standard P hull. Featuring two additional turrets and reinforced hull plating, the prevailing theory is that the D is intended to bolster Xenon anti-fighter capabilities.</t>
	<t id="5">IG M - D Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="6">{20403,9}{20403,24}</t>
	<t id="7">An even more dangerous configuration of the Xenon I, the IX possesses a host of enhancements- an expanded array of main battery turrets, overcharged internal generator, and heavily reinforced hull structure. Thankfully, the ships are a rare sight outside of deeply occupied Xenon sectors and do not appear to be a standard combat configuration used in offensive actions, possibly due to the vast amount of resources required to produce one. All confirmed encounters with the type follow the same pattern: a fleet conducting offensive operations against the Xenon gains the upper hand, pushing deep into Xenon territory. When victory against the local branch matrix seems to be at hand, the situation shifts with the sudden appearance of an IX that swiftly swings the balance of power. \n\nMuch of what is known about the IX is sourced from encounters by the Terran Intervention Corps, with the Terran government being uncharacteristically open and cooperative in sharing intelligence regarding the type. Military analysts have attached the "Reclamation" title to these vessels, concluding that they are a reactive, last-ditch attempt by the Xenon to secure certain "core" sectors under threat, by dedicating all remaining available resources to their production in hopes of re-establishing the local presence once the sector is cleared of hostiles. As the ships have been observed seemingly appearing from nowhere even after the destruction of local Xenon shipbuilding facilities, it is theorized that they are assembled under asteroid cover or heavy sensor jamming fields, utilizing the same in-situ bootstrapped self-assembly technology that has been observed in the construction of Xenon stations.</t>	
	<t id="8">IG XL - IX Internal Generator</t>	
	<t id="9">{20403,12}{20403,24} (LX)</t>	
  </page>
  <!--<page id="19530005" title="N/A" descr="N/A" voice="no"/>-->
  <page id="19530006" title="Weapons" descr="Weapons" voice="no">
	<t id="1">\033#993d7bff#MH\033X Xenon Plasma Bomb</t>
	<t id="2">The Plasma Bomb is a weapon designed to penetrate the shield of a heavier ship to disable its engines and weaponry, or deal direct hull damage. </t>			
  </page>
  
			<!--Reemergence Assets-->
  <page id="19530007" title="Ships" descr="Ships" voice="yes">
	<!--TURRETS/WEAPONS-->
	<t id="200">\033#95e03b29#BMB\033X\ Light Plasma Bomb</t>  
	<t id="201">\033#95e03b29#LM\033X Extended Range PPC</t>
	<t id="202">Target Ranging and Tracking Designator - 22km</t>	
	<t id="203">Target Ranging and Tracking Designator - 30km</t>
	<t id="204">Kitsune Heavy Missile Launcher</t>	
	
	<!--TURRETS/WEAPONS DESCRIPTIONS-->
	<t id="300">Size: SMALL\n Weapon Class: BOMBER\n\nThe Light Plasma Bomb is a standardized, near-universally compatible weapon intended to be fitted to the heavy ordnance hardpoint found on bomber-type attack craft.\n\nA derivative offshoot of the ubiquitous Plasma Cannon technology, the weapon fires a highly unstable ionized plasma mixture held within a transient containment field. Upon impact the projectile loses containment and produces a high-energy flare, causing significant damage to anything unlucky enough to be caught within the sizable blast radius. Though very destructive, the projectiles have an extremely poor velocity and effective range due to containment bleed-off, making the weapon largely ineffective when deployed against anything other than its intended capital-class targets.</t>	
	<t id="301">Size: LARGE\n\nThis modified version of the standard Argon-built Photon Pulse Cannon was developed specifically for use as the primary armament of the Boron Marlin frigate. \n\nThough it uses the same underlying operating principles as the Argon progenitor, the Boron version of the PPC has been re-engineered to fit Boron power architecture and tactical sensibilities, boasting greater engagement distance at the cost of limited gimbal range and incompatibility with non-Boron ship systems.</t> 
	<t id="302">This piece of equipment is used to assist Viper missile frigate captains in maintaining proper distance from their intended targets. \n\nWhile manually operated rangefinding and targeting devices are a primitive solution dating back to pre-spaceflight era, their adoption has been highly effective in curtailing Split captains' tendency to grow bored in their standoff fire support role and demanding that their ship "close with the enemy, so that they may strike them with their blade", by giving them something to do. The additional benefits of slightly reduced target acquisition times and marginally improved terminal guidance are seen as welcome but ultimately unnecessary side effects. </t>	
	<t id="303">A sophisticated target acquisition and tracking suite utilizing a human-in-the-loop advanced long-range recognition system, initially designed for the Kitsune. \n\nThough the early trial versions of the system were fully automated and demonstrated excellent performance, battlefield experience revealed that in the heat of combat, the inability of the crew to directly influence the ship's armament produced a variety of psychological effects that manifested in poor tactical judgement and significantly impaired combat efficiency. By reintroducing the human factor at several critical points of the target engagement process, these issues were eliminated and overall combat effectiveness saw an notable improvement, even in low-pressure trial scenarios.</t>
	<t id="304">The integrated missile launch system designed for the Kitsune, capable of firing Agile and Shield-bypass cruise missiles to ranges of up to 30km.</t>

	<!--VRO description overrides-->
	<t id="400">Properties: Cruise missile | Guided | Swarm | Target-seeking \nAI Launch Range: 24 km \n\nDeveloped specifically for use with Viper's multi-tube launchers, this light cruise missile can deal with most light and medium targets and still be effective versus larger ships. </t>	
	<t id="401">Properties: Cruise missile | Guided | Target-seeking \nAI Launch Range: 32 km \n\nThis cruise missile, launched exlusively by Kitsune missile frigate, is remarkably fast for it's size and payload.</t>
	<t id="402">Properties: Cruise missile | Guided | Target-seeking \nAI Launch Range: 32 km \n\nA heavy cruise missile exclusive to the Kitsune missile frigate. The Shield-Bypass Cruise Missile is more sluggish and possesses a less destrucitve payload than the Agile, but the advanced dual-action warhead allows the weapon to inflict heavy damage against a target with active shields.</t>
	
	<!--SHIPS-->
	  <!-- L carriers -->
	<t id="700">Cheetah</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="701">(Chiba E){20101,62901} {20111,5462}</t>	
	<t id="702">Ariadne</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="703">(Griffon){20101,12201}</t>
	<t id="704">LEAVE EMPTY (teladi spot)</t>
	<t id="705">LEAVE EMPTY (boron spot)</t>
	  <!-- S bombers -->
	<t id="710">Wolf</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="711">(Falchion){20101,61901}</t>
	<t id="722">PAR placeholder</t>
	<t id="713">(Buster){20101,10201}</t>
	<t id="714">Hawk</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="715">(Candiru){20101,52801}</t>	  
	  <!-- frigates -->
	<t id="720">(Marlin){20101,51701}</t>
	<t id="721">Caracal</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="722">Serval</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="723">(Cassowary){20101,22801}</t>	
	  <!-- TMs -->
	<t id="730">Crocodile</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="731">(Scabbard){20101,63301}</t>
	<t id="732">(Helianthus){20101,120901}</t>
	<t id="733">Orthrus</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="734">Jacana</t> <!--AI Voice-->
	<t id="735">(Pleco){20101,51501}</t>
	  <!-- others / misc -->
	<t id="740">BOR BELUGA placeholder</t>
	<t id="741">ALI ARAN placeholder</t>
	<t id="742">(Kagawa){20101,64701}</t>
	  <!-- M corvettes -->
	<t id="750">(Centaur){20101,12801}</t>		  
	  
	<!--SHIP DESCRIPTIONS-->
	  <!-- L carriers -->
	<t id="800">A new development and seldom seen outside of Split space, the Cheetah is a light carrier ostensibly built in a bout of cooperation among the Split Free Families as a more specifically tailored version of the Split Panther. However, observers have noted that the Cheetah's unique capabilities are oddly well-suited to the lightning-fast ambush raids carried out by Fallen Families raiders, and the ship is just as commonly seen wearing Fallen Families colors as it is in Free Families livery, leading to a widely-accepted theory that the ship was in fact built to the specifications of an influential Fallen Families warband. \n\nRegardless of the truth of its origins, the Cheetah itself is an extremely capable raider - boasting an exceptionally high top speed along with an L-class turret hardpoint, a very large fighter capacity, and numerous launch tubes to rapidly surprise and overwhelm a target with fighters. However it is much less capable than its peers when it comes under direct threat, having poor shielding and only a small number of M-class defensive turrets. In addition, the Cheetah is fitted with relatively few landing pads, making it slow to recover its fighter complement. Alongside its limited capacity for self-defense against peer targets, this means that Cheetah captains must remain mindful of not only their attack vectors, but also be constantly planning an exit strategy should the tides of battle turn against them.</t>	
	<t id="801">The Chiba E is the Terran refinement of the Pioneers' original converted design. In a rare display of technological acknowledgement, the Terran Protectorate purchased access to the Chiba's design specifications and soon placed an improved version into service. While the design heritage of the Hokkaido hull remains clearly evident, the Chiba E is built to purpose from the keel up; featuring numerous internal modifications and improvements including expanded fighter-handling facilities and dedicated launch tubes, the ship has greatly improved performance in the light carrier role. \n\nIdentical in function to the original, the Chiba E is commonly seen patrolling Terran space, serving as a a base for local policing efforts or as small task force leaders.</t>	
	<t id="802">Ariadne</t>
	<t id="803">Griffon</t>
	<t id="804">LEAVE EMPTY (teladi spot)</t>
	<t id="805">LEAVE EMPTY (boron spot)</t>
	  <!-- S bombers -->
	<t id="810">The Split Wolf bomber is one of the largest and deadliest S-class combat ships, surpassing even the powerful Chimera. Developed with the assistance of OTAS engineers under a diplomatic effort to cooperate against their enemy, the Argon Federation, the Wolf makes use of technologies first pioneered for the OTAS Notus bomber, adapted for the generally lower Commonwealth technology base. Though relatively slow and a large target, the Wolf has a powerful arsenal of weapons fitted to a heavily reinforced hull, and in numbers presents a formidable threat to capital-class targets of any size. \n\nWith the Wolf demonstrating an integration of OTAS and Commonwealth engineering, the technology soon spread through the Gate Network, with other powers fielding their own bomber-type vessels.</t>
	<t id="811">The Terran Falchion bomber is perhaps the most heavily specialized ship in the class. While broadly identical in strategic function as the Notus and other Commonwealth counterparts, the Falchion does not use any version of the Notus' technology, and was developed and built completely from scratch by Terran engineers. \n\nUnlike other bombers, the Falchion carries no secondary armament to accompany the ordnance hardpoints, and is largely reliant on fighter escorts to clear the battlespace. In exchange, the ship presents a very small target profile and possesses robust shielding, maximizing its survivability against its capital sized targets. </t>
	<t id="822">PAR placeholder</t>
	<t id="813">Designed, built, and put into service with staggering and uncharacteristic alacrity by the Argon Federation Navy, the Buster is the result of Argon efforts to swiftly close the capabilities gap posed by the OTAS Notus and Split Wolf bombers. \n\nUnlike many of its peers, the Buster as a combat machine is wholly unremarkable: lacking the configurable multi-missile launchers found on the Notus, backing up it's single bomber-class hardpoint with a pair of conventional light weapons mounts and featuring a singular shield projector, the ship trades individual power for expedience in service and an exceptionally low production cost.\n\nThanks to the Argon Navy's numerous external threats and competing priorities, it has thus far maintained that "the ship you have now is better than a ship you might have next year" and the Buster has remained in service with no replacement in sight despite its various shortcomings, much to the annoyance of its pilots. Many common jokes within Argon Buster squadrons pointedly highlight the attractiveness of the ship's low cost of production and operation to the Argon civilian government, laced with macabre punchlines wondering how many Busters must be destroyed before it becomes economically advantageous to develop an improved ship. However, this same affordability has resulted in the Buster finding a surprisingly successful market among small independent mercenary outfits or private security firms, where the ship represents a very cheap opportunity to augment marketable capabilities.</t>
	<t id="814">Hawk</t> 
	<t id="815">BOR placeholder</t>	  
	  <!-- frigates -->
	<t id="820">A cooperative effort between Boron and Argon engineers, the Marlin is a frigate built with lessons learned from encounters with Split and Xenon forces following the reconnection of Boron space to the wider Commonwealth. Having identified a need for heavier anti-capital firepower than that provided by the larger Ray, the Marlin is designed with a unique (among Boron vessels) primary weapon hardpoint capable of mounting the powerful Argon Photon Pulse Cannon. Coupled with its small size and reduced price compared to a full destroyer, a squadron of Marlins can match the firepower of much larger vessels and overwhelm otherwise superior foes while maintaining cost parity.\n\nBased on a heavily redesigned version of their previous Sturgeon hull, the Marlin represents a surprising breakthrough success for the nascent Stellar Shores Shipping company, providing their first foothold in the highly competitive military procurement market and placing them solidly in line with their older, more established corporate peers.</t>
	<t id="821">Caracal</t>
	<t id="822">Serval</t>
	<t id="823">One of the more unusual ships produced by the Teladi Company, the Cassowary frigate is something of an engineering and marketing oddity. Abruptly released to the market with little fanfare shortly after the launch of the Heron E, critical observers have noted the ship's resemblance to a truncated forward dome section of the larger Heron freighter. The Teladi Company has vehemently denied allegations that the Cassowary is simply a repurposed Heron hull section that suffered structural failure during construction, with one Teladi Company spokesperson being quoted as saying that "The front section did not 'fall off' of anything! If anything, the Cassowary IS the front!". The Teladi Company has since distanced itself from the quoted official and has not acknowledged any requests for clarification.\n\nUnusual appearance notwithstanding, the Cassowary is an uncharacteristically well-armed offering in the Teladi catalogue. Boasting no less than three large turret hardpoints and protected by two large shield projectors, the ship is a superlative standout in the frigate class, though it is notably lacking in point-defense armament compared to its peers and suffers from a significant aft blindspot due to the unique hull layout.</t>
	  <!-- TMs -->
	<t id="830">A class of ship that fell out of favour during the Shutdown-Era, TM-class Military Transports serve dual roles as well-defended couriers of sensitive cargo and as cost-effective solutions for low-intensity patrol and police duties.\n\nThough they were largely unneeded during the isolation of the Gate Shutdown, the class was reintroduced following the Reconnection to alleviate the increased pressure placed on military forces by the rise in inter-faction tensions and Xenon activity, replacing frontline-capable combat units in second-line roles. Traditionally built on a modified civilian transport hull, TM-class vessels sacrifice a large portion of their cargo capacity in exchange for handling and servicing equipment to support a small wing of fighters. Rather than traditional docking pads, TMs are fitted with short range graviton tractor beam arrays to hold docked fighters in place, using a standard service umbilical to transfer crew between vessels rather than maintaining an "open-space" atmospheric envelope. Though this allows TMs to carry a large number of parasite fighters for their size, the lack of internal storage bays means that the externally-docked fighters are vulnerable to damage and the ship can only realistically support as many fighters as it can dock. \n\nThe Split-built Crocodile is one of the smallest ships in the class, though it still manages to land a wing of four heavy fighters and features the aggressive speed common to Split designs.</t>
	<t id="831">TM</t>
	<t id="832">A class of ship that fell out of favour during the Shutdown-Era, TM-class Military Transports serve dual roles as well-defended couriers of sensitive cargo and as cost-effective solutions for low-intensity patrol and police duties.\n\nThough they were largely unneeded during the isolation of the Gate Shutdown, the class was reintroduced following the Reconnection to alleviate the increased pressure placed on military forces by the rise in inter-faction tensions and Xenon activity, replacing frontline-capable combat units in second-line roles. Traditionally built on a modified civilian transport hull, TM-class vessels sacrifice a large portion of their cargo capacity in exchange for handling and servicing equipment to support a small wing of fighters. Rather than traditional docking pads, TMs are fitted with short range graviton tractor beam arrays to hold docked fighters in place, using a standard service umbilical to transfer crew between vessels rather than maintaining an "open-space" atmospheric envelope. Though this allows TMs to carry a large number of parasite fighters for their size, the lack of internal storage bays means that the externally-docked fighters are vulnerable to damage and the ship can only realistically support as many fighters as it can dock. \n\nThe Paranid Helianthus is a fairly minimal modification of the Demeter, simply extending the chassis and replacing many of the outer-hull storage units with an array of micro-tractor emitters. Though lightly armed, like its transporter ancestor the Helianthus boasts improved shielding and excellent mobility.</t>
	<t id="833">A class of ship that fell out of favour during the Shutdown-Era, TM-class Military Transports serve dual roles as well-defended couriers of sensitive cargo and as cost-effective solutions for low-intensity patrol and police duties.\n\nThough they were largely unneeded during the isolation of the Gate Shutdown, the class was reintroduced following the Reconnection to alleviate the increased pressure placed on military forces by the rise in inter-faction tensions and Xenon activity, replacing frontline-capable combat units in second-line roles. Traditionally built on a modified civilian transport hull, TM-class vessels sacrifice a large portion of their cargo capacity in exchange for handling and servicing equipment to support a small wing of fighters. Rather than traditional docking pads, TMs are fitted with short range graviton tractor beam arrays to hold docked fighters in place, using a standard service umbilical to transfer crew between vessels rather than maintaining an "open-space" atmospheric envelope. Though this allows TMs to carry a large number of parasite fighters for their size, the lack of internal storage bays means that the externally-docked fighters are vulnerable to damage and the ship can only realistically support as many fighters as it can dock. \n\nThe Argon Orthrus is in many ways the archetypical example of the class, with average shielding and mobility backed up by a pair of M-class turrets for self defense, supporting a wing of four fighters.</t>
	<t id="834">A class of ship that fell out of favour during the Shutdown-Era, TM-class Military Transports serve dual roles as well-defended couriers of sensitive cargo and as cost-effective solutions for low-intensity patrol and police duties.\n\nThough they were largely unneeded during the isolation of the Gate Shutdown, the class was reintroduced following the Reconnection to alleviate the increased pressure placed on military forces by the rise in inter-faction tensions and Xenon activity, replacing frontline-capable combat units in second-line roles. Traditionally built on a modified civilian transport hull, TM-class vessels sacrifice a large portion of their cargo capacity in exchange for handling and servicing equipment to support a small wing of fighters. Rather than traditional docking pads, TMs are fitted with short range graviton tractor beam arrays to hold docked fighters in place, using a standard service umbilical to transfer crew between vessels rather than maintaining an "open-space" atmospheric envelope. Though this allows TMs to carry a large number of parasite fighters for their size, the lack of internal storage bays means that the externally-docked fighters are vulnerable to damage and the ship can only realistically support as many fighters as it can dock. \n\nThe Teladi Jacana boasts above-average shielding, hull integrity and cargo capacity, though it possesses the typically below-average mobility and poor armament found on civilian Teladi designs.</t>
	<t id="835">A class of ship that fell out of favour during the Shutdown-Era, TM-class Military Transports serve dual roles as well-defended couriers of sensitive cargo and as cost-effective solutions for low-intensity patrol and police duties.\n\nThough they were largely unneeded during the isolation of the Gate Shutdown, the class was reintroduced following the Reconnection to alleviate the increased pressure placed on military forces by the rise in inter-faction tensions and Xenon activity, replacing frontline-capable combat units in second-line roles. Traditionally built on a modified civilian transport hull, TM-class vessels sacrifice a large portion of their cargo capacity in exchange for handling and servicing equipment to support a small wing of fighters. Rather than traditional docking pads, TMs are fitted with short range graviton tractor beam arrays to hold docked fighters in place, using a standard service umbilical to transfer crew between vessels rather than maintaining an "open-space" atmospheric envelope. Though this allows TMs to carry a large number of parasite fighters for their size, the lack of internal storage bays means that the externally-docked fighters are vulnerable to damage and the ship can only realistically support as many fighters as it can dock. \n\nFurther building on the success of the Dolphin transporter, the Pleco is a result of a joint effort between Atreus Shipbuilding Currents and Stellar Shores Shipping to develop a mid-size TM-type vessel. Though using the same grav-harness docking technology as most TMs, the unique hull form and docking arrangement of the Pleco allows it to carry no less than six parasite fighters, giving it a distinct edge in offensive capabilities compared to its peers, despite its poor speed. Coupled with the characteristically sturdy Boron shielding, the Pleco makes for a far more dangerous opponent than its spindly appearance and unassuming name might suggest.</t>
	  <!-- others / misc -->
	<t id="840">BOR BELUGA placeholder</t>
	<t id="841">ARAN placeholder</t>
	<t id="842">One of the largest ships found in Terran space, the Pioneer-built Kagawa is a freighter vessel of truly mammoth proportions. Rivaling the Terran Asgard battleship in sheer size and mass, the Kagawa features one of the largest cargo-handling capacities found anywhere in the Gate Network.\n\nFollowing the reconnection of the Althes and Megnir jumpgates, and the ensuing massive military and humanitarian efforts to secure those sectors against Xenon assault, the engineers of the Pioneer Initiative were tasked with preparing an ultraheavy transport vessel capable of ferrying enormous amounts of humanitarian supplies or necessary war materiel that might be needed if a route was discovered to the final lost colony of Aldrin. The advent of Project Genesis terraforming efforts expedited development of the Kagawa, with the sheer scale of resources demanded by the terraforming process promising a steady demand for such large transports.</t>	
	  <!-- M corvettes -->
	<t id="850">As the first highly-anticipated combat-line product launched by the post-shutdown reconsolidated Jonferson Space Dynamics Division, the Mk3 Centaur is a dramatic return to the ship's roots as a fast, aggressive corvette-class striker. Designed in a bid to produce a ship capable of matching or exceeding the capabilities of the venerable Terran Katana, the ship boasts a formidable array of forward weaponry, good all-around turret coverage and fighter-like agility, though this comes at the cost of a light-duty hull structure and somewhat mediocre overall protection. \n\nWith the newly-reformed company holding a tenuous financial position, it was a deliberate decision by Jonferco designers to recall the classic Argon design in a bid for a knockout market entrance. Though the Centaur fell somewhat short of the impossibly lofty expectations set upon it by Jonferco executive leadership, the ship proved a commercial and military success, being well liked by its users and earning a particular popularity with the semi-independent Special Action Task Forces of the Argon and Antigone navies.</t>	

	<!--iSHIELDS-->
	  <!-- L carriers -->
	<t id="900">IG L - Cheetah Internal Generator</t>	
	<t id="901">IG L - Chiba E Internal Generator</t>	
	<t id="902">IG L - Ariadne Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="903">IG L - Griffon Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="904">IG L - LEAVE EMPTY (teladi spot)</t>
	<t id="905">IG L - LEAVE EMPTY (boron spot)</t>
	  <!-- S bombers -->
	<t id="910">IG S - Wolf Internal Shield Generator</t>
	<t id="911">IG S - Falchion Internal Shield Generator</t>
	<t id="922">IG S - PAR placeholder Internal Shield Generator</t>
	<t id="913">IG S - Buster Internal Shield Generator</t>
	<t id="914">IG S - Hawk Internal Shield Generator</t> 
	<t id="915">IG S - BOR placeholder Internal Shield Generator</t>	  
	  <!-- frigates -->
	<t id="920">IG L - Marlin Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="921">IG L - Caracal Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="922">IG L - Serval Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="923">IG L - Cassowary Internal Generator</t>
	  <!-- TMs -->
	<t id="930">IG M - TM Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="931">IG M - TM Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="932">IG M - TM Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="933">IG M - TM Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="934">IG M - TM Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="935">IG M - TM Internal Generator</t>
	  <!-- others / misc -->
	<t id="940">IG XL - Beluga Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="941">IG XL - Aran Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="942">IG XL - Kagawa Internal Generator</t>
	  <!-- M corvettes -->
	<t id="950">IG M - Centaur Internal Shield Generator</t>

	<!--STATIONS-->
<!--<t id="1000"></t>-->	
    <t id="1000">Haven</t>
    <t id="1001">{20006,102}(No information available)</t>	
    <t id="1002">(Yaki S Haven){20203,2801} {20111,5011} {19530007,1000}</t>
    <t id="1003">(Yaki M Haven){20203,2801} {20111,5021} {19530007,1000}</t>
    <t id="1004">(Yaki L Haven){20203,2801} {20111,5031} {19530007,1000}</t>
    <t id="1005">Den</t>	
    <t id="1006">(Scaleplate S Den){20203,1001} {20111,5011} {19530007,1005}</t>
    <t id="1007">(Scaleplate M Den){20203,1001} {20111,5021} {19530007,1005}</t>
    <t id="1008">(Scaleplate L Den){20203,1001} {20111,5031} {19530007,1005}</t>	
	<!--MISC-->
	<t id="1100">{20111,5302} {20101,100401}(Standard Defence Drone)</t>
	<t id="11001">The product of a joint Argon-Teladi venture to produce a new generation of cheap defence drone following the Gate Reconnection, the Universal Standard-Armaments Semi-Autonomous Fighter Drone - more commonly referred to as the Commonwealth Standard defence drone, or simply the Standard - is a massive commercial and military success that can be found both in service and available for sale throughout every corner of settled space. \n\nThough the design has begun to significantly show its age in the modern battlespace and brings very little in the way of individual combat power, decades of design maturation and manufacturing refinements have driven the cost of the Standard down to practically nothing, letting even the most cash-strapped freighter captain freely deploy them in bulk as disposable countermeasures against pirate attack. This has ensured the continued popularity of the Standard despite its perceived obsolescence in frontline military use.</t>	
	<t id="1101">{20202,601} {20101,100401}(Xenon Defence Drone)</t>
	<t id="11011">Little is known about the Xenon defence drone beyond the proven fact that it is tactically superior to any of its counterparts. Beyond being larger, more robust and having better armament, Xenon AGI systems also ensure the drone is smarter and meaner than any other drone system. A swarm of Xenon drones can swiftly bring down an underprepared foe of any size and present a formidable obstacle when contesting battlespace control of Xenon-occupied systems.</t>	
	<t id="1102">Keris Defence Drone(Terran)</t>
	<t id="11021">The modern incarnation of Terran Keris defence drone is a powerful and advanced semiautomonous weapons system. Though somewhat slower than its Commonwealth counterparts, the Keris presents a reduced target profile and possesses superior armament in the form of a standard Terran Pulse Cannon.</t>	
	<t id="1103">Krill Defence Drone(Boron)</t>
	<t id="11031">Designed in a bid to reduce casualty risk to fighter pilots, the Krill defense drone is a very agile drone armed with a single Ion Gatling. \n\nAccording to Boron fleet doctrine, correct usage of the Krill drone in a coordinated fleet action sees it deployed in large numbers alongside manned fighters, using its physical presence to distract enemy fire and the engine-disrupting properties of the Ion Gatling to pull apart enemy formations, thus allowing crewed fighters to deliver decisive tactical strikes in relative safety.</t>	
	<t id="1104">Skink Defence Drone(Split)</t>
	<t id="11041">A highly conventional application of Split combat philosophy, the Split-designed Skink defence drone is extremely fast and mounts a deadly Tau Accelerator as the main weapon system, giving it an unexpected edge in combat when facing larger targets.</t>	
	<t id="1105">Cupid Defence Drone(Paranid)</t>
	<t id="11051">As much a product of cultural dogma as one of military necessity, the Paranid Cupid defence drone was initially designed by the Holy Order to both provide their forces with a combat advantage and to free their captains from the perceived shame of relying on the heretical Standard drone. The Holy Order enjoyed a brief period of drone superiority before the design was acquired by the Godrealm, which swiftly adopted the system and began to field their own copy. \n\nArmed with a scaled-down version of the Paranid Railgun system, the Cupid gives Paranid forces a unique form of offensive support.</t>
	<t id="1106">Sparrow Defence Drone(Teladi)</t>
	<t id="11061">DESCRIPTION KEYWORDS: RUGGED, SURVIVABLE, ONLY ARMED WITH Impulse Ray Emitter, BUT WELL SHIELDED</t>
	<t id="1107">{20111,5302} {20101,100401} mk2(Argon)</t>
	<t id="11071">DESCRIPTION KEYWORDS: the II is Arg's bid to recreate the success but too little too late with factions having developed their own. ARMED WITH PAC, better speed and mobility</t>
  </page>	
  
  <page id="19530201" title="Skull+Bones" descr="pirates" voice="yes">	
	<t id="100">YAR HAR ME BOY'OS</t>
	<!--TURRETS/WEAPONS-->
	<t id="200">Incendiary Bomb Launcher</t>
	<t id="201">\033#95e03b29#BMB\033X\ Incendiary Bomb Mortar</t>	  
	<t id="202">Burst Ray Turret</t>
	<t id="203">Rail Slugger Turret</t>	  	 
	<!--TURRETS/WEAPONS DESCRIPTIONS-->
	<t id="300">\033#95e03b29#L Turret\033X\ \nUnable to easily gain possession of high-tech capital ship weapons, pirate engineers designed the Incendiary Bomb Launcher as an easily producible alternative. With the name being in use for nearly a century, each iteration of the IBL is based on the design of a contemporary weapon and shares little in common with its predecessor, aside from the basic mode of operation and effect on target. The modern IBL is essentially just a massively scaled up and mildly deconstructed Plasma Cannon, hurling massive balls of high-energy plasma that destabilize and explode on impact. This explosion deals significant damage across a wide blast radius and momentarily leaves behind a burning reside that can damage the hulls of shielded targets, though the unstable nature of the projectile somewhat limits the IBL's effective range compared to similarly sized weapons.\n\nCuriously, neither of the IBL's secondary effects are intentional- in a bid to reduce the power demands of the weapon, a variety of features dedicated to safety and reliability were stripped from the Plasma Cannon design, though the negative effects of such a move are clearly of little interest to the pirates.</t>	
	<t id="301">Size: SMALL\n Weapon Class: BOMBER\n\nThe Incendiary Bomb Mortar is a miniaturized version of capital-sized Incendiary Bomb Launcher. Just like the larger counterpart, the IBM throws unstable plasma projectiles that explode on impact and briefly leave a burning residue that can damage the hull of a shielded vessel. While it offers a remarkable amount of firepower for its size, the lack of a capital-grade power supply drastically limits the projectile's maximum range and velocity.</t>	  
	<t id="302">As its name suggests, the Yaki Burst Ray turret incorporates the same phased-wavelength technology found on the standard fixed-mount Burst Ray. Much like the progenitor technology, the Burst Ray turret deals extra damage against exposed hull and surface components, and can partially bypass active shield layers, though this comes at the cost of a reduction in maximum effective range- a tradeoff deemed necessary in order to enhance their raiders' ability to swiftly overwhelm and disable targets when making forays through hostile space.</t>
	<t id="303">The Yaki Rail Slugger turret is a straightfoward modification, mounting a Paranid-designed Rail Slugger onto a medium-class turret mount. Though it has extremely poor tracking capability, the weapon boasts a best-in-class effective range and lethally fast projectiles, giving Yaki raiders an extremely effective armament to harrass targets while on the offensive or covering rear arcs to deter pursuers.</t>		  
	<!--STATION MODULES-->
	<t id="400">PLACEHOLDER</t>
	<!--SHIPS-->
	<t id="700">Galleon</t>
	<t id="701">Blastclaw</t>
	<t id="702">Brigantine</t>	
	<t id="703">Carrack</t>
	<t id="704">Marauder</t> 	
	<!--SHIP DESCRIPTIONS-->
	<t id="800">Scale Plate pirates have long been rumored offer a premium to employ Teladi builders for remote jobs, only to commandeer their vessels after the work is complete. While the majority of these captured construction ships are swiftly broken up for scrap to turn a quick credit and recoup costs, recent shifts in internal culture of the Scale Plate Pact have resulted in a different fate for some of the vessels. The growing trend of organization and cooperation among Pact pirates has led to the emergence of pirate warlords, commanding of large fleets of roaming marauders seeking to leave their mark on the galactic stage. In an apparent bid to recall the old legends of pre-shutdown pirate might, some captured Albatross builders have resurfaced as massive pirate scavenger-carriers, heavily modified but clearly recognizable, serving as flagships for the most successful pirate warlords. Dubbed the Galleon, these ad-hoc warships are a rare sight despite the proliferation of the Pact- a testament to the difficulty of procuring such a vessel given the unruly nature of pirate warbands and the significantly limited resources available to the pirates. \n\nWith its primary purpose being to visually demonstrate the power of their warlord-captains, the Galleon eschews defensive measures, with only modest shielding for its class and no point defense emplacements. In exchange, the ship boasts one of the heaviest armaments of any Commonwealth vessel: a formidable battery of 12 large turrets, often fitted with an eclectic loadout of whatever was on hand at the time, supported by abundant internal hangar space and numerous small ship landing pads. Beyond it's own capabilities, a Galleon is also inevitably accompanied by a full warband of pirates- motley swarms containing any number of attending vessels of all sizes. The arrival of a Galleon-led Warlord fleet presents a grave threat to any civilian or military asset in the system, and those few examples that are successfully wrested away from pirate control are jealously guarded trophies. </t>
	<t id="801">Another revived design borne of the increasing cooperation within the Scale Plate Pact, the Blastclaw bomber is a remarkably capable ship and is a common sight in among larger pirate flotillas, both escorting larger vessels and operating as an independent strike wing. \n\nThough rather slow, the ship is well-shielded and features a heavily reinforced hull. However, the true strength of the bomber lies in the Incendiary Bomb Mortar mounted under the cockpit, capable of rapidly blasting away exposed surface elements and weakening shielded hulls. Even a single Blastclaw poses a deadly threat to poorly defended freighters, while a sufficient number of them can even challenge and disarm a destroyer, leaving it disabled and vulnerable to boarding actions undertaken by larger ships.</t>	
	<t id="802">One of the larger threats in regular use by the Scale Plate Pact, the Brigantine is a heavily armed capital ship that can pose a significant threat even to military forces. Found almost anywhere that Scale Plate pirates operate and fulfilling any role demanded of it from solo raider to warband leader, the ship's pervasive presence in pirate fleets is owed primarily to its relative ease of acquisition. As many observers have concluded from it's appearance, the Brigantine is cobbled together by pirate shipwrights using the hull sections of Teladi auxiliary ships and carriers- scavenged from battlefield wrecks, decommissioned hulks and even the occasional captured prize. As with the Galleon, rumors abound of the Scale Plate Pact employing less overt means of acquiring these hulls through independent purchasers or unscrupulous Teladi officials, though the Teladi Company vehemently denies the rumors as slander and the Pact remains characteristically cagey with its secrets. \n\nIn the battlespace, the Brigantine employs a typically mismatched grab bag of weaponry and shielding, with the pirates making up what they lack in sophistication and planning with enthusiasm and sheer volume of fire. A handful of docking pads and launch tubes- remnants of the original ships that make up the hull- allows the Brigantine to deploy and support a small wing of fighters or drones to bolster its already-formidable firepower, while cavernous cargo capacity alleviates any need to be picky with plundered loot. Even the sheer imposing size of the vessel offers another weapon in the form of a menacing intimidation factor against civilian freighters. However, the design has numerous flaws as well- the nature of the Brigantine's construction leaves it with a weak hull structure for a ship of its size, a problem made worse by the relatively limited shielding and subpar speed. The substantial armament is also widely distributed across the hull, leaving few blind spots but in turn greatly degrading the ship's ability to concentrate fire on a target.</t>
	<t id="803">CARRACK DESCR</t>
	<t id="804">Another of the Scale Plate Pact's homegrown designs, the Marauder corvette was first created in an act of desperation by a mechanically inclined Pact captain whose Minotaur Raider had been crippled in a raid gone awry. Though he managed to limp back to a hidden freeport, survival was only the first of his problems. Financially destitute, with a shattered ship and a crew on the verge of desertion, the captain - one Iljorgawas Minanoros Ioannis XII - noticed that although the central section of his Minotaur was little more than twisted scrap, the critical forward control and the aft machinery sections were still mostly intact. Struck by a flash of inspiration, he managed to cajole a little more faith from his crew and spent the next several days cutting out the damaged central section of his ship and reconnecting the two remaining portions. A few modifications later, he and his crew once again headed out in what would become the template design for the Marauder. \n\nAs the smallest medium-class ship currently found in the Gate Network, the Marauder specializes in attacking smaller foes while running from larger ones with its good agility and comparatively high speed. A varied collection of armaments - a pair of M-class fixed mounts, a single M-class turret, and four S-class fixed mounts thrown in for good measure - gives the ship good striking power against small transporters or enemy fighters, while the surprisingly capacious cargo storage for its size allows SCA freebooters to haul home their spoils. In exchange, the poor shielding, somewhat questionable hull strength, and anemic armament for its weight class leaves the ship with unfavorable odds when facing other corvettes or even a particularly ornery heavy fighter pilot. Nonetheless, its low operating costs and cheap construction price(often made cheaper through the use of written-off Minotaurs, like the original) ensure its place as a mainstay among the Scale Plate Pact pirates.</t>
	<!--iSHIELDS-->
	<t id="900">IG XL - Galleon Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="901">IG S - Blastclaw Internal Generator</t>	
	<t id="902">IG L - Brigantine Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="903">IG L - Carrack Internal Generator</t>
	<t id="904">IG M - Marauder Internal Generator</t>
  </page>  

  <page id="19530010" title="Corporations" descr="Corporations" voice="yes">
	<t id="1">Jonferco</t>
	<t id="1000">Jonferco Desc</t>	
	<t id="2">JSDD</t>
	<t id="3">Strong Arms</t>
	<t id="3000">Strong Arms Desc</t>	
	<t id="4">STR</t>	
	<t id="5">NMMC</t>
	<t id="5000">NMMC Desc</t>	
	<t id="6">NMMC</t>	
	<t id="7">Atreus Shipbuilding</t>
	<t id="7000">Atreus Desc</t>	
	<t id="8">ASC</t>	
	<t id="9">Intervention Corps</t>	
	<t id="9000">Intervention Desc</t>		
	<t id="10">ATF</t>		
	<t id="11">Jonferco Capital Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="12">Jonferco Capital Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="13">Strong Arms Capital Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="14">Strong Arms Capital Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="15">NMMC Capital Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="16">NMMC Capital Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="17">Atreus Capital Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="18">Atrues Capital Ship Licence</t>	
	<t id="19">ATF Capital Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="20">ATF Capital Ship Licence</t>	
	<t id="21">Jonferco Professional</t>
	<t id="22">Jonferco Master Chief</t>
	<t id="23">Strong Arms Warrior</t>
	<t id="24">Security Protector</t>
	<t id="25">NMMC Specialist</t>
	<t id="26">NMMC Profiteer</t>
	<t id="27">Atreus Broker</t>
	<t id="28">Atrues Protector</t>
	<t id="29">ATF Recruit</t>
	<t id="30">ATF Sergeant</t>	
	<t id="31">Jonferco General Use Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="32">Jonferco General Use Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="33">Strong Arms General Use Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="34">Strong Arms General Use Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="35">NMMC General Use Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="36">NMMC General Use Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="37">Atreus General Use Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="38">Atreus General Use Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="39">ATF General Use Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="40">ATF General Use Ship Licence</t>	
	<t id="41">Jonferco Military Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="42">Jonferco Military Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="43">Strong Arms Military Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="44">Strong Arms Military Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="45">NMMC Military Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="46">NMMC Military Ship Licence</t>		
	<t id="47">Atreus Military Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="48">Atreus Military Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="49">ATF Military Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="50">ATF Military Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="51">Jonferco Police Licence</t>
	<t id="52">Strong Arms Police Licence</t>
	<t id="53">NMMC Police Licence</t>
	<t id="54">Atreus Police Licence</t>
	<t id="55">ATF Police Licence</t>		
	<t id="56">Jonferco Capital Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="57">Jonferco Ancillary Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="58">Strong Arms Capital Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="59">Strong Arms Ancillary Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="60">NMMC Capital Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="61">NMMC Ancillary Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="62">Atreus Capital Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="63">Atreus Ancillary Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="64">ATF Capital Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="65">ATF Ancillary Ship Building Module Licence</t>	
	<t id="66">Jonferco Advanced Module Licence</t>
	<t id="67">Jonferco Basic Module Licence</t>
	<t id="68">Jonferco Intermediate Module Licence</t>
	<t id="69">Jonferco Trade Offer Subscription</t>
	<t id="70">Strong Arms Advanced Module Licence</t>
	<t id="71">Strong Arms Basic Module Licence</t>
	<t id="72">Strong Arms Intermediate Module Licence</t>
	<t id="73">Strong Arms Trade Offer Subscription</t>
	<t id="74">NMMC Advanced Module Licence</t>
	<t id="75">NMMC Basic Module Licence</t>
	<t id="76">NMMC Intermediate Module Licence</t>
	<t id="77">NMMC Trade Offer Subscription</t>
	<t id="78">Atreus Advanced Module Licence</t>
	<t id="79">Atreus Basic Module Licence</t>
	<t id="80">Atreus Intermediate Module Licence</t>
	<t id="81">Atreus Trade Offer Subscription</t>
	<t id="82">ATF Advanced Module Licence</t>
	<t id="83">ATF Basic Module Licence</t>
	<t id="84">ATF Intermediate Module Licence</t>
	<t id="85">ATF Trade Offer Subscription</t>	
	<t id="86">Jonferco Ship Sale Contract</t>	  
	<t id="87">Strong Arms Ship Sale Contract</t>	  
	<t id="88">NMMC Ship Sale Contract</t>	  
	<t id="89">Atreus Ship Sale Contract</t>	  
	<t id="90">ATF Ship Sale Contract</t>	  	
  </page>   
  
  <page id="19530011" title="Xaar's Faithful" descr="Xaar" voice="yes">
	<t id="1">Xaar's Faithful</t>
	<t id="1000">Cut off from the Empire's leadership, and with much of the local religious structure lost in a freak navigational accident, the Paranid inhabitants of Wretched Skies spent much of the Shutdown building an unusual bond of blood with their Split neighbors through constant violent clashes. \n\nStrangely, the influence of the Split had something of a stabilizing effect on these leaderless Paranid; rather than descending into madness or despondence, the Paranid of Wretched Skies rallied around a new doctrine that combined scattered elements of the traditional Paranid mythos with the brutal tenets of Split culture. Once the Gates reopened, this earned them the respect of the Split Patriarch, but also the enmity of both the Godrealm and the Holy Order, a position which is held mutually by the Faithful. Unlike the Holy Order, they are much less concerned about the heresies of the "lesser races" and maintain generally nonhostile, if somewhat chilly, relationships with most other Commonwealth powers. \n\nThe fanatical beliefs of Xaar's Faithful are simple, straightforward, and impossibly heretical to the larger Paranid factions. According to the Faithful, the continued absence of Paranid Prime from the known Gate Network is no mere accident. They hold that the Priest-Emperor has shrouded the system from sight, biding his time in the darkness between the stars as a trial laid upon all Paranid, and that he someday will return to lead the Paranid people once more: embracing those who remained devoted, rewarding those who took up arms in his name, and cleansing all apostates with holy fire. As was decreed fitting of their position as subservient to the Priest-Emperor, no Paranid of Xaar's Faithful may hold a title above Deacon, and thus Xaarist affairs are generally directed by the "Deacon Triumvirate" - a triplet of councils representing the dogmatic pillars of Belief in Xaar, Force of Arms, and Mundanity of Life.</t>
	<t id="2">XAAR</t>	
	<t id="3">Xaar Capital Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="4">Xaar Capital Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="5">Xaar Apostle</t>
	<t id="6">Xaar Adherent</t>	
	<t id="7">Xaar General Use Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="8">Xaar General Use Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="9">Xaar Military Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="10">Xaar Military Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="11">Xaar Police Licence</t>	
	<t id="12">Xaar Capital Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="13">Xaar Ancillary Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="14">Xaar Advanced Module Licence</t>
	<t id="15">Xaar Basic Module Licence</t>
	<t id="16">Xaar Intermediate Module Licence</t>
	<t id="17">Xaar Trade Offer Subscription</t>
	<t id="18">Xaar Ship Sale Contract</t>	 	
  </page>		

  <page id="19530102" title="Aldrin Colony" descr="Aldrin" voice="yes">	
	<t id="1">Aldrin Colony</t>
	<t id="1000">desc</t>	
	<t id="2">ALD</t>	
	<t id="3">Aldrin Capital Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="4">Aldrin Capital Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="5">Friend of the Colony</t>
	<t id="6">Hero of Aldrin</t>	
	<t id="7">Aldrin General Use Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="8">Aldrin General Use Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="9">Aldrin Military Equipment Licence</t>
	<t id="10">Aldrin Military Ship Licence</t>
	<t id="11">Aldrin Police Licence</t>	
	<t id="12">Aldrin Capital Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="13">Aldrin Ancillary Ship Building Module Licence</t>
	<t id="14">Aldrin Advanced Module Licence</t>
	<t id="15">Aldrin Basic Module Licence</t>
	<t id="16">Aldrin Intermediate Module Licence</t>
	<t id="17">Aldrin Trade Offer Subscription</t>
	<t id="18">Aldrin Ship Sale Contract</t>		
  </page>  
  
  <page id="19530025" title="Email" descr="Emails" voice="no"> 
	<t id="1">(Title)You've got mail!</t>
	<t id="2">(Source/From:)GalNet</t>	
	<t id="3">(Text)We've been trying to reach you regarding your ships's extended warranty!</t>  
	<t id="4">(Signature)\n\nKel Rova\n- Executive Sales Representative, Windfall Insurance LLC</t>  	
  </page>

  <page id="199430204" title="NMMC Trade Guild" descr="Texts for the NMMC Trade Guild mission group and sub-mission variants" voice="no">
	<t id="1">(missiongroup)NMMC Trade Guild</t>
	<t id="2">The well known and respected NMMC Trade Guild is always looking for skilled and proven traders to bolster our ranks. You have caught our attention and we wish to extend this invitation to you. If you are interested, please meet with me.</t>
	<t id="3">NMMC Trade Guild Office</t>
	<t id="200">(Character Entity Titles)</t>
	<t id="201">Guild Membership Salesman</t>
	<t id="202">Guild Membership Saleswoman</t>
	<t id="300">(Mails)</t>
	<t id="301">(Mail Greeting){30005,1001}</t>
	<t id="302">(Mail Signature)$TITLE$\n{199430204,1}</t>
	<t id="310">(Mail Title){199430204,1} - Trade Guild Invitation</t>
	<t id="311">(Mail Content){199430204,2}</t>
	<t id="3000">(title variants)Problematic Obstacles</t>
	<t id="3100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="3101">The path to profit often is a treacherous one, with both natural and artificial obstacles along the way. We at the NMMC Trade Guild believe that a proactive stance is needed to both protect our assets and clients as well as discourage any heinous acts against us.</t>
	<t id="3102">Those who wish to make a profit can never help the natural and artificial obstacles that may stand in their way. That, however, does not mean that these obstacles cannot be overcome, and we believe that an active approach to dealing with these obstacles is necessary to protect both our assets and our clients.</t>
	<t id="3110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="3111">We need a number of pilots to go out and deal with a number of potentially dangerous situations.</t>
	<t id="3112">We are looking for experienced pilots capable of dealing with these problematic issues.</t>
	<t id="4000">(title variants)Increase Portfolio</t>
	<t id="4100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="4101">The NMMC Trade Guild is looking to expand its operations and influence in the local area. To do so, we must find opportunities to expand and act on them.</t>
	<t id="4102">A stagnant operation is an unprofitable one, which is why the NMMC Trade Guild is looking to expand our presence in a number of areas.</t>
	<t id="4110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="4111">A trusted business partner is requested to help us identify such opportunities and potentially provide assets to take advantage of them.</t>
	<t id="4112">We need a versatile and skilled partner to act in the interests of the NMMC Trade Guild to help us in this endeavour.</t>
	<t id="5000">(title variants)Help Trade Operation</t>
	<t id="5100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="5101">An organisation as large and far-reaching as the NMMC Trade Guild will often run into mundane issues which limit its profitability. Should these issues never be addressed, it may well lead to financial loss. This is unspeakable.</t>
	<t id="5102">We at the NMMC Trade Guild pride ourselves on managing a vast network of traders and leading them to profit. That said, we recognise that minor issues do occur which lead to reduced profit or even a loss.</t>
	<t id="5110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="5111">We need a resourceful pilot to look into such issues and solve them so that we can guarantee hassle-free profit for our members.</t>
	<t id="5112">An adaptable and skilled pilot is required to help us get a handle on these issues so that we can ensure continued profitability.</t>
	<t id="6000">(title variants)Price Dumping</t>
	<t id="6100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="6101">Our influence on the market goes far beyond simply ensuring our stations remain stocked and our traders remain active. We are of course here to turn a profit and we will do so by a number of means.</t>
	<t id="6102">Running such a large and profitable organisation such as our own is a testament to our prowess in trade and management. It also highlights that our many strategies continue to work and bring in additional credits.</t>
	<t id="6110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="6111">Controlling the price of goods with supply and demand is a time-tested technique to maximise our gains in this area. We require a NMMC Trade Guild member to perform a number of tasks to help shift the market in our favor.</t>
	<t id="6112">Manipulating supply and demand to control the prices of goods works well to maximise our profits. To this end, a NMMC Trade Guild member should perform a number of tasks to help shift the market in our favour.</t>
	<t id="7000">(title variants)Setup Satellite Network</t>
	<t id="7100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="7101">Intelligence is key to making sound business decisions, especially when that intel concerns your competition. It is also imperative that we keep an eye on our ships to ensure their safety and that they are not taking part in nefarious acts which could lead the Guild itself into disrepute.</t>
	<t id="7102">Argon and Teladi share an old adage in that knowledge is power; in this case, the power to make a profit for one and all. In order to make the best possible business decisions, it is very important that we keep two eyes on both our competition and our own ships, as often as we can spare them, in order to ensure a broad and deep view of the current situation.</t>
	<t id="7110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="7111">We need a pilot to help expand our sensor network in the local area.</t>
	<t id="7112">We are looking for someone to help expand our sensor network to this endeavour.</t>
	<t id="8000">(title variants)Maintain Satellite Network</t>
	<t id="8100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="8101">Once an intelligence network has been built, it is vital to the operation that it is maintained, so that we can always have an ear to the ground and ensure not only that our competition remains behind us, but also that our members remain out of trouble.</t>
	<t id="8102">We are keen to ensure that the vast intelligence network that we have already built is also properly maintained. This will allow us to keep an eye out for any new developments both within our own organisation and for our competition.</t>
	<t id="8110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="8111">We seek a pilot who can help with this maintenance on our sensor network.</t>
	<t id="8112">We are looking for someone to help make sure our sensor network is well maintained.</t>
	<t id="9000">(title variants)Danger Zone</t>
	<t id="9100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="9101">Some say that profit thrives in a warzone, and they are not necessarily incorrect, but there is little profit to be found for a trader that has a weapon pointed directly at them. The universe remains a dangerous place, and in order to ensure the safety of our assets and our clients, these dangers must be dealt with accordingly.</t>
	<t id="9102">Though a lot of steps have been taken since the Jump Gates began to realign to ensure a safer and more peaceful life for all, there are still many dangers across the Jump Gate network. Not only for the sake of our profit, but of course for the sake of our and our clients safety, we must make sure that we deal with these dangers.</t>
	<t id="9110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="9111">We are looking for pilots who feel like they can tackle these dangers, should they be in the form of Xenon incursions, pirates or other, more threatening menaces.</t>
	<t id="9112">We would like someone to help us deal with these dangers, whatever they may be, without risking a loss of profit.</t>
	<t id="100001">Prospecting</t>
	<t id="100002">All economy stems from the natural resources that exist across the Jump Gate network. To give our members and clients the best start to their economic activities, we'd like someone to use resource probes to find strong resource regions in $SPACENAME$. Specifically, you should look for the following resources: $WARENAMES$</t>
	<t id="100003">{30132,1}</t>
	<t id="100010">{30132,10}</t>
	<t id="100011">{30132,11}</t>
	<t id="100101">Identify Profitable Regions</t>
	<t id="100102">We would like to see an increase in the number of natural resources available for us, and in order to do that, we first want to prospect profitable regions. We'd like you to use resource probes in $SPACENAME$ to find strong yields of the following resources: $WARENAMES$</t>
	<t id="100103">{30132,1}</t>
	<t id="100110">{30132,10}</t>
	<t id="100111">{30132,11}</t>
	<t id="101001">Mine Clearance</t>
	<t id="101002">Many of our traders have been complaining about their trade routes being blocked by mines lay down by pirates and their competitors in recent times. We would like someone to deal with these mines so that our traders can go about their business in peace.</t>
	<t id="101003">(destroy: )Explosives</t>
	<t id="101011">(hint){30137,100}</t>
	<t id="101101">(own mines){30137,101101}</t>
	<t id="101102">{30137,101102}</t>
	<t id="101103">(Mines){1001,1326}</t>
	<t id="101201">(pirate mines){30137,101201}</t>
	<t id="101202">{30137,101202}</t>
	<t id="101203">(Mines){1001,1326}</t>
	<t id="102001">Ship Procurement</t>
	<t id="102002">We are looking to improve our trading fleet with a new freighter. We have spent significant time looking into areas where we are falling flat and have identified an exact specification for this ship, and would like you to source it for us:\n$FLEET$</t>
	<t id="102003">(deliver: )Freighter</t>
	<t id="102004">(deliver: )$NEEDED$x freighters</t>
	<t id="102005">{30004,5301}</t>
	<t id="102006">{30004,5304}</t>
	<t id="102011">Transfer</t>
	<t id="102012">Keep</t>
	<t id="103001">Improve Satellite Coverage</t>
	<t id="103002">As part of our work to improve our intelligence network, we would like you to help build up our satellite network in an area of interest to a number of our members' competitors. This will allow our members to keep a better eye on the competition, and build trust in the NMMC Trade Guild.\n$REQUIREMENTS$</t>
	<t id="103003">{30102,203}</t>
	<t id="103004">{30102,204}</t>
	<t id="103010">{30102,210}</t>
	<t id="103011">{30102,211}</t>
	<t id="104001">Observation Post Required</t>
	<t id="104002">We have identified an area of space that shows a lot of potential to be a popular trading point in the near future. We would like to give our members as much of an advantage as possible, and so would like satellites to be placed in the area so we keep an eye on development and tell our members when the best time to start investing will be.</t>
	<t id="104003">{30136,130}</t>
	<t id="104004">{30136,131}</t>
	<t id="104005">{30136,132}</t>
	<t id="104006">{30136,133}</t>
	<t id="104010">{30004,5005}(normal satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="104011">{30004,5006}(advanced satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="104101">Static Defence Placement</t>
	<t id="104102">After a number of Xenon incursions and raids as of late, some of our members have asked us to ensure that their stations are kept safe. We take the safety of our members' assets very seriously, and would like to ask that laser towers be placed around some member stations to show that we are willing to help.</t>
	<t id="104103">{30136,110}</t>
	<t id="104104">{30136,111}</t>
	<t id="104105">{30136,112}</t>
	<t id="104106">{30136,113}</t>
	<t id="105001">Satellite Repair</t>
	<t id="105002">A number of our satellites have been broken by weapon-fire, accidental collisions and of course deliberate attacks and sabotage. As part of the maintenance of our network, we ask you to fly to these satellites and repair their hull to $PERCENTAGE$%.</t>
	<t id="105003">{30146,20}</t>
	<t id="105004">{30146,21}</t>
	<t id="105005">{30146,22}</t>
	<t id="105101">Data Leak Repair</t>
	<t id="105102">A number of our members' stations have been suffering from a number of data leaks. This is not only harmful to our members but can also lead to significant problems for us, so we would like to ask that the leaks be dealt with in a timely fashion. We trust you to take care of this for us.</t>
	<t id="105103">{30146,30}</t>
	<t id="105104">{30146,31}</t>
	<t id="105105">{30146,32}</t>
	<t id="106001">Item Recovery</t>
	<t id="106002">One of our courier pilots has reported that they were forced to drop a number of items while en route to one of our stations. A lot of Credits were paid for these items, so we need you to first find the crate that the items were dropped in, then recover the items for us.</t>
	<t id="106003">(Find: )Container</t>
	<t id="106004">(Pick up: )Item to recover</t>
	<t id="106005">{1001, 96}</t>
	<t id="106006">{1002,3000409}</t>
	<t id="106007">{30004,1055}</t>
	<t id="107001">Panel Hack</t>
	<t id="107002">This operation is more sensitive than most: To keep you safe, we will only tell you what you are required to know. We need you to board a station belonging to one of our member's competitors and make your way to the control rooms. From there, it is imperative that you quickly and quietly sabotage the station by hacking into its control panels. Good luck.\n$REQUIREMENT$</t>
	<t id="107003">(Hack: )The specified station control panel</t>
	<t id="108001">Fatal Attraction</t>
	<t id="108002">One of our courier pilots has got themselves trapped in a mine field and we need someone to lure the mines away from them. The mines should only be detonated if it is sure that our courier will not come to any harm. Once the mines are out of the way, the crew has instructions to resume their flight.</t>
	<t id="108003">(Mines){1001,1326}</t>
	<t id="108101">Fragile Extraction</t>
	<t id="108102">One of our couriers has been caught in a mine field. Though they were able to eject from the ship and pilot themselves to safety, the ship requires recovery. Please board the ship and clear the mine field, then plot a course to the designated station. There you can transfer ownership of the ship back to us.\n$REQUIREMENTS$</t>
	<t id="108103">(Mines){1001,1326}</t>
	<t id="108104">(FlyTo)Manouevre out of minefield</t>
	<t id="108105">(Secure)Assume Control</t>
	<t id="108106">(Secure)Approach target</t>
	<t id="108107">(Secure)return ship to owner</t>
	<t id="108108">(Secure)Search spacesuit dock</t>
	<t id="108109">(Secure)Enable {20108,1051} for decryption(spacesuit scanner)</t>
	<t id="108111">Transfer Ownership</t>
	<t id="108112">Not yet</t>
	<t id="109001">An Open Request</t>
	<t id="109002">One of our members has placed an open request for some items that they seek on our notice board. It is not of very high priority, but if you find yourself with time to spare, you could help us by finding these items and taking them to the pilot. We are sure they would be very grateful for the work.</t>
	<t id="109003">(Deliver: )$AMOUNT$x $WARE$</t>
	<t id="109004">(Conversation option)Deliver: $AMOUNT$x $WARE$</t>
	<t id="109005">{30135,105}</t>
	<t id="109007">{30135,107}</t>
  </page>
  
  <page id="199430205" title="Jonferco Trade Guild" descr="Texts for the Jonferco Trade Guild mission group and sub-mission variants" voice="no">
	<t id="1">(missiongroup)Jonferco Trade Guild</t>
	<t id="2">The Jonferco Trade Guild is looking for skilled and proven entrepreneurs to join our organisation and you have been flagged as a prime candidate. If you would like to discuss this further please come and meet me.</t>
	<t id="3">Jonferco Trade Guild Office</t>
	<t id="200">(Character Entity Titles)</t>
	<t id="201">Trade Guild Representative</t>
	<t id="300">(Mails)</t>
	<t id="301">(Mail Greeting){30005,1001}</t>
	<t id="302">(Mail Signature){199430205,201}\n{199430205,1}</t>
	<t id="310">(Mail Title){199430205,1} - Trade Guild Invitation</t>
	<t id="311">(Mail Content){199430205,2}</t>
	<t id="3000">(title variants)Stumbling Blocks</t>
	<t id="3100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="3101">At the Jonferco Trade Guild, we try to make it as easy as possible for our members to enjoy trading without interruption. Unfortunately, the Jump Gate network is full of both natural and created obstacles, and we must take an active approach to protect our members from them.</t>
	<t id="3102">Those who are members of the Jonferco Trade Guild like to enjoy trading with as little interruption as possible. We take a proactive approach to providing this, dealing with any natural and created obstacles quickly and effectively, so that our our members may focus on what is important to them.</t>
	<t id="3110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="3111">We are looking for someone to go out into space and deal with a number of potentially dangerous situations.</t>
	<t id="3112">We are looking for those who can help us by dealing with these kinds of problematic obstacles.</t>
	<t id="4000">(title variants)Portfolio Improvements</t>
	<t id="4100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="4101">We at the Jonferco Trade Guild are ambitious, and ever looking for ways in which we can expand our operation to help even more traders make money. To this end, we must of course seek out new opportunities and act upon them.</t>
	<t id="4102">To make sure we are serving our members as best we can, we must always keep moving forwards and look to grow our operation where we can. In order to do this, we are looking to expand our presence in a number of different areas.</t>
	<t id="4110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="4111">We need a skilled and versatile businessperson to help us identify the opportunities we can use to grow and potentially provide assets in order to take advantage of them.</t>
	<t id="4112">We are looking for a trusted business partner to act towards these interests, potentially providing assets to the Jonferco Trade Guild, so that all members might gain from them.</t>
	<t id="5000">(title variants)Trade Operation Assistance</t>
	<t id="5100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="5101">The Jonferco Trade Guild, much like the Jonferco Space Dynamics Division, is built on people helping each other, even with the most mundane of problems. These problems, should they never be tackled, might cause problems for us all further down the line.</t>
	<t id="5102">We recognise that our Guild is not yet at the same level as the NMMC Trade Guild, we strive to one day be better, which means learning to manage small problems before the grow and become unsolvable.</t>
	<t id="5110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="5111">We look to solve such problems as quickly and effectively as possible, and we are seeking resourceful pilots to help us in this endeavour. This will help ensure convenient trading for all of our members.</t>
	<t id="5112">We are looking for an adaptable and resourceful pilot to help us solve such problems quickly and efficiently so that all of our members can continue their endeavours and help us to grow.</t>
	<t id="6000">(title variants)Market Manipulation</t>
	<t id="6100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="6101">At the Jonferco Trade Guild it is our highest priority to make sure our members and all of their assets stay in business, and ideally also profitable. To achieve this, it is sometimes necessary to go the extra mile, beyond keeping our member stations in stock and making sure our members can trade at all.</t>
	<t id="6102">Sometimes in order to keep our members in business and profitable, our number-one priority at all times, it is necessary to use techniques other than keeping our members' stations in stock and giving our members suggestions on where and how to get the best deal.</t>
	<t id="6110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="6111">Controlling the price of goods by removing or adding a ware from the market in bulk not only allows us to ensure our members make a good profit on their trades, but also protects the economy against potential future collapses. We are looking for an Jonferco Trade Guild member to help us with tasks relating to this goal.</t>
	<t id="6112">A commonly-used technique for ensuring long-lasting profits is to manipulate the supply and demand of goods and thus to control their prices. This doubles somewhat as ensurance against potential economic collapse. We're currently looking for one of our members to perform a number of tasks to help shift the market in this way.</t>
	<t id="7000">(title variants){30204,7000}</t>
	<t id="7100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="7101">We are only able to do our work because of our vast and still growing intelligence network. It allows us not only to keep an eye on economic trends, but also to keep an eye on our competition when it is necessary, as well as working as an early-warning system when our own members reach trouble.</t>
	<t id="7102">A lot of hard work has already gone into building our intelligence network. One of our greatest assets, it means we can know in advance if one of our members gets into trouble, we can keep an eye on our competition where we find it necessary and of course can quickly identify economic trends worth our members' attention.</t>
	<t id="7110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="7111">We are looking for a pilot to help us further build and expand on the sensor network already in place.</t>
	<t id="7112">In order to keep us up to date, we seek a pilot who will further build and expand on our sensor network.</t>
	<t id="8000">(title variants){30204,8000}</t>
	<t id="8100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="8101">It is not much use to build an intelligence network without then maintaining it. It is key to our Guild that this is done, so that we can continue keeping an eye out for market changes that may help our members, as well as helping us to keep an eye on our competition and keep our members out of trouble.</t>
	<t id="8102">We wish to make sure that our intelligence network is not only expanded, but also properly maintained. This will allow us to notice quickly any changes to the economy that are of interest to our members, as well as enabling us to keep an eye on our competition and to make sure our own members stay out of trouble.</t>
	<t id="8110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="8111">We are looking for a pilot who can help with this maintenance on our satellite network.</t>
	<t id="8112">We need one of our members to help make sure our sensor network is well maintained.</t>
	<t id="9000">(title variants)Dealing With Dangers</t>
	<t id="9100">(briefing - section 1)</t>
	<t id="9101">As an organisation, our main objective is to ensure stress-free trading for all of our members, and this is difficult to achieve when there are so many threats across the Jump Gate network. We need to ensure the safety of our members and their assets, and to do that these need to be dealt with.</t>
	<t id="9102">The Jonferco Space Dynamics Division has been one of the driving forces behind creating a safer and more peaceful Jump Gate network, but there remain many threats that have yet to be dealt with. The Jonferco Trade Guild recognises these threats as a danger to its members, and realises that these threats must be dealt with.</t>
	<t id="9110">(briefing - section 2)</t>
	<t id="9111">As such, we ask that a willing and able member of our Guild help us in tackling some of these dangers, whatever they may be.</t>
	<t id="9112">To help us in this endeavour, we would like a willing and able member of our guild to deal with some of these threats.</t>
	<t id="100001">(Find Resources Var 1)Source Local Regions</t>
	<t id="100002">To help our members who are interested in mining, we would like to find some local high-yield regions that we might share with them. We'd like someone to use resource probes to identify profitable mining spots in $SPACENAME$. Specifically, the resource probes should be used to find: $WARENAMES$</t>
	<t id="100003">{30132,1}</t>
	<t id="100010">{30132,10}</t>
	<t id="100011">{30132,11}</t>
	<t id="100101">(Find Resources Var 2)Identify Bountiful Regions</t>
	<t id="100102">We are looking to expand into more mining activities, and would like to see a number of profitable regions in the area prospected to help us with this. We need you to use resource probes in $SPACENAME$ to find strong yields of the following resources: $WARENAMES$</t>
	<t id="100103">{30132,1}</t>
	<t id="100110">{30132,10}</t>
	<t id="100111">{30132,11}</t>
	<t id="101001">(Destroy explosives)Explosive Clearance</t>
	<t id="101002">We've been informed by some of our members that they have been held up by mines being placed at Gates and highway entrances along their trading routes, no doubt placed by pirates or their own competition. We would like you to deal with these mines so that our members can go about their business in peace again.</t>
	<t id="101003">{30204,101003}</t>
	<t id="101011">(hint){30137,100}</t>
	<t id="101101">(own mines){30137,101101}</t>
	<t id="101102">{30137,101102}</t>
	<t id="101103">(Mines){1001,1326}</t>
	<t id="101201">(pirate mines){30137,101201}</t>
	<t id="101202">{30137,101202}</t>
	<t id="101203">(Mines){1001,1326}</t>
	<t id="101601">(Jonferco)Expired Licence</t>
	<t id="101602">To deter some pirates lingering near our trade routes, we placed a couple of cheap mines. Knowing those pirates, the mines are probably good enough to do some damage to their ships and keep them from making trouble. However, the next inspection from Jonferco bureaucrats will reveal, that the mines' software licence is long expired. To avoid paying a fee for using outdated and potentially dangerous technology, we want you to destroy them.</t>
	<t id="101603">(Mines){1001,1326}</t>
	<t id="102001">Ship Attainment</t>
	<t id="102002">We are looking to grow our own merchant fleet with the addition of a new transporter. After significant work to analyse what exactly it is we need, based on areas where we feel we are falling short, we have identified an exact specification for this ship. We would like you to source it for us:\n$FLEET$</t>
	<t id="102003">{30204,102003}</t>
	<t id="102004">{30204,102004}</t>
	<t id="102005">{30004,5301}</t>
	<t id="102006">{30004,5304}</t>
	<t id="102011">{30204,102011}</t>
	<t id="102012">{30204,102012}</t>
	<t id="103001">{30204,103001}</t>
	<t id="103002">A number of our members have expressed an interest in knowing more about what their competitors are up to. We see an opportunity here to broaden our intelligence network, and so would like you to deploy a number of satellites in an area that we've identified as of interest to our members.</t>
	<t id="103003">{30102,203}</t>
	<t id="103004">{30102,204}</t>
	<t id="103010">{30102,210}</t>
	<t id="103011">{30102,211}</t>
	<t id="104001">Observations Required</t>
	<t id="104002">Sources tell us that one particular trader, not a member of our Guild, has the potential to significantly damage trading routes for not one but many of our members. We would like to be able to analyse the situation for ourselves, so we require a satellite to be deployed in the specified location.</t>
	<t id="104003">{30136,130}</t>
	<t id="104004">{30136,131}</t>
	<t id="104005">{30136,132}</t>
	<t id="104006">{30136,133}</t>
	<t id="104010">{30004,5005}(normal satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="104011">{30004,5006}(advanced satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="104101">Laser Tower Placement</t>
	<t id="104102">A number of our members have been suffering from raids on their stations recently, as well as an increased number of Xenon incursions. The safety of Jonferco Trade Guild members and the security of their assets is one of our top priorities, and as such we would like to see laser towers deployed around the affected stations.</t>
	<t id="104103">{30136,110}</t>
	<t id="104104">{30136,111}</t>
	<t id="104105">{30136,112}</t>
	<t id="104106">{30136,113}</t>
	<t id="105001">{30204,105001}</t>
	<t id="105002">Be it from stray weapon fire, accidental conditions or deliberate acts of vandalism or sabotage, a number of our satellites have been taken out of commission. As part of the maintenance to our network, we'd like you to fly to these satellites and repair their hull to $PERCENTAGE$%.</t>
	<t id="105003">{30146,20}</t>
	<t id="105004">{30146,21}</t>
	<t id="105005">{30146,22}</t>
	<t id="105101">{30204,105101}</t>
	<t id="105102">A number of our member stations are suffering from data leaks that are leaking very sensitive trading information, not only to our competition, but potentially also to pirates. We can't allow this data to be used harmfully - we need the leaks dealt with in a timely fashion.</t>
	<t id="105103">{30146,30}</t>
	<t id="105104">{30146,31}</t>
	<t id="105105">{30146,32}</t>
	<t id="106001">{30204,106001}</t>
	<t id="106002">A member of the Jonferco Trade Guild was attacked while they were on a trading run, and reported to us that they were forced to drop some of their inventory to make sure it wasn't destroyed. The pilot is fine, at least physically, but unable to retrieve the items. Instead, we would like you to find the crate in which the items were dropped in, and then recover them on our behalf.</t>
	<t id="106003">{30204,106003}</t>
	<t id="106004">{30204,106004}</t>
	<t id="106005">{30204,106005}</t>
	<t id="106006">{30204,106006}</t>
	<t id="106007">{30204,106007}</t>
	<t id="107001">{30204,107001}</t>
	<t id="107002">We don't usually condone these kinds of operations, but the matter is urgent and needs to be dealt with quickly and quietly. For your own safety, we will only tell you what you need to do. Without asking questions, please make your way to the designated station, board it and make your way to the control rooms. Once there, please use the appropriate equipment to... temporarily disarm the specified panel. Thank you and good luck.\n$REQUIREMENT$</t>
	<t id="107003">{30204,107003}</t>
	<t id="108001">Fatal Attraction</t>
	<t id="108002">One of our members found a mine field on their trade route and attempted to traverse it instead of going around. They are now stuck in a field of tracking mines. In order to rescue the pilot, we would like someone to lure the mines away from the ship. Be careful: The mines should only be detonated once it is certain that the pilot will not come to harm. When the mines have been cleared, the pilot knows to resume their flight.</t>
	<t id="108003">(Mines){1001,1326}</t>
	<t id="108101">Extraction Necessary</t>
	<t id="108102">One of our members has been caught in a minefield they were trying to traverse on their trade route. Once stuck, they were able to eject into a spacesuit and navigate out of the field, but the ship has been stranded. We'd like it to be returned to its owner. Please board the ship and clear the mine field, then plot a course to the station we've designated. There you can transfer ownership back to us.\n$REQUIREMENTS$</t>
	<t id="108103">(Mines){1001,1326}</t>
	<t id="108104">{30204,108104}</t>
	<t id="108105">{30204,108105}</t>
	<t id="108106">{30204,108106}</t>
	<t id="108107">{30204,108107}</t>
	<t id="108108">{30204,108108}</t>
	<t id="108109">{30204,108109}</t>
	<t id="108111">{30204,108111}</t>
	<t id="108112">{30204,108112}</t>
	<t id="109001">{30204,109001}</t>
	<t id="109002">{30204,109002}</t>
	<t id="109003">{30204,109003}</t>
	<t id="109004">{30204,109004}</t>
	<t id="109005">{30135,105}</t>
	<t id="109007">{30135,107}</t>
  </page>
	
  <page id="199430211" title="Atreus vs Strongarms War" descr="Texts for the 'Atreus-Strong Arms war' mission-group and sub-mission variants" voice="no">
	<t id="1">(missiongroup)Atreus Currents Vs. Strong Arms</t>
	<t id="2">The Strong Arms, a rival company of the agressive Split race, continues to test our borders. We are looking for trusted friends of the Atreus Currents to help keep them in check.</t>
	<t id="3">Strongarms War Room</t>
	<t id="10">(intro mission)Split Aggression</t>
	<t id="11">The Strong Arms grows more bold and desperate with each passing day and we must show them that the Atreus Currents will not tolerate any incursions into our space. We are looking for volunteers to help us enforce that stance. If you believe you have the skills and fortitude, sign up!</t>
	<t id="200">(Character Entity Titles)</t>
	<t id="201">War Coordinator</t>
	<t id="300">(Mails)</t>
	<t id="301">(Mail Greeting){30005,1001}</t>
	<t id="302">(Mail Signature){199430211,201}\n$FACTION$</t>
	<t id="310">(Mail Title)$FACTION$ - Recruiting Volunteers Against the Strong Arms</t>
	<t id="311">(Mail Content){199430211,2}</t>
	<t id="312">(Mail Appendix){30005,2010}</t>
	<t id="1000">(common briefing texts)</t>
	<t id="1100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="1101">The Strong Arms again seem to be massing on our borders and we must be ready to deal with them.</t>
	<t id="1102">The remains of our intelligence network in Strong Arms space points to them preparing their forces.</t>
	<t id="1200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="1201">Like before, the Strong Arms continues to underestimate our resolve and preparedness.</t>
	<t id="1202">Our intelligence links and recon ships confirm a build up of military assets in Strong Arms.</t>
	<t id="3000">(title variants)Build Defence</t>
	<t id="3001">Defence Preparations</t>
	<t id="3002">Safeguard against Potential Invasion</t>
	<t id="3100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="3101">It looks as though the Strong Arms is once again preparing for a skirmish into our space, massing a number of ships on our borders.</t>
	<t id="3102">What remains of our intelligence network in Strong Arms space points to them preparing forces to make another push towards our territory.</t>
	<t id="3110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="3111">While we continue to press the Split Strong Arms to reign in their agression, we must remain vigilant and prepare for any outcome.</t>
	<t id="3120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="3121">The Strong Arms believes they have the upper hand but we will be sure to have our defences ready should they try their luck. We're looking for able bodies and minds to help us in this endeavour.</t>
	<t id="3122">Time is short on us to make preparations. Defences are a priority and we're looking for independent contractors to coordinate with us in maintaining our existing countermeasures as well as deploying new ones.</t>
	<t id="3200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="3201">The Strong Arms continues to underestimate our resolve and preparedness, as they have many times before. They are readying for a move into our space, but they will not get their wish.</t>
	<t id="3202">Our intelligence network and reconnaisance vessels confirm a build up of military assets in Strong Arms space adjacent to our territory. We believe they are readying an 'invasion'.</t>
	<t id="3210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="3211">Should they come, we will meet them as we have before and hold this sector with ease. We must of course be cautious and ready for whatever they throw at us.</t>
	<t id="3220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="3221">We will coordinate with all local forces, corporations and any willing civilians to be sure that everyone is prepared. Will you join us in the defence of our people?</t>
	<t id="4000">(title variants)Large-Scale Defence Construction</t>
	<t id="4001">Heavy Construction Operation</t>
	<t id="4100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="4101">The Strong Arms once again prepare to test us. Reports talk of many combat ships, from scouts to capital-class destroyers, stocked for days of conflict, massing on our borders.</t>
	<t id="4102">We reach out again as the Strong Arms prepare to test our already battered defences with newly built or prepared combat ships, armed to the teeth as always.</t>
	<t id="4110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="4111">Our forces are stretched to a point where we must begin driving forward with the construction of new ships and defensive structures. Our shipwrights are hard at work putting together effective and capable warships while our engineering corps continue to build and maintain our static defences.</t>
	<t id="4120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="4121">Any aid in these areas is much needed. We are looking for able individuals prepared to invest significant resources and effort in preparing our space for anything the Strong Arms will throw at us.</t>
	<t id="4122">While we only have a short window to shore up our defences, we expect any help in these areas will play a key part in future engagements with the Strong Arms.</t>
	<t id="4200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="4201">The Strong Arms once again prepare to engage against us. They expect that we will bend and break under the force of their newly built fleets, but we know they're coming, and now we can prepare.</t>
	<t id="4202">Scouting and intelligence reports talk of Strong Arms ships massing at the Jump Gates leading towards our territory. As to be expected, it looks as though it is a strong offence, but when we know it's coming, we can prepare appropriately.</t>
	<t id="4210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="4211">While our warships and static defences have proven themselves time and time again, we will continue to strengthen them in the face of aggression from the Strong Arms.</t>
	<t id="4220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="4221">We are looking for able individuals to aid us with significant time and resources in preparing our defences against anything the Strong Arms can throw at us.</t>
	<t id="5000">(title variants)Secure Resources</t>
	<t id="5001">Safeguarding Resource Supplies</t>
	<t id="5100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="5101">With reports stating that the Strong Arms are building up their forces and rumours of war spreading like the plague, we have decided to take action. We assume that when the time does come, our defences will not be the only thing targeted.</t>
	<t id="5102">We stand on the brink of another conflict with the Strong Arms and must take action if we are to survive yet another onslaught. When the time comes, we must make sure we are ready for the worst case scenario.</t>
	<t id="5110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="5111">We must be sure to safeguard the resources vital to our operations. This involves finding and protecting raw materials as well as stocking up whatever wares we are currently short on.</t>
	<t id="5120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="5121">The Strong Arms continue to make it difficult for our freighters to do their work effectively, but with the aid of pilots like you and the rest of the Atreus Currents defense forces, we will get our infrastructure running smoothly - so we can get back to dealing with the Strong Arms aggression head on.</t>
	<t id="5122">This conflict has put a sizable strain on our infrastructure and supply lines, leaving us with slow construction projects and the onset of rationing. We will not let this continue, but we require the skills of all able pilots to help us reverse the situation.</t>
	<t id="5200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="5201">The Strong Arms will soon attempt another strike at our territories, according to all trustworthy reports. Though it has not always been the case, we must assume they have learned from prior mistakes and will target more than our defences if they wish to destroy us.</t>
	<t id="5202">Another day, another feeble attempt by the Strong Arms to break our defences and our spirit. Reports indicate that they are preparing another attack, and we will be ready for them to attack not just our fleets and defences, but, desperately, our civilian structures as well.</t>
	<t id="5210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="5211">As we press forward against the Strong Arms, we must continue to guarantee that our economy continues to function smoothly. This will include protecting our supply lines and mining areas as well as searching for any new sources of raw resources.</t>
	<t id="5220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="5221">The Strong Arms are looking to make it difficult for our freighters but with the aid of pilots like you and the rest of the Atreus Currents forces, we will continue to keep our economy running smoothly so we can focus on dealing with the Strong Arms aggression head on.</t>
	<t id="6000">(title variants)Preemptive Offensive</t>
	<t id="6001">Deterrence</t>
	<t id="6100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="6101">The intelligence network we have managed to set up in Strong Arms territory has reported back that they are preparing yet another attack against us. We have decided to change our tactical response, in an attempt to change our fortune.</t>
	<t id="6102">You have no doubt heard the rumours, or seen for yourself; the Strong Arms is massing combat ships on our borders. We fear another assault on our territory, soon, and wish to take them by surprise in order to get the upper hand.</t>
	<t id="6110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="6111">Given our position, we are looking to find and strike low risk targets in the hope that it can draw the Strong Arms's attention from the fronts where our forces are stretched.</t>
	<t id="6120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="6121">We expect that neutralising these targets will not only destabilise the cohesion of the current enemy forces, but will also give us a decisive edge when we are ready to counter.</t>
	<t id="6122">While the Strong Arms have forced our hand, we do believe that striking these targets will help turn the tide back in our favor. At the very least, it will give the Strong Arms something to think about.</t>
	<t id="6200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="6201">Once again our intelligence network has come through for us! We now know that the Strong Arms is preparing another offensive against us, and our tacticians have already started planning our counter attack. We want you to take part!</t>
	<t id="6202">We have known for some time that the Strong Arms would try to push their luck, as they have many times already. Our tactical teams are forever working to find new ways to embarrass the Strong Arms , and we are confident in this new plan.</t>
	<t id="6210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="6211">As we continue to strengthen our position in our space, we must prepare for the next phase of the conflict with the Strong Arms.</t>
	<t id="6220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="6221">Before we commit a large number of our forces to the front, we first want to remove some strategic targets in order to destabilise the enemy defences.</t>
	<t id="7000">(title variants)Gather Intel</t>
	<t id="7001">Intelligence</t>
	<t id="7100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="7101">While some signs point to the Strong Arms planning another offensive against us, we lack the intel to be able to deploy our defences effectively.</t>
	<t id="7102">In recent weeks we have been working with nought but rumour as we try to get on top of the Strong Arms's plans. We believe they are planning a new offensive.</t>
	<t id="7110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="7111">Intel has been a shortcoming for us so far in this conflict. We have made preparations to improve the situation but it will require skilled individuals to work alone and potentially behind enemy lines.</t>
	<t id="7120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="7121">What intel we do have indicates that the Strong Arms continues to be overconfident and often stretch beyond their means. With improved intel, we should be able to launch strikes when they are at their most vulnerable.</t>
	<t id="7122">Our intelligence division is confident we can plug what gaps we have in our network and give us an edge on the Strong Arms when we choose to strike. Of course, it will also aid us in protecting our borders against whatever they choose to throw at us.</t>
	<t id="7200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="7201">While we continuously push the Strong Arms, we do not expect a quick solution to their agression. This has left our intelligence community with a lot work to do in a short amount of time with limited resources.</t>
	<t id="7202">It might have been quite easy for the Strong Arms to push straight through it were it not for our continuously impressive preparations; preparations we must continue to make if we wish to continue fighting the Strong Arms. For this, we will use our greatest assets.</t>
	<t id="7210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="7211">Throughout this conflict, we have proven that our intelligence division is much more capable than anything the Strong Arms has. In order to move forward, we must continue to press this advantage.</t>
	<t id="7220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="7221">We are looking for trusted individuals to put their skills to use against the Strong Arms on their home turf. These tasks are not without risk but they will certainly help us maintain the upper hand.</t>
	<t id="8000">(title variants)Support Invasion</t>
	<t id="8100">(briefing - taking sectors back - section 1)</t>
	<t id="8101">As most likely know, we have been caught off guard several times in our conflict against the Strong Arms, allowing them to make advances on several fronts.</t>
	<t id="8110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="8111">We have commenced operations to drive them out of our territories, but this will be a prolonged struggle.</t>
	<t id="8120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="8121">We need skilled pilots to aid in achieving our objectives. These will include backing up combat units when pushing the enemy back as well as holding out critical areas as we continue to rebuild our defences.</t>
	<t id="8200">(briefing - taking enemy home sectors - section 1)</t>
	<t id="8201">Thanks to the hard work of our people and allies, we find ourselves in a prime position to deal a heavy blow to the Strong Arms.</t>
	<t id="8210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="8211">They are currently on the back foot and we must continue to press them and hinder their ability to launch any form of aggression.</t>
	<t id="8220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="8221">We are looking for brave and skilled pilots to help us ramp up the pressure. The situation is very volatile and tasks will shift from attacking enemy positions to defending our own.</t>
	<t id="9000">(title variants)Seize Strong Arms Space</t>
	<t id="9001">Strong Arms Station Offensive</t>
	<t id="9100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="9101">We cannot just sit idly by as these zealots expand their reach further and further. If we do not act decisively, and soon, we might reach a point where we cannot resist their advances further. Taking the fight back to their territory is our top priority.</t>
	<t id="9102">We have received troubling reports that the Strong Arms fleet is gathering its forces. Command is worried that if they decide to start a full scale invasion, we have little to put in their way. We need to inflict massive damage in order to divert their efforts away from readying their fleet.</t>
	<t id="9110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="9111">It is crucially important to hit one of their stations hard. It is the most sure-fire way to stem their expansionist efforts. The fighting will be intense, and we have to expect losses on both sides.</t>
	<t id="9120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="9121">We are fighting wars on several fronts, and our resources are starting to run low, so we decided to take the slightly unusual step of hiring outside help for this task. You will be well compensated if you take down this station on our behalf.</t>
	<t id="9122">The odds might be against us right now, but we Borons are a tenacious people, and we will fight them with everything we've got. If you help us in our battle, we will be eternally grateful and pay you well.</t>
	<t id="9200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="9201">Thanks to an increase in supplies and recruiting efforts, we are ready to start an advance into Strong Arms Space. Our intelligence officers have identified a potential target station which, if eliminated, will weaken the hold these Split freaks have over the territory.</t>
	<t id="9202">The fighting so far has been fierce, and we are ready to escalate the conflict even further. If we mean to win this war at some point, we have to make meaningful progress, and we are confident that we can beat them back.</t>
	<t id="9210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="9211">Our intelligence officers have identified a potential target station that, if eliminated, will significantly slow down these fanatics.</t>
	<t id="9220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="9221">This offensive is of significant importance, which is the reason why we turn to you. It will take a considerable amount of preparation, and there will likely be heavy casualties, but this will be reflected in the reward we are willing to pay if you succeed.</t>
	<t id="100001">{30141,101}</t>
	<t id="100002">{30141,102}</t>
	<t id="100003">{30141,103}</t>
	<t id="100004">{30141,104}</t>
	<t id="100101">{30141,201}</t>
	<t id="100102">{30141,202}</t>
	<t id="100103">{30141,203}</t>
	<t id="100104">{30141,204}</t>
	<t id="101001">Deploy Static Defence</t>
	<t id="101002">While there are others working on building larger military installations to help in our defence, many areas still lack smaller defences such as laser towers. These require placing in areas that are vulnerable to enemy attack.</t>
	<t id="101003">{30136,110}</t>
	<t id="101004">{30136,111}</t>
	<t id="101005">{30136,112}</t>
	<t id="101006">{30136,113}</t>
	<t id="101101">Mine Strong Arms Entry Point</t>
	<t id="101102">Given our current level of intel, we gauge there are only a few places that the Strong Arms can launch an effective attack from. One of these areas is not in our space, but we feel it imperative to reinforce any potential entry point. We require a number of mines to be placed in this strategic location.</t>
	<t id="101103">{30136,120}</t>
	<t id="101104">{30136,121}</t>
	<t id="101105">{30136,122}</t>
	<t id="101106">{30136,123}</t>
	<t id="101201">Mine our borders to Strong Arms space</t>
	<t id="101202">As you may well know, we share a border with the Strong Arms, which makes that entry point an incredibly important strategic location. As part of our defensive plans for that area, we require a number of mines to be deployed there.</t>
	<t id="101203">{30136,120}</t>
	<t id="101204">{30136,121}</t>
	<t id="101205">{30136,122}</t>
	<t id="101206">{30136,123}</t>
	<t id="101301">Deploy Static Defence</t>
	<t id="101302">As part of our push to secure our resources from the enemy, we would like you to place defensive laser towers at strategic points in resource-heavy regions that are critical to our economy.</t>
	<t id="101303">{30136,110}</t>
	<t id="101304">{30136,111}</t>
	<t id="101305">{30136,112}</t>
	<t id="101306">{30136,113}</t>
	<t id="101401">Imperative satellite placement</t>
	<t id="101402">At the request of our intelligence division, we require a single satellite to be placed in a vital area. We not only want to gain sensor data for that region, we also want to bait the Strong Arms into some response. Anything we can do to dictate their movements or reveal their strength will aid us when we have to make a move ourselves.</t>
	<t id="101403">{30136,130}</t>
	<t id="101404">{30136,131}</t>
	<t id="101405">{30136,132}</t>
	<t id="101406">{30136,133}</t>
	<t id="101410">{30004,5005}(normal satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="101411">{30004,5006}(advanced satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="102001">Sensor gap needs plugging</t>
	<t id="102002">Though our main priority in this area is to keep an eye on the movements of the Strong Arms, a sensor grid is necessary to track any potential threats to our space. We are looking for you to fill the holes in that net.\n$REQUIREMENTS$</t>
	<t id="102003">{30102,1}</t>
	<t id="102004">{30102,2}</t>
	<t id="102010">{30102,3}(advanced-satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="102011">{30102,4}(area-hint)</t>
	<t id="102101">{30102,301}(Achieve Coverage)</t>
	<t id="102102">{30102,302}</t>
	<t id="102103">{30102,303}</t>
	<t id="102104">{30102,304}</t>
	<t id="102110">{30102,310}</t>
	<t id="102111">{30102,311}</t>
	<t id="103001">Drive to repair damaged ships</t>
	<t id="103002">Several of our ships are in need of minor repairs and to help take the strain off of our shipyards, we are looking to make as many in-space repairs as possible. As the crew continues to repair the internal systems, we require additional help for the hull and external sub-sytems.</t>
	<t id="103003">{30146,10}</t>
	<t id="103004">{30146,11}</t>
	<t id="103005">{30146,12}</t>
	<t id="104001">Deliver specialist to the front</t>
	<t id="104002">A number of specialists on Strong Arms tactics and history are to be transported to strategic locations to give direct assessments of our preparations. We require a number of pilots to come forward to provide safe and swift transport for these clients.</t>
	<t id="104003">(comeonboard conversation option){1002,3015}</t>
	<t id="104007">(onboardnotification){30004,5102}</t>
	<t id="104008">(passengerleftnotification){30004,5103}</t>
	<t id="104009">(male)Transport specialist</t>
	<t id="104010">(female)Transport specialist</t>
	<t id="105001">Build Military Base</t>
	<t id="105002">We are requesting a new military installation to be built in a strategic location to help us deter aggression from the Strong Arms. We will require the facility to fit the following specifications.</t>
	<t id="105003">(objective1){30004,5201}</t>
	<t id="105004">(objective2){30004,5213}</t>
	<t id="105005">(objective3 - Defence Station){30004,5211}</t>
	<t id="105006">(objective4){30004,5203}</t>
	<t id="105007">(Destination){30120,200}</t>
	<t id="106001">{30132,101}</t>
	<t id="106002">{30132,102}</t>
	<t id="106003">{30132,103}</t>
	<t id="106010">{30132,110}</t>
	<t id="106011">{30132,111}</t>
	<t id="106101">Scout enemy mining regions</t>
	<t id="106102">In order to plan future operations against the Strong Arms, we would like to gauge what resources they have available to them in their space. Attempt to find high yield regions of the following resource: $WARENAMES$</t>
	<t id="106103">{30132,1}</t>
	<t id="106110">{30132,10}</t>
	<t id="106111">{30132,11}</t>
	<t id="107001">(next ID reserved for gender)Take out Strong Arms Agent</t>
	<t id="107003">(ma target)We have identified a key player involved in several acts of espionage against us and our allies. $NPCName$ has been spotted posing as an entrepreneur on several of our stations while he meets with known Strong Arms sympathisers. Unfortunately for him, the last one he met with is on our payroll.</t>
	<t id="107004">(fe target)We have identified a key player involved in several acts of espionage against us and our allies. $NPCName$ has been spotted posing as an entrepreneur on several of our stations while she meets with known Strong Arms sympathisers. Unfortunately for her, the last one she met with is on our payroll.</t>
	<t id="107005">(ma target)\nThey were last seen flying a ship with ID: $SHIPID$. Make sure he doesn't come back from this one.</t>
	<t id="107006">(fe target)\nThey were last seen flying a ship with ID: $SHIPID$. Make sure she doesn't come back from this one.</t>
	<t id="107101">(ma target)$NPCName$ must be stopped</t>
	<t id="107102">(fe target)$NPCName$ must be stopped</t>
	<t id="107103">(ma target)During one of our last engagements with the Strong Arms, one of our ships was lost. It seems that some of the wreckage was salvaged by the individual $NPCName$, who then went on to sell sensitive data pulled from the ship's databanks. Our contacts believe he is soon to contact another buyer and we must stop him from making the exchange, by any means.</t>
	<t id="107104">(fe target)During one of our last engagements with the Strong Arms, one of our ships was lost. It seems that some of the wreckage was salvaged by the individual $NPCName$, who then went on to sell sensitive data pulled from the ship's databanks. Our contacts believe she is soon to contact another buyer and we must stop her from making the exchange, by any means.</t>
	<t id="107105">(ma target)\nThey're flying ship: $SHIPID$. Don't let him go any further.</t>
	<t id="107106">(fe target)\nThey're flying ship: $SHIPID$. Don't let her go any further.</t>
	<t id="108001">Seize Strong Arms ship</t>
	<t id="108002">We have determined a certain Strong Arms ship to be a prime target for a data-extraction operation. The ship must be engaged, boarded and its data-core cloned for us to analyse. The information contained in that ship may be decisive in the battles to come.</t>
	<t id="108003">{30004,4001}</t>
	<t id="108004">(fe target){199430211,108002}</t>
	<t id="109001">Support Invasion</t>
	<t id="109002">The time has come to make an offensive push to remove the Strong Arms from this sector. We have full confidence in our fleet and our pilots, but they will require some support as they fight. We would like you to provide this support for us.</t>
	<t id="110001">Looking for Pilots</t>
	<t id="110002">To greater improve our chances of striking back against the Strong Arms, we are looking for $NPCCOUNT$ pilot\(s\) to take command of our ships. These pilots should be brought to one of our stations before the fighting starts.\n$DESTINATION$\n$SKILLS$</t>
	<t id="110003">Pilot</t>
	<t id="110004">$NPCCOUNT$ Pilots</t>
	<t id="110005">(progress bar)Pilots</t>
	<t id="110101">Station Engineers needed</t>
	<t id="110102">To make sure that our military installations are performing at peak efficiency during the war against the Strong Arms, we are looking for $NPCCOUNT$ engineer\(s\) to be brought to one of our stations.\n$DESTINATION$\n$SKILLS$</t>
	<t id="110103">(Acquire)Station Engineer</t>
	<t id="110104">(Acquire)$NPCCOUNT$ Station Engineers</t>
	<t id="110105">(progress bar)Engineers</t>
	<t id="120001">Assemble fleet</t>
	<t id="120002">You cannot win a war without a fleet. Our shipyards are working at full capacity, but in order to bolster our numbers, we require the support of independent suppliers. To help in the war-effort, please bring the following ships to our headquarters:\n$FLEET$</t>
	<t id="120003">(deliver:)Combat ship</t>
	<t id="120004">(deliver:)$NEEDED$ Combat ships</t>
	<t id="120005">{30004,5301}</t>
	<t id="120006">{30004,5304}</t>
	<t id="120011">{30004,5302}</t>
	<t id="120012">{30004,5303}</t>
	<t id="130001">Station Supply</t>
	<t id="130002">We need to keep the production running and need your help in fulfilling the open trade-orders. Try to get above the specified minimum storage threshold.\n\nMinimum storage level: $STORAGEPERCENT$%</t>
	<t id="130003">(Supply)Supplies</t>
	<t id="140001">Ship Hunt</t>
	<t id="140002">(singular)Track down a ship matching the following specification and destroy them.$SPECS$</t>
	<t id="140003">(plural)Track down ships matching the following specification and destroy them.$SPECS$</t>
	<t id="140004">{30004,1701}</t>
	<t id="140005">{30004,1702}</t>
	<t id="150001">{30140,10001}(GM_Scan1)</t>
	<t id="150002">{30140,10002}</t>
	<t id="150003">{30004,1900}</t>
	<t id="150101">{30140,20001}(GM_Scan2)</t>
	<t id="150102">{30140,20002}</t>
	<t id="150103">{30004,1901}</t>
	<t id="150201">{30140,30001}(GM_Scan3)</t>
	<t id="150202">{30140,30002}</t>
	<t id="150203">{30004,1902}</t>
	<t id="150301">{30140,40001}(GM_Scan4)</t>
	<t id="150302">{30140,40002}</t>
	<t id="150303">{30004,1903}</t>
	<t id="150401">{30140,50001}(GM_Scan5)</t>
	<t id="150402">{30140,50002}</t>
	<t id="150403">{30004,1904}</t>
	<t id="150501">{30140,60001}(GM_Scan6)</t>
	<t id="150502">{30140,60002}</t>
	<t id="150503">{30004,1905}</t>
	<t id="150601">{30140,70001}(GM_Scan7)</t>
	<t id="150602">{30140,70002}</t>
	<t id="150603">{30004,1906}</t>
	<t id="150701">Operative Evaluation</t>
	<t id="150702">Atreus Intelligence is supporting a splinter cell of the Strong Arms to gather intel and disrupt the Order's administrative capabilities. Our aid consists of water transports to feed the cell's workforce. However, Intelligence recognised a small but unexpected increase in the Strong Arms's population, and is now concerned about the cell's loyalty. Thus, the last deliveries have been marked with an isotope. To confirm that our resources are not being used against the Atreus Currents, Intelligence requests scans of Strong Arms ships transporting Water.</t>
	<t id="150703">(Scan Ship containing Ware){30004,1903}</t>
	<t id="150801">Threat Assessment</t>
	<t id="150802">Since the Strong Arms seem to be unwilling or unable to deal with its aggression any time soon, the Atreus Currents is initiating the appropriate steps to contain these sadistical pirates and secure our trade and our borders. To this end, Atreus Intelligence suggests an evaluation of their access to Hull Parts. These numbers tell us how much firepower we have to bring along in order to turn their ships, stations, hopes and dreams into space dust. To aid Intelligence in their evaluation, provide scans of Strong Arms ships transporting Hull Parts.</t>
	<t id="150803">(Scan Ship containing Ware){30004,1903}</t>
	<t id="160001">(Mines)Misleading of Counterintelligence</t>
	<t id="160002">To locate security breaches within their ranks, the Strong Arms set up this minefield and leaked its location to specific branches of their military command. Targeting it diverts their counterintelligence from our agents.</t>
	<t id="160003">{1001,1326}(Mines)</t>
	<t id="160101">(Mines)Manoeuvre Preparations</t>
	<t id="160102">This minefield is an obstacle to a manoeuvre our captains might want to execute. Strategic Planning thus requested it to be removed before a battle takes place in its vicinity.</t>
	<t id="160103">{1001,1326}(Mines)</t>
	<t id="161001">(Lasertowers)Intelligence Success Assurance</t>
	<t id="161002">There are a couple of laser towers that would expose nearby undercover ships executing a mission. We have to assume that they lack knowledge of these towers. Additionally, we cannot warn them as the communication attempt would uncover them. To ensure their success, we have to take out the towers.</t>
	<t id="161003">{1001,1333}(Laser Towers)</t>
	<t id="161101">(Lasertowers)Undermining the Meritocracy</t>
	<t id="161102">One Strong Arms strategist is quite incompetent, yet he is a candidate for promotion. We do our best to make it look like his predictions are correct, to encourage them to promote him. Lately, he suspected that we would target a specific group of laser towers.</t>
	<t id="161103">{1001,1333}(Laser Towers)</t>
	<t id="170001">(Station)Destroy Strong Arms Station</t>
	<t id="170002">This is a critical task. You will be operating in Strong Arms territory, so expect heavy resistance. They certainly won't take this lying down. We need this station to be destroyed completely.</t>
	<t id="170003">{1001,3}(Station)</t>
	<t id="180001">(Station Turrets)Preparing a Station Raid</t>
	<t id="180002">We have become aware that an important Strong Arms dignitary is going to be assigned to a station within our reach. We are going to send a team of experienced marines to infiltrate the station, and snatch him up for intel. A basic kidnap job. Unfortunately, the ships equipped for such an incursion aren't well suited to weathering strong defensive fire. So, before we can set this plan in motion, we need you to destroy the turrets that would prevent our crew from getting close.\n\nStation: $STATION$\nAmount of turrets to destroy: $TURRETS$</t>
	<t id="180003">{30144,1003}</t>
  </page>
	
  <page id="199430215" title="Strongarms vs Atreus War" descr="Texts for the 'Strongarms vs Atreus war' mission-group and sub-mission variants" voice="no">
	<t id="1">(missiongroup)Strong Arms Vs. Atreus Currents</t>
	<t id="2">Wretched Boron refuse to back down. Their insistence on opposing subjugation can only be met with open war. Split are looking for capable individuals to aid with Boron annihilation. Reinforce borders. Lead attacks on their turf. Split can offer a variety of duties for you to tend to!</t>
	<t id="3">Atreus War Room</t>
	<t id="10">(intro mission)Conscript!</t>
	<t id="11">Split always in need for volunteers to help fight Boron. Enlist, if you feel you are up to task. Demonstrate skill, engage Boron!</t>
	<t id="200">(Character Entity Titles)</t>
	<t id="201">Patriarchal Marshal</t>
	<t id="300">(Mails)</t>
	<t id="301">(Mail Greeting){30005,1001}</t>
	<t id="302">(Mail Signature){199430215,201}\n$FACTION$</t>
	<t id="310">(Mail Title)$FACTION$ - War Against the wretched Boron</t>
	<t id="311">(Mail Content){199430215,2}</t>
	<t id="312">(Mail Appendix){30005,2010}</t>
	<t id="1000">(common briefing texts)</t>
	<t id="1001">Missiongroup name - 'family business'</t>
	<t id="1100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="1101">Ever since Gate reconnection, the Boron Atreus Currents and Split Strong Arms have clashed. Split foresee enemy military campaign, and must be prepared to counter-attack.</t>
	<t id="1102">Though cowardly Boron are hard to predict, Split worry about a possible imminent attack. Need to be prepared.</t>
	<t id="1110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="1111">Negative mood section 2.</t>
	<t id="1120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="1121">Negative mood section 3 variation 1</t>
	<t id="1122">Negative mood section 3 variation 2</t>
	<t id="1200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="1201">Boron keep interfering in Split affairs. Split respond in kind, inflict casualties, and push them back. Atreus seem to insist on witlessly repeating their grave mistake.</t>
	<t id="1202">Split vanguard spotted Boron bordering Split space. They seem unaware of our presence, or severely underestimate Split strength. Either way, they will soon regret foolish action.</t>
	<t id="1210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="1211">Positive mood section 2.</t>
	<t id="1220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="1221">Positive mood section 3 variation 1</t>
	<t id="1222">Positive mood section 3 variation 2</t>
	<t id="3000">(title variants)Set Up Defence</t>
	<t id="3001">Improve Defence Against Boron</t>
	<t id="3002">Safeguard Split Space</t>
	<t id="3100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="3101">Boron ships occasionally slip through our defensive perimeter from both sides, to escape imprisonment or run operations in Split sectors. Intolerable! If Split do not react, control over the territory will be lost.</t>
	<t id="3102">The Atreus Currents has proved surprisingly resourceful. Again and again, they send troops into Split space. Inflict massive damage. Split need to shore up defences, or Boron campaign will continue and families will challenge Patriarch's control.</t>
	<t id="3110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="3111">Split identified several defensive weaknesses. To address them immediately is very important.</t>
	<t id="3120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="3121">Boron cannot be underestimated. Split must be well prepared. Once their ships are kept outside Split territory, Split families can coordinate effort to beat Boron down.</t>
	<t id="3122">Split need protection from Boron raids. To not guarantee it would dishonour the Patriarch. Once Split space is securely under control, Split again turn attention toward crushing Boron.</t>
	<t id="3200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="3201">Boron ships throw themselves against Split defences with little effect. At great cost they hope to wear Split down. Desperate measure, but it might pay off eventually if Split grow complacent.</t>
	<t id="3202">Split and Boron fought in glorious combat. Many of theirs dead. More taken prisoner. Split can expect the Atreus Currents to mount desperate attempt to bring them back, so it is safe to assume an attack will follow shortly.</t>
	<t id="3210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="3211">They are pathetically predictable. Knowing that they will attack again gives Split severe strategic advantage.</t>
	<t id="3220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="3221">It is a concerted effort of several families. You, too, can help Split improve our defences. Decisive action will see Boron vessels ground to particles.</t>
	<t id="4000">(title variants)Large-Scale Defence Construction</t>
	<t id="4001">Heavy Construction Operation</t>
	<t id="4100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="4101">While Split families bicker, Boron is united. Very much puts Split on back foot. We need to strengthen our fleet and defences. Not only so can oppose Boron military, but also to intimidate families, and in turn ensure obedience.</t>
	<t id="4102">Recent losses to Boron assaults have caused internal strife. Families start to doubt Patriarch's might. Some might say Split leadership's strategy was too offensive, and neglected to safeguard home front. A bolstered fleet and improved defensive structures should keep everyone in line.</t>
	<t id="4110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="4111">This project demands Split full attention. Boron threat cannot be underestimated or put aside any longer. Fleet has to demonstrate strength. Has to kill all who oppose Patriarch's might. Stations must to be testimony to military superiority.</t>
	<t id="4121">Anyone who can contribute to Split goal of defensive supremacy is invited to join effort.</t>
	<t id="4122">Timely response is critical, so Split turn to outside help. Any assistance in these key areas could be what tips war back in Split favour.</t>
	<t id="4200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="4201">Boron continue to suffer heavy casualties on the battlefield. Their Navy's losses brings shame upon the Atreus Currents. Recent pathetic performance gives Split enough room to fortify current position.</t>
	<t id="4202">We proud warriors show time and time again that all who oppose Split families die. Boron have not yet taken lessons to heart. Keep coming, keep dying. Split have to seize current advantage to fortify defences and expand fleet.</t>
	<t id="4210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="4211">While the enemy still reels from defeats, Split have to act. Our cause to drive back Boron and destroy any who oppose Split requires position of strength.</t>
	<t id="4220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="4221">Split looking for servants willing to provide the significant time and resources needed to help complete a number of large construction projects.</t>
	<t id="4222">Should you be experienced in ship or station construction, Split encourage you to contribute to war effort.</t>
	<t id="5000">(title variants)Secure Resources</t>
	<t id="5001">Safeguarding Resource Supplies</t>
	<t id="5100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="5101">Split Patriarch so preoccupied with battle plans and waging war, that lesser things are left unattended for longer than perhaps they should. Resources are running low. This neglect could prove fatal if not addressed.</t>
	<t id="5102">Resources are running out. Split families grow restless, and frustrated. Families need resources to fuel war effort, otherwise no way to contest Borons' current advantage.</t>
	<t id="5110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="5111">Waging war is essential to Split way of life. Unacceptable to allow industry to grind to a halt. Those responsible will be punished. Split must secure supply lines to factories and shipyards.</t>
	<t id="5120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="5121">Our patrols report an increased Atreus Currents presence, and escalation in slave revolts take noticeable effort to smother. In combination with already severe resource shortage, these new developments force Split on our knees. Split need to lay groundwork for new resource extraction.</t>
	<t id="5122">It is not only Boron Split must worry about, but also internal struggles. To keep families amenable, Split need to provide stability through secured supply lines. Procurement of resources is of crucial importance.</t>
	<t id="5200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="5201">Expansion of Split space going very well. Boron struggling to keep up fight, backing down like weaklings they are. But, rapid expansion puts stress on existing supply lines.</t>
	<t id="5202">Boron are losing majority of direct confrontations. That is why they changed strategies. Instead of nobly fighting combat fleets, they engage Split freighters and miners in pitiful attempt to weaken economy. Split protect as much as Split can, but supply deliveries have to be dependable.</t>
	<t id="5210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="5211">Well-functioning economy crucial to ability to wage war. As such, Split would be foolish to disregard its importance. Split need to secure supply lines and mining areas as well as open up new sources of raw resources.</t>
	<t id="5221">Split offer several assignments meant to safeguard supply lines and relieve economic stress. If you have the facilities to help, Split command you to take up task!</t>
	<t id="6000">(title variants)Preemptive Offensive</t>
	<t id="6001">Deterrence</t>
	<t id="6100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="6101">Atreus Currents is unrelenting in their attacks. Split need to step up offensive operations, and take fight to them. These operations, no matter how small in scale, will take pressure off of Split. Allow for coordinated counter-incursion into enemy territory.</t>
	<t id="6102">The Boron have amassed a vast number of ships and resources, and are intent on pushing into our territory. It is only matter of time. We need to initiate a preemptive attack to soften their blows, before they launch the invasion.</t>
	<t id="6110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="6111">If Split hit key military targets, Boron might change approach, or slow down assault. Then, Split have chance to improve defences or mount a meaningful large scale counter attack.</t>
	<t id="6120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="6121">Split do not understand the way wretched Boron wage war, but some behaviours are universal. Split hit hard enough and Boron have no choice but to shift efforts away from attack to defence. Split in need of valiant warriors, capable of disrupting Boron enough to trigger reaction.</t>
	<t id="6122">Caution is advised. Sometimes, even Split cannot engage enemy in direct combat. To divert enemy efforts away from attack, Split need to fall back on ambushes, and hit-and-run tactics. Only way to minimise losses and maximise damage.</t>
	<t id="6200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="6201">Split demonstrate military prowess again and again, leaving shattered ship wrecks floating in our wake. Every skirmish won, chips away at Boron resources. Split cannot allow taking off pressure now. Hits must come fast - and frequent.</t>
	<t id="6202">Split families have always valued offensive approach to war. Split not yet ready for large scale invasion into Boron space, but still, effort has to be made to keep up pressure. Constant assaults will keep Boron on the defensive while Split prepare serious campaign.</t>
	<t id="6210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="6211">Any blows dealt to the enemy will help Split efforts in the long run. Gives Split time to prepare next big push into Boron space.</t>
	<t id="6220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="6221">If you are experienced Pilot, serve Split effort to disrupt enemy operations. Get behind enemy lines and see them cower in fear of next attack. Break Boron will to fight as well as their ships.</t>
	<t id="7000">(title variants)Gather Intel</t>
	<t id="7001">Extract Intelligence</t>
	<t id="7100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="7101">An unexpected encounter with Boron ships resulted in Split scout responsible for gathering intel being shot down. Result is Split now blind to enemy movement. Unacceptable. This loss has set back Intelligence Agency, and Split need to bring intelligence network back up to be able to react to Boron movement.</t>
	<t id="7102">Amount and quality of intelligence gathered by Split officers is severely lacking. Patriarch troubled by inadequate coverage of Atreus Currents ship movement. Efficiency of Split raids depends on precise information.</t>
	<t id="7110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="7111">Solid information to act on allows Split to set ambushes and inflict critical damage to Boron war effort. Split not wait for enemy to come for Split. Split kill enemy, but only if we know their movement.</t>
	<t id="7112">Boron minds seem weak-willed compared to Split. In open combat, Split tear them apart. But the Atreus Currents is cunning, and if Split not careful, they trick us. We need more information to better understand their strategies and movement.</t>
	<t id="7120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="7121">Split identified several tasks crucial to improving intelligence network. Some require work behind enemy lines, and even direct interaction with the Atreus Currents. Risky, but fearless warrior will prevail.</t>
	<t id="7122">Pilot accepting these assignments will operate in enemy territory. Direct conflict possible. Reason why the Patriarch seeks experienced warriors for these tasks.</t>
	<t id="7200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="7201">Split pushed back wretched Boron. They hide in safety of own territory, recovering. Preparing fight back. Split cannot let up now, need information on their plans to keep upper hand.</t>
	<t id="7202">War is going well, but intelligence is outdated. If Split want to snuff out Boron for good, Split are dependant on reliable information.</t>
	<t id="7210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="7211">Split have resources and plans to improve intel, and if plans are implemented, result will be be increased efficiency in battle.</t>
	<t id="7220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="7221">Reliable, honourable servants are needed to execute these tasks. The improved intelligence network will see Split enemies ground to dust!</t>
	<t id="8000">(title variants)Support Invasion</t>
	<t id="8100">(briefing - taking sectors back - section 1)</t>
	<t id="8101">This war has shown Boron to be worthy adversaries. They advanced on several fronts. Split families fight back vigorously, but enemy is taking considerable grounds from us.</t>
	<t id="8110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="8111">Split families have come together to fight back, and reclaim what was ours. Boron will surely match Split ferocity. Split expect long-winded campaign and many dead.</t>
	<t id="8120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="8121">Now Split request help from all who are able to aid us. Support Split driving the wretched Boron out of our space. Shed their blood. Protect our combat units. Defend critical areas.</t>
	<t id="8200">(briefing - taking enemy home sectors - section 1)</t>
	<t id="8201">Due to Split warriors' determination and sacrifice, and allies such as yourself, Split are in position of strength. An opportunity presents itself to seize Boron space. Split hunt them down.</t>
	<t id="8210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="8211">This invasion will not win us the war, but taking their territory will put Split in position of significant advantage. Result will be space for families to expand into and fortify.</t>
	<t id="8220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="8221">Split seek driven and skilled warriors to join in conquest. Tasks include linking with combat wings to attack their positions as well as defend ours.</t>
	<t id="9000">(title variants)Seizing Boron Territory</t>
	<t id="9001">Engage Boron Station</t>
	<t id="9100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="9101">Hard to admit, but currently Split warriors are outmatched. They lack resources to properly defend territory against Atreus Currents. Boron can afford to coordinate and gather their strength for impressive feats of war, and all Split can do is react.</t>
	<t id="9102">Split have lost a considerable amount of ships on raids into enemy territory. Gaining hold in heavily fortified space is an issue, even for mighty Split warriors. Reason for grave humiliation is a specific station supporting Boron fleet in that space.</t>
	<t id="9110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="9111">If Split not change way this is going, consequences will be critical. Split need to hit Atreus Currents hard. Only possible solution is destroying station.</t>
	<t id="9120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="9121">It is a monumental undertaking, and only the most valiant warriors will pull it off. But, it will give Split time to recover. Split will also be able to gain ground in conflict.</t>
	<t id="9122">Right now situation is dire. Should a valiant warrior be up to the task of wrecking Station, this victory might give push to Split families, and mobilise them into attacking.</t>
	<t id="9200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="9201">Split warriors so superior to Boron scum that right now Split push into several enemy fronts successfully. Split are looking to conquer Boron sector, and drive the weaklings out. Best way to go after them is to destroy their structures.</t>
	<t id="9202">Families are fighting united. Patriarch is demanding blood of Split enemies. Soon, Boron space will belong to Split. We are looking to do critical damage to their sector control. Split spent enough time shooting down ships, now Split go after their stations.</t>
	<t id="9210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="9211">If Split destroy Boron station, Atreus Currents could lose control of supplies and manufacturing. Or they might be open to all out attack on sector, without defence.</t>
	<t id="9220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="9221">This task only suitable for the most trusted, powerful allies. It will be great challenge, but success will be met with a reward even greater.</t>
	<t id="100001">Supply Provisions</t>
	<t id="100002">Split warriors require sustenance. If food ever runs out, families will assuredly rise up to overthrow Patriarch. If Atreus Currents is smart, they will eventually try to starve Split out. Split must be prepared. Supply provisions so Split warriors remain content.</t>
	<t id="100003">{30141,303}</t>
	<t id="100004">{30141,304}</t>
	<t id="100101">Combat Supplies Required</t>
	<t id="100102">Well-stocked armoury is mandatory for besting enemy. Supplies needed to build ships and equipment are in danger of running low. Split require pilot able to bring these resources.</t>
	<t id="100103">{30141,403}</t>
	<t id="100104">{30141,404}</t>
	<t id="101001">Set up Split Defence</t>
	<t id="101002">Split always working on complex defensive structures, but basic defensive measures cannot be neglected. Several regions in Split space still lack fundamental defence. Tasks like setting up laser towers might not bring the rush of a good fight, but need doing. So do them.</t>
	<t id="101003">{30136,110}</t>
	<t id="101004">{30136,111}</t>
	<t id="101005">{30136,112}</t>
	<t id="101006">{30136,113}</t>
	<t id="101101">Improve Split Families' Defences</t>
	<t id="101102">Split need to secure entry points to Split families' neighbouring sectors. Boron regularly send assault teams to sabotage supply lines. Mines will make access to Split space more dangerous. Drop Mines at strategic access points.</t>
	<t id="101103">{30136,120}</t>
	<t id="101104">{30136,121}</t>
	<t id="101105">{30136,122}</t>
	<t id="101106">{30136,123}</t>
	<t id="101201">Block Slave Escape</t>
	<t id="101202">Boron slaves are becoming more and more defiant. Many try to make a break for Boron space in hijacked ships. In response, Split plan to install mines at sector entry points. Will not return escaped slaves, but their deaths will likely deter potential imitators.</t>
	<t id="101203">{30136,120}</t>
	<t id="101204">{30136,121}</t>
	<t id="101205">{30136,122}</t>
	<t id="101206">{30136,123}</t>
	<t id="101301">Deploy Static Defence</t>
	<t id="101302">The Atreus Currents has been eyeing Split regions rich in resources. We will not allow anyone to tap Split space, least of all our enemies. Deploy laser towers to protect areas critical to Split economy.</t>
	<t id="101303">{30136,110}</t>
	<t id="101304">{30136,111}</t>
	<t id="101305">{30136,112}</t>
	<t id="101306">{30136,113}</t>
	<t id="101401">Critical Satellite Placement</t>
	<t id="101402">Split cunning! Split identified area Boron frequently travels through. Split plan to deploy single satellite. But, Split not only want it deployed for enemy visibility, but also to bait Boron into ordering a convoy to stop and take it out. Then, we ambush Boron and take them out.</t>
	<t id="101403">{30136,130}</t>
	<t id="101404">{30136,131}</t>
	<t id="101405">{30136,132}</t>
	<t id="101406">{30136,133}</t>
	<t id="101410">{30004,5005}(normal satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="101411">{30004,5006}(advanced satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="102001">Split Sector Visibility</t>
	<t id="102002">Split want sector to be scattered with satellites. It will help Split be prepared for Boron attacks, but that is not the only purpose. Additional benefit is keeping eye on Split families the Patriarch suspects might revolt. If Split can spot insubordination before they pick up momentum, Split can deal with them easily.\n$REQUIREMENTS$</t>
	<t id="102003">{30102,1}</t>
	<t id="102004">{30102,2}</t>
	<t id="102010">{30102,3}(advanced-satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="102011">{30102,4}(area-hint)</t>
	<t id="102101">Satellites Required In Boron Space</t>
	<t id="102102">Your task is to place Satellites in enemy space. Split aware that satellites will not last long. Eventual destruction acceptable, as long as Split get picture of current enemy movement.\n$REQUIREMENTS$</t>
	<t id="102103">{30102,1}</t>
	<t id="102104">{30102,2}</t>
	<t id="102110">{30102,3}(advanced-satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="102111">{30102,4}(area-hint)</t>
	<t id="103001">Repair Damaged Split Ships</t>
	<t id="103002">Conflicts with Boron often leave our ships severely damaged. While Split prioritise fixing most grievous issues in shipyards, Split are looking for pilot to help fix minor damage to hull and external sub-systems in space.</t>
	<t id="103003">{30146,10}</t>
	<t id="103004">{30146,11}</t>
	<t id="103005">{30146,12}</t>
	<t id="104001">Deliver Courageous Champions To Front</t>
	<t id="104002">You have honour of transporting famed Split fighters to front. Heroes upholding the name of Patriarch have killed hundreds each. They will first train undisciplined Split grunts on front line before joining the fight. We require many pilots for this special delivery. Make sure valiant warriors arrive safely.</t>
	<t id="104003">(comeonboard conversation option){1002,3015}</t>
	<t id="104007">(onboardnotification){30004,5102}</t>
	<t id="104008">(passengerleftnotification){30004,5103}</t>
	<t id="104009">(male)Transport war hero</t>
	<t id="104010">(female)Transport war hero</t>
	<t id="105001">Build Military Base</t>
	<t id="105002">Split recognise value of an impenetrable defence. Patriarch has decreed a station be built in specific location to protect families from Boron invasion. Specifications as follows:</t>
	<t id="105003">(objective1){30004,5201}</t>
	<t id="105004">(objective2){30004,5213}</t>
	<t id="105005">(objective3 - Defence Station){30004,5211}</t>
	<t id="105006">(objective4){30004,5203}</t>
	<t id="105007">(Destination){30120,200}</t>
	<t id="106101">Split Expansion Calculations</t>
	<t id="106102">Split always looking to expand into enemy space. Once Split snuff out Boron fleets and drive survivors out of sector, Split must immediately get to work. Defence stations need to be built to secure position. Split need to know what resources are available in enemy territory. Find high-yield regions of the following resource: $WARENAMES$</t>
	<t id="106103">{30132,1}</t>
	<t id="106110">{30132,10}</t>
	<t id="106111">{30132,11}</t>
	<t id="107001">Take Out Boron Hotshot</t>
	<t id="107003">(male)Split realised that one valiant Boron warrior has been responsible for many sullied family names throughout this conflict. Split cannot tolerate this dangerous enemy to live unpunished. Split want him dead.</t>
	<t id="107004">(female)Split realised that one valiant Boron warrior has been responsible for many sullied family names throughout this conflict. Split cannot tolerate this dangerous enemy to live unpunished. Split want her dead.</t>
	<t id="107005">(ma target)\nHe was last seen flying ship with ID: $SHIPID$. Kill him.</t>
	<t id="107006">(fe target)\nShe was last seen flying ship with ID: $SHIPID$. Kill her.</t>
	<t id="107101">(female)Make An Example Out Of $NPCName$</t>
	<t id="107103">(male)$NPCName$ recently supported a slave revolt. He helped slaves escape their bonds and supplied them with a ship. Slaves made for Boron territory. Occasionally this happen, but most times Split capture or kill them before they vanish. Not so this time. With $NPCName$'s help they slipped our reach. This story is now inspiration to other captives. Split want him killed, as demonstration that no one ever interferes with Split affairs without facing consequences.</t>
	<t id="107104">(female)$NPCName$ recently supported a slave revolt. She helped slaves escape their bonds and supplied them with a ship. Slaves made for Boron territory. Occasionally this happen, but most times Split capture or kill them before they vanish. Not so this time. With $NPCName$'s help they slipped our reach. This story is now inspiration to other captives. Split want her killed, as demonstration that no one ever interferes with Split affairs without facing consequences.</t>
	<t id="107105">(ma target)\nHe was last seen flying ship with ID: $SHIPID$. Kill him.</t>
	<t id="107106">(fe target)\nShe was last seen flying ship with ID: $SHIPID$. Kill her.</t>
	<t id="108001">Seize Boron Ship</t>
	<t id="108002">Split command wants to own Boron ship to analyse its technology and decode its military encryption. Only reliable way to get hands on ship is a boarding operation. Restraint is not a strength of Split military. Chances of target ship being destroyed completely, if engaged by Split fleet, is very high. That is why Split give task to you.</t>
	<t id="108003">{30004,4001}</t>
	<t id="108004">(fe target){199430215,108002}</t>
	<t id="109001">Support Invasion</t>
	<t id="109002">Split have privilege of shedding blood for sector control. We demand our allies to support our offensive in whatever way possible.</t>
	<t id="110001">Looking For Pilots</t>
	<t id="110002">Split in need of pilots. Many capable veterans lose their lives on the battlefield every time Split engage enemy, and it hard to find replacement. Split not want incompetent pilots in their ranks, but high turnover sometimes leaves little choice. So, Split ask you to find suitable people to fight in war.\nWe are looking for $NPCCOUNT$ pilot\(s\) to undergo provisional tests for Split rapid-response program.\n$DESTINATION$\n$SKILLS$</t>
	<t id="110003">Pilot</t>
	<t id="110004">$NPCCOUNT$ Pilots</t>
	<t id="110005">(progress bar)Pilots</t>
	<t id="110101">Station Engineers Needed</t>
	<t id="110102">To ensure military installation functioning in times of war, Split are looking for $NPCCOUNT$ engineer\(s\) to be brought to Split station. Experience in maintaining weapons systems mandatory.\n$DESTINATION$\n$SKILLS$</t>
	<t id="110103">(Acquire)Station Engineer</t>
	<t id="110104">(Acquire)$NPCCOUNT$ Station Engineers</t>
	<t id="110105">(progress bar)Engineers</t>
	<t id="120001">Assemble Fleet</t>
	<t id="120002">Split always plan expansion. An increase in conflicts with Atreus Currents assured. In anticipation, Split ask you to help out in fleet production, as Split shipyards always run at capacity. To aid war effort, bring following ships to $SECTOR$ :\n$FLEET$</t>
	<t id="120003">(deliver:)Combat ship</t>
	<t id="120004">(deliver:)$NEEDED$ Combat ships</t>
	<t id="120005">{30004,5301}</t>
	<t id="120006">{30004,5304}</t>
	<t id="120011">{30004,5302}</t>
	<t id="120012">{30004,5303}</t>
	<t id="130001">Split Station Demands Supplies</t>
	<t id="130002">Several families have grown increasingly restless, as the war with Boron has begun to impact their supply lines. State of Split economy has a direct impact on ability to manufacture offensive fleets, so Patriarch has agreed to assign a number of servants to help families stockpile resources.\n\nThe station related to this task requests that their resource levels are raised above: $STORAGEPERCENT$%</t>
	<t id="140001">Hunting down Boron Ships</t>
	<t id="140002">Split want to thin out Boron Navy. If you come across ships of certain type, shoot them down indiscriminately. Purpose of this project is to demoralise Boron pilots. No one wants to be potential next target.\nKeep eye out for Boron ships with following specification:\n$SHIP$</t>
	<t id="140003">{199430215,140002}</t>
	<t id="140004">{30004,1701}</t>
	<t id="140005">{30004,1702}</t>
	<t id="150001">Boron Ship Recon</t>
	<t id="150002">Split believe we have found weakness in enemy Boron ship hulls. If Split can confirm observations through scan, findings might increase combat efficiency significantly. Scan enemy ship to determine validity.\n\nTarget reveal percentage: $PERCENT$</t>
	<t id="150003">{30004,1900}</t>
	<t id="150101">Boron Station Scan</t>
	<t id="150102">Split want to initiate new invasion. To formulate new campaign, Split strategists need to evaluate several stations to determine best way forward. Split are looking to cripple economy in bid to deliver critical blow to Boron. Scan potential target station to aid Split decision.\n\nTarget reveal percentage: $PERCENT$</t>
	<t id="150103">{30004,1901}</t>
	<t id="150201">Station Module Scan</t>
	<t id="150202">Split adept at manufacturing weapons and combat ships, but lack efficiency in other industries. It would be beneficial if Split could get hands on any information regarding Boron station modules. Split can likely reverse engineer technology.\n\nSplit need the following module scanned: $MODULE$</t>
	<t id="150203">{30004,1902}</t>
	<t id="150301">Cargo Inspection</t>
	<t id="150302">Spies learned of Atreus Currents plot to send ships into Patriarch's territory to free slaves. From radio message Split intercepted, the only indication of which ship they plan to send is what ware it is currently hauling as a deception. Split now want database of all potential ships to look out for.\n\n Find an Boron ship containing: $WARE$</t>
	<t id="150303">{30004,1903}</t>
	<t id="150601">Locate Boron Coward</t>
	<t id="150602">An Boron commander recently fled the battle when Split overran his forces. As a matter of principle, this weakling cannot be allowed to live. According to Split intelligence networks, the commander has been spotted in a new ship, trying to escape our reach. Locate this ship for Split so we can dish out punishment for dishonourable conduct. The ship in question has ID code $IDCODE$</t>
	<t id="150603">{30004,1906}</t>
	<t id="150701">Atreus Currents Hull Surveillance</t>
	<t id="150702">Split hear rumours of Boron improving their ship hull manufacturing process. Critical to know what Split are dealing with, and how to upgrade current arms setup in response. Best way to gather intel on the subject is to seek out ships supplying stations with manufacturing materials. Scan Atreus Currents ships carrying hull parts so that Split know what Split are dealing with.</t>
	<t id="150703">(Scan Ship containing Ware){30004,1903}</t>
	<t id="150801">Split Scouting Shortcut</t>
	<t id="150802">Split running low on materials that are necessary to sustain war effort. Now, Split have to open up new resources to keep going. Could take immense effort to locate, and time is something Split cannot afford to lose. Split would rather focus attention on drafting battle plans. If Split could identify locations that Boron mine for ore, Split could tap existing sources once Atreus Currents has been displaced. Easiest method is to identify ships carrying ore and retrace travel path back to source. To do that, all you have to do is scan ships transporting ore.</t>
	<t id="150803">(Scan Ship containing Ware){30004,1903}</t>
	<t id="150901">Water Delivery Survey</t>
	<t id="150902">Split manufacturing stations in need of labour. Split set on raiding Boron stations to obtain new work force. To be efficient, Split need to identify easy targets with a sizeable population. Any station with a large number of inhabitants requires basic natural resources, like drinking water. If Split can keep track of how many necessities are transported to which station, Split can extrapolate population, and identify suitable target station. Help gather data by scanning ships transporting water.</t>
	<t id="150903">(Scan Ship containing Ware){30004,1903}</t>
	<t id="160001">Pave The Way</t>
	<t id="160002">Split identified Boron minefield that will make advancing Split fleet needlessly difficult. Would make things significantly simpler if it were cleared before advancing. Seek out minefield and destroy mines.</t>
	<t id="160003">{1001,1326}(Mines)</t>
	<t id="160101">Clear Boron Minefield</t>
	<t id="160102">In their desperation, Atreus Currents keeps deploying mines in hopes of inflicting casualties on Split. It is rare that reckless Split fighters fall for it. Even so, these mines should be taken care of to give Split more space to manoeuvrer. Remove them swiftly.</t>
	<t id="160103">{1001,1326}(Mines)</t>
	<t id="161001">(Lasertowers)Laser Tower Removal</t>
	<t id="161002">Last raid failed catastrophically due to Split not taking into account laser towers. During retreat, Split fighters flew into waiting arms of towers. Massive casualties. Split have to learn from this humiliation, and ensure that repeat mistake is impossible.</t>
	<t id="161003">{1001,1333}(Laser Towers)</t>
	<t id="161101">(Lasertowers)Split Offensive Measures</t>
	<t id="161102">Split are planning incursion into Boron space. Troops ready to go, but scouts spotted defence network that Boron installed to keep Split out. Dispose of laser towers to allow for Split offensive.</t>
	<t id="161103">{1001,1333}(Laser Towers)</t>
	<t id="170001">(Station)Split Attack Station</t>
	<t id="170002">Time has come for most noble task. Split want to move into enemy Boron space. In order to achieve this, Split need key Atreus Currents station razed. That is your responsibility. Will be hard fight, but good one.</t>
	<t id="170003">{1001,3}(Station)</t>
	<t id="180001">(Station)Wreck Boron Defences</t>
	<t id="180002">Split need access to Boron station in order to extract valuable work force. However, their station defences are too strong right now. If Split approach, Split will be taken apart. Should the station's turrets be destroyed, Split can approach and board station with less risk.\n\nStation: $STATION$\nAmount of turrets to destroy: $TURRETS$</t>
	<t id="180003">{30144,1003}</t>
  </page>
	
  <page id="199430216" title="ATF vs Xenon War" descr="Texts for the 'ATF vs Xenon war' mission-group and sub-mission variants" voice="no">
	<t id="1">(missiongroup)ATF Vs. Xenon</t>
	<t id="2">The Community of Planet's irresponsible inaction in containing the Xenon has once again demonstrated that Sol can only be safe if the Terran Protectorate takes a proactive stance. We request that any able citizen of the Sol system reports to their designated representative. Furthermore, we also welcome any individual from outside Sol, as long as they prove to be capable.</t>
	<t id="3">Xenon War Room</t>
	<t id="10">(intro mission)Fight for Sol!</t>
	<t id="11">These machines threaten everything we hold dear. It is crucial that we never budge, no matter the cost! Be vigilant! Destroy the enemy!</t>
	<t id="200">(Character Entity Titles)</t>
	<t id="201">Admiralty Officer</t>
	<t id="300">(Mails)</t>
	<t id="301">(Mail Greeting){30005,1001}</t>
	<t id="302">(Mail Signature){199430216,201}\n$FACTION$</t>
	<t id="310">(Mail Title)$FACTION$ - War Against the Xenon</t>
	<t id="311">(Mail Content){199430216,2}</t>
	<t id="312">(Mail Appendix){30005,2010}</t>
	<t id="1000">(common briefing texts)</t>
	<t id="1100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="1101">Despite our best efforts, the Xenon have been steadily approaching our borders and their numbers are rapidly growing.</t>
	<t id="1102">Reconnaissance has picked up a significant number of Xenon ships heading right for the Sol system.</t>
	<t id="1200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="1201">Our recent engagements with Xenon forces have resulted in massive losses on their side. However, this does not change the fact that there is still a significant Xenon presence right outside our borders.</t>
	<t id="1202">Terran scouts have registered a large Xenon presence not too far from here. While their proximity is alarming, we now know where they are, which means we can engage them on our terms.</t>
	<t id="3000">(title variants)Re-establish a Secure Perimeter</t>
	<t id="3001">Last Line of Defence</t>
	<t id="3002">Initiate Protectorate Protocol</t>
	<t id="3100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="3101">Our military has suffered heavy losses, and the Xenon are encroaching on Protectorate territory. We have to turn the tide while we still can. It is of vital importance that we re-establish a secure perimeter and set up our defences, or the Sol system will be overrun.</t>
	<t id="3102">These machines just won't stop coming. Their sheer numbers are overwhelming. The consequences of Xenon ships slipping through our defences this close to Earth would be disastrous.</t>
	<t id="3110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="3111">We simply cannot afford any holes in our line of defence. It needs to be air-tight.</t>
	<t id="3120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="3121">This war has reached the point where any negligence could result in untold civilian lives lost. A solid defence has to be our immediate priority.</t>
	<t id="3122">If we ever want to win this war, we have to make sure we have a stable base of operations. There cannot be any doubt about whether our defences will hold the Xenon at bay.</t>
	<t id="3200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="3201">The Xenon fleet regularly attempts to intrude into our space, but our defence system is maintaining the battle line and decimating their numbers. Even so, we have to make sure that our defences are adequately prepared for any possible attack.</t>
	<t id="3202">Our forces are continuing to clash with the Xenon. Right now, we have the advantage that we are fighting close to home, and we can use all of the defensive measures we have put in place to provide our pilots with backup.</t>
	<t id="3210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="3211">It is our first priority to ensure that all protocols are in place, and all of our defensive systems are in working order.</t>
	<t id="3220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="3221">You can help us with this immense task. Our work here, if done with diligence, will save many lives.</t>
	<t id="4000">(title variants)Sol Defence Efforts</t>
	<t id="4001">Operation Stronghold</t>
	<t id="4100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="4101">So far we have not been able to stop the Xenon advance. Unfortunately, we can no longer dismiss the possibility of having to engage them, here, in the Sol system.</t>
	<t id="4102">So far, all attempts at defending against the Xenon have resulted in heavy losses. It has become painfully obvious that our defences are not adequate for the threat we are facing.</t>
	<t id="4110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="4111">These recent developments have underlined the need for stronger security to be in place.</t>
	<t id="4121">We ask anyone with the necessary capabilities to help by building defence stations and expanding our fleet, to aid us in our endeavour of creating a more secure Sol system.</t>
	<t id="4122">Since the enemy is so close by, time is of the essence. It is crucial that anyone capable of helping us significantly increase our security, does so.</t>
	<t id="4200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="4201">The Xenon fleets trying to gain entry into our territory are suffering from heavy attrition thanks to our valiant troops. We have to ensure that we support the troops by supplying replacements and fortifying their defences.</t>
	<t id="4202">The Protectorate is renowned for its military supremacy. What people might not realise, though, is that it takes a lot of effort to maintain our fleets and defence stations.</t>
	<t id="4210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="4211">Now, with the enemy at our gates, it is key that we act swiftly, and decisively.</t>
	<t id="4220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="4221">It is for this reason that we must turn to outside help. If you can help deliver fleets or build defence stations, you are duty-bound to do so.</t>
	<t id="4222">We are asking anyone experienced in ship or station construction to aid us in our task. Lives depend on it.</t>
	<t id="5000">(title variants)Secure Supplies</t>
	<t id="5001">Ensure Resource Supplies</t>
	<t id="5100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="5101">With the Xenon so close at hand, we had little option but to focus all of our attention on keeping them back. Now, that narrow focus has resulted in our supply lines coming under threat.</t>
	<t id="5102">Unfortunately, the Xenon fleet's movement has caused some areas, specifically ones that the Protectorate usually relies on for resources, to become unavailable. This is unacceptable.</t>
	<t id="5110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="5111">A resource shortage in this critical situation could lose the war and seal all our fates.</t>
	<t id="5120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="5121">While we increase pressure on the Xenon fleet in an attempt to push it back from our borders, we need the help of someone who can identify new ways of procuring the required resources that fuel this war effort.</t>
	<t id="5122">Resource availability has to become our second-largest focus, next to protecting our system from being overrun. Things are not looking good, and we need help with maintaining a reliable resource supply.</t>
	<t id="5200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="5201">While our recent war efforts have been going well, Command is worried about potential supply shortages. Some of our usual ways of obtaining resources have become unavailable due to the shifting war front.</t>
	<t id="5202">Thanks to the tremendous efforts of our troops, the Xenon are losing ground. We are steadily pushing them away from our borders. However, we are also worried that our current resource supplies might not be sufficent, should the Xenon launch a prolonged counter-offensive.</t>
	<t id="5210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="5211">These resources are of critical importance in maintaining our fleet.</t>
	<t id="5221">As such, it is important to ensure the supply of raw materials and resources. Outsourcing these urgent tasks would take a lot of pressure off of our own military. If you have the facilities, please consider taking up this responsibility.</t>
	<t id="6000">(title variants)Preemptive Defence</t>
	<t id="6001">Counter Offensive</t>
	<t id="6100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="6101">The Xenon attacks are unrelenting. Our fleet is able to hold them off, but just barely. Anything that tips the scales in their favour might become a watershed moment, and our system could be overrun.</t>
	<t id="6102">The fighting outside our borders has not let up. We are taking heavy casualties, and so are they. The battle lines have become very entrenched, and High Command does not like them to be drawn this close to home.</t>
	<t id="6110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="6111">We need more room to manoeuvre. If we could ease the pressure, we could focus on rebuilding our defences, stocking up our supplies and starting to push back.</t>
	<t id="6120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="6121">We need more fighters on our side. You would not have to beat back their entire fleet. It would suffice if you hit them enough to tip the scales back in our favour.</t>
	<t id="6122">Right now, we need all the help we can get. Any combat pilot who is capable of inflicting casualties on the Xenon is welcome to join our efforts.</t>
	<t id="6200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="6201">The results of our ongoing military campaign have far exceeded our expectations. We have a real opportunity to push the Xenon fleet away from our borders for good.</t>
	<t id="6202">While it is worrying that the Xenon were ever able to establish a presence so close to our system in the first place, our fleet has done a tremendous job of keeping them in check.</t>
	<t id="6210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="6211">If we can press our advantage, and do not let up, we will be able to regain ground currently occupied by the Xenon, and re-establish a safety zone between them and Sol.</t>
	<t id="6220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="6221">If you are an experienced Pilot, we invite you to take part in this initiative. Destroy as many of these machines as you can. It will help turn the tides of war.</t>
	<t id="7000">(title variants)Front Line Reconnaissance</t>
	<t id="7001">Sol System Intelligence</t>
	<t id="7100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="7101">The Terran Secret Service is preoccupied with a number of operations outside Sol, so they have reached out and asked to outsource all intelligence work pertaining to the Xenon threat outside our borders.</t>
	<t id="7102">Despite the worrying fact that the Xenon have established a presence close to our system, we do not have much actionable intelligence on their numbers, or their movements.</t>
	<t id="7110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="7111">Accurate information is critical to waging a war. Especially if you are up against an enemy that, while fundamentally unpredictable, has at times displayed recognisable patterns. We can leverage that fact to our advantage.</t>
	<t id="7112">With the Xenon having managed to gain a foothold so close to our home, we need any advantage we can get. Even in the face of superior technology, or a much larger fleet, almost any battle can be turned around through actionable intel.</t>
	<t id="7120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="7121">There are tasks which will help improve the data we have gathered on the Xenon. Some of them might bring you into close contact with them, while others are less direct. They are all equally important to securing Terran space.</t>
	<t id="7122">To be able to defend our system, we are dependent on capable pilots to map out the enemy territory, and gather as much intelligence as possible without them putting themselves at risk.</t>
	<t id="7200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="7201">The military has been making good progress in pushing the Xenon away from our gates. However, we frequently lose ships due to a lack of information on enemy movement and fleet strength. This issue is quite unfortunate, but it can be addressed.</t>
	<t id="7202">After much back and forth, the Protectorate has finally gained the upper hand, and can purge the Xenon outside their gates. However, in order to ensure all machines are located and properly dealt with, we need to gather more intelligence.</t>
	<t id="7210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="7211">An increase in the quality and quantity of the information we gather could save Terran lives and help eradicate the Xenon presence going forward.</t>
	<t id="7220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="7221">We have assembled a list of tasks that need to be fulfilled to improve our intel. You can help us establish the new network that will deliver this crucial information to our headquarters.</t>
	<t id="8000">(title variants)Support the Strike Force</t>
	<t id="8100">(briefing - taking sectors back - section 1)</t>
	<t id="8101">The Xenon have gained significant ground on us. It is simply unacceptable to cede control of our territory to them. For this reason, High Command has decreed the reclamation of lost ground to be our highest priority.</t>
	<t id="8110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="8111">In fighting the enemy, our military has suffered heavy losses. For that reason, we ask that everyone, no matter what their specialisation, gets involved in our takeover efforts.</t>
	<t id="8120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="8121">You do not have to be a brave combat pilot to leave a mark. You can transport officers to the front, or set up a defensive perimeter in the sector. All are duty-bound to do their part.</t>
	<t id="8200">(briefing - taking enemy home sectors - section 1)</t>
	<t id="8201">Through the united efforts of our valiant military branches, we have gained a position of strength over the Xenon. We have to press the advantage, and move forward into Xenon space.</t>
	<t id="8210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="8211">Taking Xenon territory is a crucial objective on the path to winning this war. It will significantly weaken their forces, and each system we free from this scourge means one more layer of protection between us and them.</t>
	<t id="8220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="8221">To ensure that this advance is a success, everyone who is capable of helping is urged to do their part. You can ferry officers, secure objectives or deliver supplies; it does make a difference!</t>
	<t id="9000">(title variants)Destroy Xenon Site</t>
	<t id="9001">Operation Station Siege</t>
	<t id="9100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="9101">We have suffered significant losses, and morale is waning. High Command is putting pressure on us to produce a victory to show to the Terran people. To that end we have identified a Xenon station of note.</t>
	<t id="9102">We have identified a station, not far from our system, that supplies the Xenon fleet. If we were to tear it down, we would be able to slow the Xenon attacks, and potentially open up that system for a counter-offensive.</t>
	<t id="9110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="9111">It has now become our top priority to take it down, not only to weaken the Xenon foothold in the system, but also to lift the spirits of our military cadets, and the civilian population.</t>
	<t id="9120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="9121">Tearing down a hostile station is no small feat. This is why we only approach the most trusted and powerful of our allies to execute this operation.</t>
	<t id="9122">Right now the situation is critical. If we do not take that station down, we might lose the war. Only our most powerful allies will be capable of helping us with this undertaking.</t>
	<t id="9200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="9201">We have fought long and hard to secure our borders from the Xenon. It seems their attacks have grown less intense. Now, we have to seize the moment, first to significantly reduce their presence here, and then to push them away from our system.</t>
	<t id="9202">We are able to defend ourselves quite well from the Xenon. A certain routine has set in, where our fighters know exactly how to engage them. The problem is, this status quo will not be broken if we do not change tack.</t>
	<t id="9210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="9211">We must be coordinated, and strike the enemy with determination. We have to come together with the single purpose of destroying their Xenon station.</t>
	<t id="9220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="9221">This task is only suitable for the most trusted, powerful allies of the Protectorate. However, should you succeed in tearing down the station, you will have significantly improved our situation.</t>
	<t id="10000">(title variants)Force Projection</t>
	<t id="10001">A Show of Strength</t>
	<t id="10002">First Line of Defence</t>
	<t id="10100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="10101">The Xenon may have set up their base somewhere far from Sol, but that does not mean that we can turn a blind eye to the infestation. They continue to wreak havoc in the universe and, if left unchecked, they will only grow in numbers.</t>
	<t id="10102">We need to hunt down the Xenon, no matter how far away from Earth they are holed up. We will not be safe until they no longer have any corner of the universe to call their own.</t>
	<t id="10110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="10111">Our military is fighting them, no matter how far they have to travel to meet the Xenon in combat. Unfortunately, though, waging war so far from your stations represents a logistical challenge.</t>
	<t id="10120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="10121">It is imperative that these fleets are supported out there. We cannot let them venture out into the unknown without adequate protection and supplies. We ask anyone who can, to make the journey and help our troops.</t>
	<t id="10122">Since we cannot afford to divert our Sol-based fleets to support the war effort on the far end of the universe, we have to rely on recruiting a third party.</t>
	<t id="10200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="10201">The Protectorate must carry the shining beacon of humanity into the deepest, darkest corners of the Gate network. Only then can we truly protect humanity.</t>
	<t id="10202">When we were reconnected with the network, it soon became apparent that we had to take the fight to the Xenon systems, and that we had to disregard the Community of Planets' sovereignty to do so efficiently.</t>
	<t id="10210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="10211">Since we cannot rely on any other organisations, it is challenging to supply and maintain a fleet that far out from home.</t>
	<t id="10220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="10221">It is for this reason that we approach powerful allies such as yourself for help. We would pay well if you could help establish our first line of defence out there.</t>
	<t id="11000">(title variants)Large-Scale Offensive Construction</t>
	<t id="11001">Heavy Construction Operation</t>
	<t id="11002">Beachhead Operations</t>
	<t id="11100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="11101">The Xenon are still overrunning systems and growing in strength. The fact that these systems are far outside our usual reach cannot matter. These machines will eventually find their way here, and they will leave a swathe of destruction in their path.</t>
	<t id="11102">It is the nature of self-replicating machines that they will grow exponentially in both strength and number. It would be tempting to ignore those Xenon strongholds far away from Sol, but we cannot afford to ease off and rely on the Community of Planets to handle the threat appropriately.</t>
	<t id="11110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="11111">Our fleets are currently tied up in border skirmishes with Xenon strays and pirate elements.</t>
	<t id="11121">It is a challenge to establish a meaningful presence halfway across the universe, and should you help us in these endeavours, you would be handsomely rewarded for doing so.</t>
	<t id="11122">Should you elect to aid us with this military operation in far-off space, the Protectorate would be eternally grateful.</t>
	<t id="11200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="11201">The Terran Protectorate aims to carry the light of human ascendancy into the farmost reaches of space. To seek the Xenon menace and exterminate it is our most founding principle.</t>
	<t id="11202">We have decisively beaten back the Xenon forces from our borders. As a result, we now have the resources to focus on more remote systems that have been overrun by the Xenon.</t>
	<t id="11210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="11211">We are looking to establish a presence and to push out into hostile Xenon space. If we do not take this fight to them, we are dealing with the symptoms, but we are not treating the disease.</t>
	<t id="11220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="11221">Due to the challenges of coordinating an operation this remote, we are looking for suitable partners to help us in our efforts.</t>
	<t id="11222">We have compiled a list of tasks for you, should you wish to help the Protectorate cut through the remote Xenon haunts.</t>
	<t id="12000">(title variants)Far-Off Offensive</t>
	<t id="12001">Preemptive Intervention</t>
	<t id="12100">(briefing - negative mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="12101">Our reports indicate that the Xenon are amassing in large numbers in a distant system. It is only a matter of time before they make their way to Sol.</t>
	<t id="12102">When the Gates reconnected, our leaders proclaimed that the Protectorate was going to become the absolute authority on protecting and policing the Gate network. We intend to fulfil our pledge. Our next target is going to be a distant Xenon system, far from Earth.</t>
	<t id="12110">(briefing - negative mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="12111">These Xenon fleets may be far away, but they are not outside the Protectorate's grasp. It is our intention to whittle down their numbers long before they find their way to the Sol system and become a threat to the Terran people.</t>
	<t id="12120">(briefing - negative mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="12121">While the Protectorate does not need help, it is a good opportunity for you to prove your mettle by assisting our fleet in this offensive operation.</t>
	<t id="12122">Since this operation will take place in a remote location, without the ability to quickly respond and send backup, we offer experienced Pilots such as yourself the opportunity to aid us.</t>
	<t id="12200">(briefing - positive mood - section 1)</t>
	<t id="12201">We are currently preparing an offensive into faraway Xenon territory. Too long has the Community of Planets turned a blind eye to the forces of destruction growing in its midst.</t>
	<t id="12202">The Xenon have been growing stronger in far-off systems, undisturbed by the other inhabitants of the Jump Gate network.</t>
	<t id="12210">(briefing - positive mood - section 2)</t>
	<t id="12211">If we want the Xenon menace dealt with, we have to be proactive and do it ourselves. Unfortunately, there is no other way.</t>
	<t id="12220">(briefing - positive mood - section 3)</t>
	<t id="12221">If you are an experienced Pilot, we invite you to join this operation. Disrupting the enemy on their home turf is our primary objective. Whittle down the Xenon numbers, and show the other factions how it is done.</t>
	<t id="100001">Feeding the Troops</t>
	<t id="100002">It takes a tremendous amount of effort and coordination to supply a Terran fleet out there. We have to ensure that our valiant troops are well equipped. Help us to supply them with provisions so that they can keep the universe safe.</t>
	<t id="100003">{30141,303}</t>
	<t id="100004">{30141,304}</t>
	<t id="100101">Request for Combat Supplies</t>
	<t id="100102">A well-stocked armoury is the key to beating back these soulless machines. Supplies also help to assemble and maintain our vast fleets. The Protectorate hopes that you can help transport resources to the areas in which they are needed.</t>
	<t id="100103">{30141,403}</t>
	<t id="100104">{30141,404}</t>
	<t id="101001">Set up Defensive Perimeter</t>
	<t id="101002">Maintaining a secure perimeter takes a lot of effort. Laser Towers are often the very first things that get damaged or destroyed during a Xenon invasion, yet they are critical in slowing down the enemy and holding them off. Please see to it that our perimeter is well defended.</t>
	<t id="101003">{30136,110}</t>
	<t id="101004">{30136,111}</t>
	<t id="101005">{30136,112}</t>
	<t id="101006">{30136,113}</t>
	<t id="101101">Explosive Defences</t>
	<t id="101102">Since the Xenon are machines at their core, they will always exhibit a certain amount of predictable behaviour. Our military can capitalise on that fact by laying minefields to deny them easy access to strategic positions. We could really use a hand in deploying these mines.</t>
	<t id="101103">{30136,120}</t>
	<t id="101104">{30136,121}</t>
	<t id="101105">{30136,122}</t>
	<t id="101106">{30136,123}</t>
	<t id="101201">Minefield Diplomacy</t>
	<t id="101202">We have had notable success in cutting down enemy attacks through strategically placed minefields. If they do not destroy a fleet outright, they will usually slow them down enough for us to initiate a counterattack. As such, it is important to continuously expand our network of minefields.</t>
	<t id="101203">{30136,120}</t>
	<t id="101204">{30136,121}</t>
	<t id="101205">{30136,122}</t>
	<t id="101206">{30136,123}</t>
	<t id="101301">Deny Resource Field Access</t>
	<t id="101302">The Xenon have repeatedly attempted to access resource fields located within our jurisdiction; resource fields which we are relying on to keep our economy running, and our fleets stocked. We need to shore up our defences and ensure they cannot access these fields. Deploying Laser Towers should be an efficient deterrence.</t>
	<t id="101303">{30136,110}</t>
	<t id="101304">{30136,111}</t>
	<t id="101305">{30136,112}</t>
	<t id="101306">{30136,113}</t>
	<t id="101401">Bring Satellite System online</t>
	<t id="101402">Far too often have Xenon attacks caught us off-guard. While none of their attacks so far have been able to penetrate all of our defences and find their way to Earth, we cannot risk them taking us by surprise. Help us to improve the quality of our intel by enhancing our satellite system.</t>
	<t id="101403">{30136,130}</t>
	<t id="101404">{30136,131}</t>
	<t id="101405">{30136,132}</t>
	<t id="101406">{30136,133}</t>
	<t id="101410">{30004,5005}(normal satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="101411">{30004,5006}(advanced satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="101501">Offensive Fortifications</t>
	<t id="101502">When our fleets invade Xenon space, we want to make sure that they are secured along their flanks. One straightforward way of offering protection is to install Laser Towers in the Xenon system. You, too, can help the Terran Protectorate to prepare for our next offensive by deploying these front-line Laser Towers.</t>
	<t id="101503">{30136,110}</t>
	<t id="101504">{30136,111}</t>
	<t id="101505">{30136,112}</t>
	<t id="101506">{30136,113}</t>
	<t id="101601">Laser Tower Initiative</t>
	<t id="101602">Our combat analysts have reviewed multiple data sources, and concluded that the presence of Laser Towers in combat areas has a positive effect on the outcome of the battle. Based on this, the Protectorate has developed an initiative which aims at deploying Laser Towers in any potential theatre of war.</t>
	<t id="101603">{30136,110}</t>
	<t id="101604">{30136,111}</t>
	<t id="101605">{30136,112}</t>
	<t id="101606">{30136,113}</t>
	<t id="101701">Booby Trapping Xenon Territory</t>
	<t id="101702">Creating minefields in Xenon territory may not be the one thing that will end this war, but deploying them still reliably slows down Xenon supply ships, and disrupts their routines. Attrition is a considerable factor in any war, and therefore tasks like these, even if they seem menial, are vitally important.</t>
	<t id="101703">{30136,120}</t>
	<t id="101704">{30136,121}</t>
	<t id="101705">{30136,122}</t>
	<t id="101706">{30136,123}</t>
	<t id="101801">Distant Minefield Operations</t>
	<t id="101802">The Community of Planets has shown themselves to be very reluctant to deploy minefields in order to protect themselves from Xenon attacks. The Protectorate does not hesitate to employ mines in order to inflict damage on Xenon fleets. Any Xenon ship taken out by mines is a ship we do not have to engage in combat.</t>
	<t id="101803">{30136,120}</t>
	<t id="101804">{30136,121}</t>
	<t id="101805">{30136,122}</t>
	<t id="101806">{30136,123}</t>
	<t id="101901">Eyes Behind Enemy Lines</t>
	<t id="101902">Ideally, the Terran Protectorate would be aware of the enemy's movements before they even finish mobilising their fleets. In order to achieve that, though, we need Satellites in their territory. Deploying Satellites this close to the enemy can be dangerous, so stay watchful.</t>
	<t id="101903">{30136,130}</t>
	<t id="101904">{30136,131}</t>
	<t id="101905">{30136,132}</t>
	<t id="101906">{30136,133}</t>
	<t id="101910">{30004,5005}(normal satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="101911">{30004,5006}(advanced satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="102001">Terran Sector Visibility</t>
	<t id="102002">While the Protectorate's attention is always focused on the Terran border, along with any systems that have been overrun by the Xenon, it is important not to lose sight of our own back yard. Having an already established satellite network would prove very useful in the case of the Xenon actually pushing into this system. Please make sure that we are adequately covered by the Satellites.\n$REQUIREMENTS$</t>
	<t id="102003">{30102,1}</t>
	<t id="102004">{30102,2}</t>
	<t id="102010">{30102,3}(advanced-satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="102011">{30102,4}(area-hint)</t>
	<t id="102101">Satellites Required In Xenon Space</t>
	<t id="102102">Our Satellites do not last long in Xenon territory. The enemy will actively seek them out, and destroy them. Despite their fragility, the Satellites' intel is invaluable to the war effort. Your task, therefore, is to enter enemy space and replace those that have been lost.\n$REQUIREMENTS$</t>
	<t id="102103">{30102,1}</t>
	<t id="102104">{30102,2}</t>
	<t id="102110">{30102,3}(advanced-satellite hint)</t>
	<t id="102111">{30102,4}(area-hint)</t>
	<t id="103001">Repair Damaged Terran Ships</t>
	<t id="103002">Clashes with Xenon forces routinely leave ships in our fleet damaged. Our military fleets have grown to such a size that maintaining them and repairing them after battle has become a genuine challenge. That is why we have asked our allies to help out with the repairs.</t>
	<t id="103003">{30146,10}</t>
	<t id="103004">{30146,11}</t>
	<t id="103005">{30146,12}</t>
	<t id="103101">Urgent Repair For Remote Craft</t>
	<t id="103102">We have received a distress call requesting the repair of a ship which has been stranded far outside our sphere of influence. They have been ambushed by the Xenon and, while they were able to escape, they are now sitting out in the open without adequate defences. Since the ship is some distance from our nearest available support units, we have delegated this urgent matter to you.</t>
	<t id="103103">{30146,10}</t>
	<t id="103104">{30146,11}</t>
	<t id="103105">{30146,12}</t>
	<t id="104001">Help Assemble our Best and Brightest</t>
	<t id="104002">The Sol system has always been renowned for its citizens' fighting spirit. It comes as no surprise, therefore, that the military is rarely short of motivated, skilled young cadets, itching to get in on the action. So many, in fact, that it can be hard to coordinate their transport. So, we need your help in bringing them all together.</t>
	<t id="104003">(comeonboard conversation option){1002,3015}</t>
	<t id="104007">(onboardnotification){30004,5102}</t>
	<t id="104008">(passengerleftnotification){30004,5103}</t>
	<t id="104009">(male)Transport Cadet</t>
	<t id="104010">(female)Transport Cadet</t>
	<t id="104101">Deliver Marines to Distant Front</t>
	<t id="104102">As you may be aware, the Protectorate is fighting the Xenon on remote fronts. We have recently suffered casualties and need to bolster our numbers. Aid us in shuttling our marines to the war front.</t>
	<t id="104103">(comeonboard conversation option){1002,3015}</t>
	<t id="104107">(onboardnotification){30004,5102}</t>
	<t id="104108">(passengerleftnotification){30004,5103}</t>
	<t id="104109">(male)Transport military personnel</t>
	<t id="104110">(female)Transport military personnel</t>
	<t id="105001">Build Military Infrastructure</t>
	<t id="105002">Our primary line of defence will always be strategically placed Defence Stations. They are instrumental in keeping the enemy fleets at bay. We need to increase the number of Defence Stations in our system, and we want you to help build a station that fits our specifications.</t>
	<t id="105003">(objective1){30004,5201}</t>
	<t id="105004">(objective2){30004,5213}</t>
	<t id="105005">(objective3 - Defence Station){30004,5211}</t>
	<t id="105006">(objective4){30004,5203}</t>
	<t id="105007">(Destination){30120,200}</t>
	<t id="105101">Remote Vanguard Station</t>
	<t id="105102">The Protectorate is not the only power waging war against the Xenon. These machines are a blight on all races of the network. Since our military superiority affords us a unique position, we have to aggressively expand our bases into distant systems to help keep the Xenon in check. Build a station that fits our specifications.</t>
	<t id="105103">(objective1){30004,5201}</t>
	<t id="105104">(objective2){30004,5213}</t>
	<t id="105105">(objective3 - Defence Station){30004,5211}</t>
	<t id="105106">(objective4){30004,5203}</t>
	<t id="105107">(Destination){30120,200}</t>
	<t id="106101">Offensive Resource Preparations</t>
	<t id="106102">We are looking to establish a presence in a hostile Xenon system. Before we engage the enemy, however, we need more information about that system, especially with regard to its resource fields. With a working knowledge of the area, we can quickly establish supply lines that will keep our fleet well stocked. We need you to find high-yield regions containing the following resource: $WARENAMES$</t>
	<t id="106103">{30132,1}</t>
	<t id="106110">{30132,10}</t>
	<t id="106111">{30132,11}</t>
	<t id="107201">(male)Kill the AGI Sympathiser</t>
	<t id="107202">(female)Kill the AGI Sympathiser</t>
	<t id="107203">(male)$NPCName$ has repeatedly come to our attention for his pro-AGI stance. He seems to be an influential voice in the debate. We cannot afford for the faction's stance on AGI to soften, so we have to silence him before his dangerous opinions change too many minds.</t>
	<t id="107204">(female)$NPCName$ has repeatedly come to our attention for her pro-AGI stance. She seems to be an influential voice in the debate. We cannot afford for the faction's stance on AGI to soften, so we have to silence her before her dangerous opinions change too many minds.</t>
	<t id="107205">(ma target)\nHe was last seen flying a ship with ID: $SHIPID$. Silence him.</t>
	<t id="107206">(fe target)\nShe was last seen flying a ship with ID: $SHIPID$. Silence her.</t>
	<t id="109001">Support Invasion</t>
	<t id="109002">The Terran Protectorate is conducting an offensive operation into Xenon territory. We demand that our allies support this operation in any way possible.</t>
	<t id="110001">Recruiting Pilots</t>
	<t id="110002">The Protectorate is always in need of capable pilots, willing to lay down their lives for Sol. There are plenty of skilled pilots out there, but capable pilots with this kind of fervent dedication are harder to come by. So, should you know of any such pilots, we ask you to deliver them to us for cadet school.\nWe are looking for $NPCCOUNT$ pilot\(s\)\n$DESTINATION$\n$SKILLS$</t>
	<t id="110003">Pilot</t>
	<t id="110004">$NPCCOUNT$ Pilots</t>
	<t id="110005">(progress bar)Pilots</t>
	<t id="110101">Station Engineers Needed</t>
	<t id="110102">We have to ensure that the military installations facing the Xenon are functional at all times. The Protectorate is looking for $NPCCOUNT$ engineer\(s\) to be brought to our station. Experience in maintaining weapons systems is mandatory.\n$DESTINATION$\n$SKILLS$</t>
	<t id="110103">(Acquire)Station Engineer</t>
	<t id="110104">(Acquire)$NPCCOUNT$ Station Engineers</t>
	<t id="110105">(progress bar)Engineers</t>
	<t id="110201">Foreign Forces Military Training</t>
	<t id="110202">In order to aid the other factions' fight against the Xenon, the Protectorate has offered to provide specialist military training in return for foreign policy concessions. The Protectorate is especially looking for skilled pilots who can teach our friends how to fight the Xenon. Bring any applicable candidates to the allied station.\nWe are looking for $NPCCOUNT$ pilot\(s\) to train their forces.\n$DESTINATION$\n$SKILLS$</t>
	<t id="110203">Pilot</t>
	<t id="110204">$NPCCOUNT$ Pilots</t>
	<t id="110205">(progress bar)Pilots</t>
	<t id="110301">Engineers Needed for Remote Work</t>
	<t id="110302">It is not always possible for us to maintain our fleets that are fighting the Xenon in systems that are far remote from Sol. For this reason that we have arranged for Terran Protectorate Engineers to be assigned on allied stations, so that they can help maintain far-off ships.\n$DESTINATION$\n$SKILLS$</t>
	<t id="110303">(Acquire)Engineer</t>
	<t id="110304">(Acquire)$NPCCOUNT$ Engineers</t>
	<t id="110305">(progress bar)Engineers</t>
	<t id="120001">Assemble Fleet</t>
	<t id="120002">The Protectorate is preparing a fleet to meet the Xenon forces head-on. The fleet has to be sizeable enough to protect Sol's borders from this, and any future, threat. You can help our war effort by binging the following ships to $SECTOR$ :\n$FLEET$</t>
	<t id="120003">(deliver:)Combat ship</t>
	<t id="120004">(deliver:)$NEEDED$ Combat ships</t>
	<t id="120005">{30004,5301}</t>
	<t id="120006">{30004,5304}</t>
	<t id="120011">{30004,5302}</t>
	<t id="120012">{30004,5303}</t>
	<t id="120101">Gather Fleet in Distant System</t>
	<t id="120102">We are planning to invade Xenon territory some considerable distance from Sol. For that, we need to gather a fleet. Aid us in assembling this fleet by bringing the following ships to $SECTOR$ :\n$FLEET$</t>
	<t id="120103">(deliver:)Combat ship</t>
	<t id="120104">(deliver:)$NEEDED$ Combat ships</t>
	<t id="120105">{30004,5301}</t>
	<t id="120106">{30004,5304}</t>
	<t id="120111">{30004,5302}</t>
	<t id="120112">{30004,5303}</t>
	<t id="130001">Station Requests Supplies</t>
	<t id="130002">In order to adequately fight off Xenon forces, our stations need to be well stocked. Without medical equipment, ammunition and miscellaneous other supplies, our fighters cannot inflict the damage they ought to.\n\nThe station concerned requests that their resource levels are raised above: $STORAGEPERCENT$%</t>
	<t id="140001">Hunting down Xenon Ships</t>
	<t id="140002">Our intelligence officers have observed a Xenon fleet of impressive size that seems to be gearing up for an invasion. We need you to preemptively weaken their fleet by reducing their numbers. Our specialists have identified one type of ship type specifically, whose absence would weaken the approaching fleet.\nHunt down Xenon ships with the following specification:\n$SHIP$</t>
	<t id="140003">{199430216,140002}</t>
	<t id="140004">{30004,1701}</t>
	<t id="140005">{30004,1702}</t>
	<t id="150001">Xenon Ship Recon</t>
	<t id="150002">We believe we may have identified a structural flaw in the Xenon ships' hulls. If we could gather more data to confirm our findings, we could adapt our combat protocols accordingly. Scan a Xenon ship to gather the crucial data.\n\nTarget reveal percentage: $PERCENT$</t>
	<t id="150003">{30004,1900}</t>
	<t id="150101">Xenon Station Investigation</t>
	<t id="150102">The Protectorate is preparing an offensive into Xenon territory. Before we commit to the assault, we need to know exactly what it is that we are facing, however. Scan a Xenon station so that we can analyse what we will be up against.\n\nTarget reveal percentage: $PERCENT$</t>
	<t id="150103">{30004,1901}</t>
	<t id="150201">Module Analysis</t>
	<t id="150202">Recently, the Xenon fleet's behaviour seems to have changed, and our specialists are puzzled as to why. We suspect that it might be connected to the nearby station's layout. If we can find any aberrations, perhaps we could use any newfound insights to our advantage.\n\nYou need to scan the following module: $MODULE$</t>
	<t id="150203">{30004,1902}</t>
	<t id="150301">Xenon Cargo Inspection</t>
	<t id="150302">Based on our observations, we are expecting Xenon ship production to rise in the near future. Since they are not rational beings, the best indicator of their battle plans is what wares they convey, and which stations they supply. Help us determine their plans.\n\n Find a Xenon ship containing: $WARE$</t>
	<t id="150303">{30004,1903}</t>
	<t id="150601">Locate Xenon Ship</t>
	<t id="150602">For reasons we cannot divulge due to your lack of security clearance, the Terran Secret Service is interested in tracking one specific Xenon ship. We need to know its whereabouts at all times. Please, locate that Xenon ship for us. The ship in question has ID code $IDCODE$</t>
	<t id="150603">{30004,1906}</t>
	<t id="150701">Xenon Hull Supply Line</t>
	<t id="150702">We want to identify and trace the Xenon supply line so that we can efficiently sabotage it by strategically placing minefields and having Terran fleets patrol the route. Anything that disrupts their fleet production will help us in the long run. You can aid us in this endeavour by scanning a ship transporting Hull Parts.</t>
	<t id="150703">(Scan Ship containing Ware){30004,1903}</t>
	<t id="150801">Xenon Resource Fields</t>
	<t id="150802">We have to know where exactly the Xenon obtain their raw resources from. If we can trace their supply routes, we can ambush their ships and slow down their growth. To achieve that, all you have to do is scan ships transporting Ore.</t>
	<t id="150803">(Scan Ship containing Ware){30004,1903}</t>
	<t id="150901">Identify Water Delivery Routes</t>
	<t id="150902">The Protectorate is always in need of water supplies. Since we intend to push the Xenon out of their system, and then hold it, we need to know where in that system the Xenon obtain their water supply. You can help us identify the source by scanning ships transporting Water.</t>
	<t id="150903">(Scan Ship containing Ware){30004,1903}</t>
	<t id="160001">Clear The Trail</t>
	<t id="160002">In preparation for the upcoming military campaign, we need to make sure that we have easy access to Xenon systems. They are known to impede access by placing mines. You are ordered to seek out the minefield and destroy the mines which would slow us down.</t>
	<t id="160003">{1001,1326}(Mines)</t>
	<t id="160101">Defuse Xenon Mines</t>
	<t id="160102">We have lost too many pilots to carelessness. It is a challenge to be aware of your surroundings at all times when engaging in dogfights with the enemy. Often, solitary mines are overlooked. To reduce the risk of unnecessary casualties, we ask you to remove these mines swiftly, before we engage the Xenon again.</t>
	<t id="160103">{1001,1326}(Mines)</t>
	<t id="161001">(Lasertowers)Neutralise Laser Towers</t>
	<t id="161002">In order to secure the fleet's next foray, we have to send a team of ships solely dedicated to removing Laser Towers. They might not be able to destroy a fleet on their own, but in a fight with another fleet, they could make all the difference.</t>
	<t id="161003">{1001,1333}(Laser Towers)</t>
	<t id="161101">(Lasertowers)Clearing the Way</t>
	<t id="161102">While our forces rally to prepare a big assault on Xenon space, we need people to fly ahead and clear the way for our valiant fighters. Will you help us destroy the Xenon Laser Towers?</t>
	<t id="161103">{1001,1333}(Laser Towers)</t>
	<t id="170001">(Station)Neutralise Xenon Station</t>
	<t id="170002">It is time to focus the Protectorate's entire attention on the Xenon stations threatening all citizens of Sol. We need you to destroy this station. Doing so, although admittedly a challenge, would greatly impact this war against the machines.</t>
	<t id="170003">{1001,3}(Station)</t>
	<t id="180001">(Station)Create a Window of Opportunity</t>
	<t id="180002">We have to get a team of scientists close to a Xenon station in order to conduct an investigation. The issue is that the station's defences would tear us apart long before we even managed to set up our equipment. If you could destroy the station's turrets in preparation for our arrival, we would be able to conduct our research, and potentially identify weaknesses in the Xenon stations' design.\n\nStation: $STATION$\nNumber of turrets to destroy: $TURRETS$</t>
	<t id="180003">{30144,1003}</t>
  </page> 
</add>  
	<!--VANILLA-->	
  <replace sel="/language/page[@id='20003']/t[@id='60002']/text()[1]">A famous hub of technical expertise before the Jump Gate shutdown, thanks largely to the people stationed there to stop the influx of Xenon activity from neighbouring Xenon Sector 472, {20003,60001} now enjoys an extended era of peace. Still, its people have remained busy, attempting to build a self-sufficient community in case history repeats itself.\n\nThough the system finds itself cut off from Argon Federation space and under the authority of the Antigone Republic however the Argon Federation provides a steady stream of supplies desperate to show that no colony of theirs will be left to fend for itself even if no longer under their authority.</replace>
  <replace sel="/language/page[@id='20004']/t[@id='60022']/text()[1]">While the Black Hole Sun(same as {20003,60001}) system found itself in a comparatively stable situation after the Jump Gate shutdown, thanks to the cessation of Xenon incursions, the people of this sector are still subject to frequent piracy. Before the shutdown, pirates used to go out of their way to take upon themselves the arduous journey into the system, enticed by the rich pickings its remote position and instability provided. Nowadays, cut off from the other Argon systems, under the loose authority of the Antigone Republic, and situated in close proximity to both Teladi and Syndicate space, this sector makes for an even more attractive target.</replace>	
	
  <replace sel="/language/page[@id='20221']/t[@id='3061']/text()[1]">Cruiser</replace>
  <replace sel="/language/page[@id='20221']/t[@id='3062']/text()[1]">Heavier than a Destroyer, ships of this class are far better better against capital ships and stations but are extremely vulnerable to smaller ships.</replace>
</diff>  